<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Foods</string>

    <string name="hello_world" translatable="false">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings" translatable="false">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b1" translatable="false">B1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b2" translatable="false">B2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b3" translatable="false">B3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b4" translatable="false">B4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b5" translatable="false">B5</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b6" translatable="false">B6</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b7" translatable="false">B7</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b8" translatable="false">B8</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b9" translatable="false">B9</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b10" translatable="false">B10</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b11" translatable="false">B11</string>
    <string name="title_activity_biryani" translatable="false">Biryani</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hfoods" translatable="false">Hfoods</string>
 <string name="mirchisalan" translatable="false">
Ingredients\n
&#8226;2 cups long green chillies\n
&#8226;1 tsp cumin seeds (jeera)\n
&#8226;1/2 tsp mustard seeds \n
&#8226;1/4 tsp fenugreek (methi) seeds\n
&#8226;1/4 tsp nigella seeds (kalonji)\n
&#8226;6 curry leaves (kadi patta)\n
&#8226;1/4 tsp turmeric powder (haldi)\n
&#8226;2 tbsp dhania-jeera powder\n
&#8226;2 tsp chilli powder\n
&#8226;1 tbsp tamarind (imli) pulp\n
&#8226;2 tbsp chopped coriander (dhania)\n
&#8226;5 tbsp oil\n
&#8226;To be ground into a dry peanut-sesame powder\n
2 tbsp roasted peanuts\n
2 tbsp sesame seeds (til) , roasted\n
1 tbsp cumin seeds (jeera), roasted\n
&#8226;To be ground into a paste\n
6 cloves of garlic (lehsun)\n
12 mm piece of ginger (adrak)\n
&#8226;1/2 cup chopped onions\n
&#8226;1 cup chopped tomatoes\n
&#8226;3 tbsp grated coconut\n
\n
Procedure:\n
1)Wash and slit the green chillies. Remove the seeds and fry in hot oil until they turn whitish in colour. Remove and keep aside.\n
2)In the same oil, add the cumin seeds, mustard seeds, fenugreek seeds, nigella seeds and curry leaves.\n
3)When the seeds crackle, add the paste and cook for 2 minutes. \n
4)Add the turmeric powder, coriander-cumin seed powder, chilli powder and powdered peanut-sesame mixture.\n
5)Cook over a medium flame, stirring continuously until the oil separates.\n
6)Add 2 cups of water and tamarind pulp and bring it to a boil.\n
7)Add the fried green chillies, coriander and salt and simmer until the gravy thickens.\n
    </string>


    <string name="paaya" translatable="false">
Ingredients:\n
&#8226;8 nos. Trotters\n
&#8226;2 nos. Onions\n
&#8226;1 tblsp Coriander seeds\n
&#8226;1 tblsp Jeera\n
&#8226;4 nos. Brinjals\n
&#8226;4 nos. Dagad phool\n
&#8226;2 pieces Cinnamon\n
&#8226;6 nos. Cloves\n
&#8226;6 nos. Black pepper\n
&#8226;4 nos. Cardamoms (green)\n
&#8226;As per taste Salt\n
\n
Procedure-
1)Clean and cut the paaya into three pieces.\n
2)Tie the coriander seeds, cumin seeds, bay leaves, dagad phool,cinnamon, cloves, pepper and cardamoms in a small muslin cloth and secure the ends to form a small pouch.\n
3)Add enough water to the paaya and place over heat.\n
4)Add the chopped onions and the spice pouch along with salt as per taste.\n
5)Cook the gravy on slow fire, preferably over charcoal for 4 to 5 hours.\n
6)Remove the spice cloth and serve. Nahari is served in the morning.\n
7)Narhari cooked overnight on a slow fire and served for breakfast is delicious.\n
8)Serve hot with bread or rice.\n

    </string>





    <string name="qabooli" translatable="false">
Ingredients:\n
&#8226;Rice 1 kg\n
&#8226;Bengal Gram Split (chana Dal) 250 gms\n
&#8226;Salt to taste\n
&#8226;Green Cardamoms 6 no\n
&#8226;Cinnamon 2 inches stick\n
&#8226;Cloves 8 nos\n
\n
Procedure:\n
1)Wash and soak the rice for half hour. Then boil with salt and half the whole garam masala till almost done.\n
2)Wash and soak the chana dal for half an hour. Boil with salt, a little turmeric powder till just cooked.\n
3)Heat oil, add the remaining cinnamon, green cardamom, cloves and saute.\n
4)Add shahi jeera and when they crackle add ginger and garlic pastes and saute.\n
5)Add chopped green chillies and a little browned onions.\n
6)Add the cooked dal, garam masala powder, finely chopped coriander leaves and stir to mix well.\n
7)Add turmeric powder, stir and take it off heat. Add yogurt and mix well.\n
8)Transfer half of the dal mixture into another pan.\n
9)Spread half the rice over the dal mix, spread browned onions, garam masala powder, chopped mint leaves, lemon juice, saffron dissolved in water or milk.\n
10)Spread the remaining dal over this followed by rice, browned onions, garam masala powder, chopped mint leaves, lemon juice and saffron.\n
11)Cover with a tight fitting lid. After 2-3 minutes lower the heat and let it cook till done.\n
    </string>


    <string name="kheemapulao" translatable="false">
Ingredients:\n
&#8226;Keema or minced Mutton 200 gms\n
&#8226;Basmati Rice 1 1/2 cups\n
&#8226;Oil 2 tbsps\n
&#8226;Garam Masala Whole 1tsp \n
&#8226;Peppercorns 8-10\n
&#8226;Cumin Seeds 1 tsp.\n
&#8226;Garlic (chopped) 2 tsps\n
&#8226;Onions (chopped) 1/2 cup\n
&#8226;Green Chillies (chopped) 2 tsps\n
&#8226;Ginger Paste 1 tbsp.\n
&#8226;Garlic Paste 1 tbsp.\n
&#8226;Red Chilli Powder 1 tsp.\n
&#8226;Tomatoes (chopped) 1 cup\n
&#8226;Mint Leaves (chopped) 15-20\n
&#8226;Coriander Leaves (chopped) 2 tbsps\n
&#8226;Salt to taste\n
&#8226;Garam Masala Powder 1 tsp\n
\n
Procedure:\n
1)Pick and clean basmati rice. Soak for 30 minutes. Drain and leave aside.\n
2)Heat oil in a pan, add whole garam masala, pepper corns, cumin seeds, chopped garlic,chopped onions and chopped green chillies. Sauté well.\n
3)Add mutton mince and cook on high heat for a few minutes.\n
4)Add garlic paste, ginger paste, red chilli powder, chopped tomatoes, 3 1/2 cups of hot water,salt and soaked basmati rice. Mix lightly.\n
5)Add garam masala powder. Allow rice to cook over a high heat.\n
6)Cover the pan and further cook on low heat for 10-12 minutes.\n
7)Add chopped mint leaves and chopped coriander leaves. Serve keema pulao hot with mix vegetable raita.\n
</string>


    <string name="khorma" translatable="false">
Ingredients:\n
&#8226;1 medium Chicken\n
&#8226;3 nos. Onions\n
&#8226;12 nos. Garlic cloves\n
&#8226;1 inch Ginger\n
&#8226;6 nos. Red chillies\n
&#8226;2 nos. Tomatoes\n
&#8226;8 nos. Almonds\n
&#8226;6 nos. Cashew nuts\n
&#8226;1 tblsp Poppy seeds\n
&#8226;4 nos. Cloves\n
&#8226;2 pieces Cinnamon\n
&#8226;3 nos. Cardamoms (green)\n
&#8226;2 tblsp Khoya\n
&#8226;2 pinches Saffron\n
&#8226;1/2 cup Water\n
&#8226;3 tblsp Ghee\n
\n
Procedure:\n
1)Slice the onions and fry till they are crisp.\n
2)Blanch and chop the tomatoes. Grind together the almonds, poppy seeds, ginger, garlic, cardamoms, cinnamon and red chillies.\n
3)Soak the saffron in 1/2 cup water and keep aside.\n
4)Heat ghee and add the ground masala and fry till ghee leaves the sides.\n
5)Add the chopped tomatoes and fry till slightly tender.\n
6)Add the chicken pieces, crushed fried onion and salt.\n
7)Fry till ghee separates, then add 11/2 cups warm water.\n
8)When nearly done, add saffron and crumbled mava.\n
9)Simmer gently till chicken is tender.\n</string>



    <string name="ghoshtpasinde" translatable="false">
Ingredients:\n
&#8226;500 gms boneless mutton, cut into pieces and flattened\n
&#8226;3/4 cup beaten curd\n
&#8226;2 tsp chilli powder\n
&#8226;1/4tsp haldi\n
&#8226;2 tsp chironji\n
&#8226;2 tsp khus khus\n
&#8226;2 tsp garam masala\n
&#8226;2 tsp adrak-lasan paste\n
&#8226;3 onions, sliced fine\n
&#8226;A handful of kothmir, chopped\n
&#8226;2 tsp dhania\n
&#8226;3 tbsp ghee or refined oil\n
&#8226;Salt to taste\n
\n
Procedure:\n
1)To the pasinde apply the adrak-lasan paste and set aside.\n
2)Lightly roast and powder the following: khus khus, chironji and dhania.\n
3)Heat ghee, add the sliced onion and fry till crisp, then remove half.To the remaining half, add the pasinde and beaten curd, salt, chilli powder and haldi.\n
4)Fry till dry. Add the powdered masala and garam masala and fry a little.\n
5)Add 1 cup warm water and cook till tender. Finally sprinkle remaining crisp fried onion and chopped kothmir.\n
    </string>






    <string name="diwanihandi" translatable="false">
Ingredients:\n
&#8226;Potatoes 3\n
&#8226;French Beans 10-12\n
&#8226;Broad Beans (sem) 1 cup\n
&#8226;Carrots 3\n
&#8226;Green Peas (shelled) 1/2 cup\n
&#8226;Baby Brinjals 6\n
&#8226;Fenugreek Leaves (methi) 1 bunch\n
&#8226;Onions 3\n
&#8226;Ginger Paste 1 tsp.\n
&#8226;Garlic Paste 1 tsp.\n
&#8226;Red Chilli Powder 1 tsp.\n
&#8226;Turmeric Powder 1/2 tsp.\n
&#8226;Salt to taste\n
&#8226;Oil 1/2 cup\n
&#8226;Coriander Leaves 1 tbsp\n
&#8226;Green Chillies 6\n
\n
Procedure-\n
1)Clean the potatoes, french beans and broadbeans and cut into diamond shapes. Trim the brinjal top and slit into two.\n
2)Wash and chop fresh fenugreek leaves. Clean and chop coriander leaves.\n
3)Slice onions. De-seed green chillies and chop.\n
4)Heat oil in a cooking vessel, add sliced onions and lightly brown.\n
5)Add ginger and garlic pastes and stir well for a minute.\n
6)Add red chilli powder, turmeric powder and salt.\n
7)Add the fresh fenugreek leaves and cook for 3-4 minutes.\n
8)Add the prepared vegetables and stir well.\n
9)Pour a cup of water and simmer till the vegetables are cooked.\n
10)Once the vegetables are 3/4 cooked add the coriander leaves and green chillies.\n
11)Cook till all the water has evaporated.\n
12)Serve hot with Hyderabadi paratha\n
</string>



    <string name="bagrebaigan" translatable="false">
Ingredients:\n
&#8226;500 grams Brinjals\n
&#8226;4 medium Onions\n
&#8226;5 grams Ginger\n
&#8226;2 nos. Garlic cloves\n
1&#8226;2 grams Coriander seeds\n
&#8226;40 grams Sesame seeds\n
&#8226;70 grams Peanuts\n
&#8226;5 grams Cumin seeds\n
&#8226;3 grams Poppy seeds\n
&#8226;20 grams Dessicated coconut\n
&#8226;2 grams Fenugreek seeds\n
&#8226;2 grams Turmeric powder\n
&#8226;5 grams Red chilli powder\n
&#8226;6 grams Jaggery\n
&#8226;75 grams Tamarind\n
&#8226;4 grams Curry leaves\n
&#8226;120 ml Oil\n
\n

Procedure:\n
1)Soak the tamarind in 1 cup of water. Mash and sieve to get tamarind water.\n
2)Discard the residue and set aside.\n
3)Wash the brinjals, make 2 inch slits along the length ensuring that the end is intact.\n
4)Roast the onions on a griddle till they soften and turn light golden brown.\n
5)Dry roast together on medium heat the coriander seeds, sesame seeds, peanuts, cumin seeds, poppy seeds,dessicated coconut and the fenugreek seeds till they darken slighly and start emitting an aroma.\n
6)Grind together the onions, roasted spices, ginger, garlic, salt, turmeric powder, red chilli powder and jaggery to a fine paste.\n
7)Mix in the tamaind water.\n
8)Keep aside some of this mixture and stuff the brinjals with the remaining mixture.\n
9)Heat oil, add the curry leaves and saute for a few minutes.\n
10)Add the stuffed brinjals and fry for about 10 minutes. Add the reserved paste and mix gently.\n
11)Add little water, cover and cook on medium heat, stirring occasionally but very gently.\n
12)Cook till the brinjals are thoroughly cooked and oil leaves the sides of the pan.\n
</string>






    <string name="khattiarbikasalan" translatable="false">

Ingredients:\n
&#8226;Colocassia (arbi) 250 gms.\n
&#8226;Oil 3 tbsps.\n
&#8226;Onion (sliced) 1\n
&#8226;Curry Leaves 8-10\n
&#8226;Green Chillies 2-3\n
&#8226;Ginger Garlic Paste 1 tbsp.\n
&#8226;Turmeric Powder 1/2 tsp.\n
&#8226;Red Chilli Powder 1 tsp.\n
&#8226;Tomatoes 3 medium\n
&#8226;Salt to taste\n
&#8226;Tamarind Pulp 2 tbsps\n
\n
Procedure:\n
1)Peel and slice onions. Chop tomatoes, de-seed and chop green chillies.\n
2)Soak tamarind in lukewarm water for 15 minutes and squeeze out the pulp.\n
3)Boil Arbi in salted water till tender, peel, slice the bigger ones into two pieces if desired.\n
4)Heat oil in a pan and sauté onions till golden brown. Add curry leaves, chopped chillies, ginger garlic paste and sauté for a few minutes.\n
5)Add turmeric, red chilli powder and sauté for 3-4 minutes on a low heat.\n
6)Add chopped tomatoes and cook till the tomatoes are completely mashed.\n
7)Add the arbi and cook for 2 minutes pour one cup of water and salt, cook for2-3 minutes.\n
8)Add tamarind pulp. Cover and simmer for 15 minutes.\n
</string>

    <string name="pulao" translatable="false">
Ingredients\n
&#8226;Basmati rice 1 1/2 cups\n
&#8226;Potatoes 1/2 inch cubes2 large\n
&#8226;Carrots 1/2 inch cubes3 medium\n
&#8226;French beans 1/2 inch pieces5-6\n
&#8226;Cauliflower 1/4 small\n
&#8226;Salt to taste\n
&#8226;Saffron (kesar) 4-5 strands\n
&#8226;Milk 2 tablespoons\n
&#8226;Onions thinly sliced4 large\n
&#8226;Oil to deep fry\n
&#8226;Yogurt 1/2 cup\n
&#8226;Biryani masala 3 tablespoons\n
&#8226;Ginger paste 1 1/2 teaspoons\n
&#8226;Garlic paste 1 1/2 teaspoons\n
&#8226;Pure ghee 4 tablespoons\n
&#8226;Fresh mint leaves chopped 2 tablespoons\n
&#8226;Fresh coriander leaves chopped 2 tablespoons\n
&#8226;Cashewnuts quartered 5\n
&#8226;Almonds blanched and halved10\n
&#8226;Raisins 2 tablespoons\n
&#8226;Wheat flour dough to seal as required\n
\n
Procedure:\n
1)Pick, wash and soak rice in three cups of water for half an hour. Drain.\n
2)Add four cups of water and salt. Bring to a boil and cook till the rice is three fourth done\n
3)Drain excess water and spread out on a plate to cool. \n
4)Parboil potatoes, carrots, French beans and cauliflower in two cups of salted water.\n
5)Drain and keep aside. Dissolve saffron in warm milk. Heat sufficient oil in a kadai and deep-fry sliced onions till golden brown. Drain ontoan absorbent paper. Beat yogurt. Add two tablespoons of Biryani Masala, half of the fried onions, ginger paste and garlic paste and parboiled vegetables.Allow to marinate for one hour. Heat ghee in a thick-bottomed vessel, add the marinated vegetables and sauté for two to three minutes.\n
6)Add three-fourth cup of water and bring to a boil, then simmer for two to three minutes. Preheat oven to 180°C.\n
7)Transfer the vegetables into a thick bottomed handi. Layer the rice over the cooked vegetables.\n
8)Sprinkle the remaining Biryani Masala, mint leaves, coriander leaves and the remaining fried onions.Garnish with cashewnuts, almonds and raisins.\n
9)Sprinkle saffron milk. Place a moist cloth on top, cover with a lid and seal with dough.\n
10)Put the sealed handi in the pre-heated oven and cook at 180°C for fifteen to twenty minutes.\n
11)Alternately keep the handi on a heated tawa and cook on very low heat for fifteen to twenty minutes.\n

    </string>
    <string name="murghdopyaza" translatable="false">
Ingredients\n
&#8226;1 kg chicken-skinned and cut into 8 pieces\n
&#8226;1/4 cup ghee\n
&#8226;1 Tbsp cumin seeds\n
&#8226;1 bay leaf\n
&#8226;4 whole peppercorns\n
&#8226;4 cloves\n
&#8226;1/2 tsp fenugreek seeds-roasted and powdered\n
&#8226;1 tsp fennel seeds- roasted and powdered\n
&#8226;1 tsp ginger paste\n
&#8226;1 tsp garlic paste\n
&#8226;1 cup grated onions\n
&#8226;1 1/2 cup onions - sliced a little thick\n
&#8226;1/2 cup yoghurt\n
&#8226;1 tsp garam masala\n
&#8226;1/2 tsp turmeric\n
&#8226;1 Tbsp coriander powder\n
&#8226;1 tsp chilli powder\n
&#8226;2-3 green chillies-slit\n
\n
Procedure:\n
1)Heat the ghee in a heavy-based saucepan, and add the cumin seeds, bay leaf, peppercorns, cloves, powdered fenugreek and fennel seeds.\n
 2)When the seeds begin to splutter, add the garlic and ginger paste and the grated onions.\n
3)Saute over high heat till brown.\n
4)Add the yoghurt, stir-frying vigorously so that it blends well and does not curdle.\n
5)Cook till fat separates.\n
6)Add the garam masala, salt, turmeric, coriander and chilli powder.\n
7)Keeping the heat high, add the chicken pieces and stir till they look a little opaque and are coated with the masala.\n
8)Lower the heat, uncover and simmer for about 10 minutes.\n
9)Add the green chillies and sliced onions.\n
10)Continue cooking over low heat, till the chicken is cooked through and fat separates.\n
11)Takes 10-15 minutes. The onions should be crunchy.\n

    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_b" translatable="false">B</string>

    <string name="biryani" translatable="false">
Ingredients-\n
&#8226;1 kg meat\n
&#8226;1 Tbsp salt\n
&#8226;1 Tbsp ginger garlic paste\n
&#8226;1 Tbsp red chilli paste\n
&#8226;1 Tbsp green chilli paste sauteed brown onions to taste\n
&#8226;1/2 Tbsp cardamom powder\n
&#8226;3-4 sticks cinnamon\n
&#8226;1 Tbsp cumin seeds\n
&#8226;4 cloves pinch of mace mint leaves to taste\n
&#8226;2 Tbsp lemon juice 250 gm curd\n
&#8226;4 Tbsp clarified butter\n
&#8226;750 gm semi cooked rice\n
&#8226;1 tsp saffron\n
&#8226;1/2 cup water\n
&#8226;1/2 cup of oil\n
\n
Procedure-\n
1)Clean the meat. Then in a pan add meat, salt, ginger garlic paste, red chilli powder, green chilli paste, sauteed brown onions, cardamom powder, cinnamon, cumin seeds, cloves, mace, mint leaves and lemon juice. Mix it well.\n
2)Add curd, clarified butter, semi cooked rice, saffron, water and oil and mix it well.\n
3)Now apply sticky dough on the sides of the pan.\n
4)Cover with lid to seal it and cook for about 25 minutes.\n
5)Hyderabadi Biryani is ready to eat. Garnish it with boiled eggs, sliced carrots, cucumbers and serve hot.\n
    </string>
</resources>
