<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tohfa</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="desemaat">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_list">List</string>




    <string name="c1">
    TIME: This namaz should be recited between Maghrib and Isha namaz \n
NIYYAT: I am praying 2-rakat Namaz-e-Gofaila sunnath qurbatan ela-lah. \n
METHOD: In first rakat after Sura-e-Alhamd, recite: \n \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM \n
WA ZAN-NOONE IZ-ZAHABA MOGHAZEBAN, FA-ZAN-NAN AN LAN NAKDERA ALAYHE FA-NAADA FIZ-ZOLOMAATE AN-LAA-ELAAHA ILLAA ANTA SUBHAANAKA INNEE KUNTO MENAZ ZAALEMINA, FASTAJABNAA LAHU WA-NAJJAY-NAAHO MENAL GHAMME WA KAZAALEKA NUNJIL MOMENEEN(Sura-e-Ambiya,Ayat:87) \n \n
In second rakat, after Sura-e-Alhamd,recite: \n
     BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
WA I\’NDAHU MAFAATEHUL GHAYBE LAA YA\’LAMOHAA ILLAA HOWA, WA YA\’LAMO MAA FIL BARRE WAL BAHRE, WA MAA TASQOTO  MIN WARAQATIN ILLAA YA\’LAMOHAA WALAA HABBATIN FEE ZOLOMAATIL ARZE WA LAA RATBIWN WA LAA YAABESIN ILLAA FEE KETAABIM MOBEEN \n \n
In the qunoot, recite the following: \n
ALLAHOMMA SALLE A\’LAA MOHAMMADIN WA AALE MOHAMMAD , ALLAHUMMA INNI AS-ALOKA BE MAFAATEHIL GHAYBILLATEE LAA YA\’LAMOHAA ILLAA ANTA , AN TOASALLEY ALAA MOHAMMADIN WA AN TAF-A\’ALA BEE…  (THEN ASK WHATEVER YOUR WISH IS AND THEN RECITE )   ILMAN WASEA\’N , WA A\’MALAN SALEHAN , WA RIZAQAN HALALNA TAYYEBAN TAHERAN , ALLAHOMMMA ANTA WALIYYO NEA\’MATEE , WAL QADERO A\’LAATALEBATEE TA\’LAMO HAAJATEE FA - AS – ALOKA BE HAQQE MOHAMMADIN WA AALE MOHAMMAD .AN TOSALLE A\’LAA  MOHAMMADIN WA AALE MOHAMMAD \n




    </string>
    <string name="c2">

      TIME: This namaz should be prayed after Namaz-e-Isha,on the night the dead is buried.\n  \n
NIYYAT: I am praying 2-rakat namaz-e-wehshat qurbatan ellaallah.\n
METHOD: In the first rakat, after Sura-e-Alhamd, recite Ayatul Qursi once.\n
                  In the second rakat, after Sura-e-Alhamd, recite Sura-e-Qadr 10times.\n
After completing the namaz,say: O Allah! Give the sawab of this namaz to (the name of the dead)  son/daughter of (the father)




    </string>
    <string name="c3">
   This namaz can be recited for parents both dead and alive.\n \n
TIME: Every night between Maghrib and Isha Namazes\n
NIYYAT: I am reciting 2 rakat Namaz-e-hadiy-e-walidain khurbatan illalah. \n
METHOD: In the first rakat after Sura-e-alhamd recite the following 10 times\n

BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
RABBIGH FIRLEE WALE WAALEDAYYA WALIL MO-MENEENA YAWMA YAQOOMUL HESAAB.\n
In the second rakat after sura-e-alhamd recite the following 10 times\n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
RABBIGH FIRLEE WALE WAALEDAYYA WALEMAN DAKHALA BAYTEYA MO-MENAN WA LIL MO-MENEENA WAL MO-MENAAT.\n
After namaz, raise your hands and recite the following 10 times.\n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
RABBIR HAMHOMA KAMAA RABBAYAANEE SAGHEERAA.\n

    </string>

    <string name="c4">
The Tahajjud Prayer (Salaat al-Layl, Namaz-e-Shab) ranks first and foremost in importance among all other optional (Sunnat) prayers. Tahajjud means to abandon sleep so as to pray Salat. The Quran refers to it in Surah 17:79 and says, "And (during part) of the night, abandon sleep and keep vigil to pray Salat, in addition to the regular obligatory prayer. Your Rabb (the Sustainer) may (as a reward) elevate you to the position of High Distinction, Glory and Praise."\n

The verse quoted above which prescribes Salaat al-Layl has been placed immediately next to the verse (17:78) which prescribes the regular daily obligatory Salat. Therefore, it underscores the great importance of Salatul-Layl. Although optional, Tahajjud is considered "nearest to obligatory (Wajib) prayer."\n

While advising Imam \’Ali (as), the Prophet repeated three times, "\’Alayka Bis-Salatul-Layl" which means, "incumbent upon you (O! Ali) is Salat al-Layl." This Hadith underscores further the importance of Salatul-Layl. Therefore, we should try never to miss it. \n \n

MERITS:\n

Imam Jaffar Sadiq(as) quotes Imam Ali(as) as saying that the Prophet(sawaw) said that a person who prays Salat al-Layl gets the following twenty four kinds of benefits: \n
1. Secures Allah\’s pleasure.\n
2. Makes friendship with Angels.\n
3. Is the Sunnat of the Prophets (as)\n
4. Provides the means to pursue knowledge.\n
5. Constitutes the root of our faith.\n
6. Keeps one physically fit.\n
7. Drives Shaytan away.\n
8. Protects one from enemies.\n
9. Serves as a means of acceptance of one\’s Duas and good deeds.\n
10.    Increases one\’s livelihood.\n
11.    Intercedes with the Angel of Death.\n
12.    Lights up the grave.\n
13.    Provides comfortable bedding in the grave.\n
14.    Helps answering with ease the questioning of Munkar and Nakir in the grave.\n
15.    Gives companionship in the grave.\n
16.    Provides shelter on the Day of Judgment.\n
17.    Crowns one on the Day of Reckoning.\n
18.    Clothes one on the Day of Resurrection.\n
19.    Provides one with light on the Day of Judgment.\n
20.    Forms a barrier against the fire of Hell.\n
21.    Gets Allah\’s pardon on the Day of Judgment.\n
22.    Increases the weight of good deeds on the scale.\n
23.    Helps one crossing the Bridge of "Siraat" without any difficulty.\n
24.    Forms the key to the Paradise.\n \n

TIME: \nThe time for praying Salat al-Layl is from midnight (midnight is reckoned as the time which is exactly half the time between sunset and the actual dawn) to the time of Adhan for Fajr prayers. Some ulema consider it permissible to pray Salat al-Layl starting after Isha prayer.\n

 METHOD:\n First 8 rakats of 2-2 rakats should be recited as Namaz-e-Nafeela. In the first 2 rakats;  in the first rakat after Alhamd, recite Qul-Howallah once. In the second rakat after Alhamd recite Qul-ya ayyohal kaferoon once.\n
In the balance of six rakats recite any small sura. After completing 8 rakats, recite the Tasbeeh of Bibi Fatima(s.a).\n Then pray 2 rakat namaz-e-shafa. In both rakats after Alhamd, recite Qulhuwallah once or in the first rakat recite Qul Aozoo be rabbil falaq once and second rakat recite Qul aoozo be rabbin-nas once.( There is no qunoot in namaz-e-shifa).\n
After salam and tasbeeh, recite this dua:\n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
ELAAHI TA-A\’RRAZA LAKA FEE HAAZAL LAYLIL MOTA-A\’RREZOON WA QASADAKA FEEHIL QAASEDOON WA A\’MMALA  FAZLAKA WA  MA\’ROOFAQATTAALEBOON WA LAKA FEE HAAZAL LAYLE NAFAHAATUN WA JAWAAA-EZO WA A\’TAAYAA WA MAWAAHEBO TAMUNNO  BEHAA A\’LAA MAN TASHAA-O MIN E\’BAADEKA WA TAMNA-O\’HAA MAN LAM TASBIKA LAHUL E\’NAAYATO MINKA WA HAA ANAA-ZAA A\’BDOKAL FAQEERO ELAYKAL MO-AMMELO FAZLAKA WA MA\’ROOFAKA FA IN KUNTA YAA MAWLAAYA TAFAZZALTA FEE HAAZEHIL LAYLATE A\’LAA AHADIM MIN KHALQEKA WA OO\’DTA A\’LAYHE BE A\’AEDATIM MIN I\’TFEKA FA SALLE A\’LAA MOHAMMADIN WA AALE MOHAMMADENIT TAYYABEENAT TAAHEREENA FASTAJIB LEE KAMAA WA-A\’DTANEE INNAKA LAA TUKHLEFUL MEE-A\’AD.\n
After this dua, recite one-rakat Namaz-e-Vitr in which  after Al-hamd, recite Qul-Howallah 3 times, Qul-Aouzoo be rabbil falaq 3 times and Qul-Aouzoo be rabbin nas once. Then in qunoot recite the following:\n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
LAA ELAAHA ILALLAAHUL HALEEMUL KAREEM, LAA ELAAHA ILALLAAHUL A\’LIYYUL A\’ZEEM, SUBHAANALLAAHE RABBIS SAMAAWAATIS SAB-E\’ WA RABBUL ARZEENAS-SAB-E\’ WA MAA FEEHINNA WA MAA BAYNAHUNNA WAMAA FAWQAHUNNA WA MAA TAHTAHUNNA WA HOWA RABBUL A\’RSHIL A\’ZEEM WA SALAAMUN A\’LAL MURSALEEN WAL HAMDO LILLAAHE RABBIL A\’ALAMEEN YAA ALLAAHUL LAZEE LAYSA KAMISLEHI SHAYUN WAHOWAS SAMEE-U\’L BASEER WA SALLE A\’LAA MOHAMMADIN WA AALE MOHAMMED.\n
Then recite following \’istigfaar\’ 70 or 100 times.\n
ASTAGFERULLAAHA RABBI WA ATUBO ELAYHE\n
Then say 7 times\n
ASTAGHFERULLAAHAL LAZEE LAA ELAAHA ILLA HOWAL HAYYUL QAYYOOMO BE JAMEE-E\’ ZULMEE WA JURMEE WA ISRAAFEE A\’LAA NAFSEE WA ATOOBO ELAYHE.\n
Then say 7 times\n
HAAZAA MAKAAMUL AA-E\’ZO BEKA MENAN-NAAR\n
Then recite the following dua:\n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
RABBE ASA-TO WA ZALAMTO NAFSEE WA BEA-SA MAA SANA\’TO WA HAAZEHEE YADAAYA YAA RABBE JAZAA-EMA BEMAA KASABAT WA HAAZEHEE RAQABATEE KHAAZA-A\’TAN LE MAA AATAYTO WA HAA ANAAZAA BAYNA YADAYKA FAKHUZ LE NAFSEKA MIN NAFSIR  REZAA HATTAA TARZAA LAKAL U\’TBAA LAA A-U\’D.\n
Then recite \’AL-A\’FWO\’(forgive me) 300 times. Then say:\n
RABBIGH FIRLEE WARHAMNEE WA TUB A\’LAYYA INNAKA ANTAT-TAWWAABUR RAHEEM.\n
Then take names of 40 momeneens( dead or alive) and say\n
ALLAAHUMMAGH FIR LEE\n
(And take the names)\n





    </string>












<string name="a1">
        Recite this dua 133 times, according to the adaad of Hazrat Abul Fadhl Abbas(a.s) in one sitting.\n \n

BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
YA KASHEFAL KARBE AN WAJHIL HUSSAIN(A.S), IKSHIF KARBI BE HAQQE AKHIKAL HUSSAIN(A.S)

    </string>


    <string name="a2">
        Recite the following dua 3 times after Namaz-e-Fajr and 3 times after Namaz-e-Isha.\n \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
YAA ALLAHO YAA ALLAHO YAA ALLAHO, YAA RABBE YAA RABBE YAA RABBE, YAA HAYYO YAA QAYYOOMO, YAA ZAL\’JALAALE WAL IKRAAME AS\’ALOKA BISMEKAL AZ\’EEMIL A\’AZAME, ANTURZEQANEE RIZQAN WASEE-A\’N HALAALAN TAYYEBAN BE REHMATEKA YA ARHAMAR RAAHEMEEN\n
        \n
        It is narrated by Mulla Mohsin Kasani that by reciting the following, one will get so much sustenance that one will get fed up of counting it.\n \n
SUNDAY(1000 TIMES)\n
YAA RABBAL A\’ALAMEEN\n
MONDAY(1000 TIMES)\n
YAA ZAL\’JALAALE WAL IKRAAM\n
TUESDAY(1000 TIMES)\n
YAA KAAZEYAL HAJAAT\n
WEDNESAY(1000 TIMES)\n
YAA ARHAMAR RAAHEMEEN\n
THURSDAY( 1000 TIMES)\n
YAA HAYYO YAA QAYYUM\n
FRIDAY(1000 TIMES)\n
LAA ELAAHA ILLAL\’LAAHUL MALEKUL HAQQUL MOBEEN\n
SATURDAY(1000 TIMES)\n
 ALLAHUMAA S\’ALLI A\’LAA MUH\’AMMADIN W\’WA AALI MUH\’MMAD


    </string>
    <string name="a3">
Recite this dua after morning prayers(fajr). This dua is from the book of \’Minhaz\’. By reciting this dua always, there will be considerable increase in sustenance and debts will also be repaid.\n \n

BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
TAWAKKALTO A\’LAL HAYYIL LAZEE LAA  YAMOOTO WAL HAMDO LILLAAHIL LAZEE LAM YATTAKHIZ WALADAN WA LAM YAKUN LAHU SHARIKUN FIL MULK, WA LAM YAKUN LAHU WALIYYUM MINAZ-ZULLE WA KABBIRHO TAKBEERAA. ALLAAHUMMA INNEE A-OO\’ZO BEKA MENAL BOA-SE WAL FAQRE WA MIN GHALABATID DAYNE WAS-SUQME WA ASALOKA AN TO-EE\’NANEE A\’LAA ADAA-E HAQQEQAA ELAYKA WA ADAA-E HAQQINNAASE ELANNAAS




    </string>
    <string name="a4">
Hazarat Imam Jaffer-e-Sadiq(a.s) has said that if one recites the following dua after Namaz-e-Fajr, the wings of Jibraeel will cover him and he will be protected from all problems of life, children and wealth.\n
        \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
ASTAWDEULLAAHAL A\’ZEEMAL JALEEL NAFSE WA AHLEE WA MAALEE WA WALADEE WA MAYN-YA\’NEENEE AMROHU WA ASTAWDEULLAAHAL MARHOOBAL MAKHOOFAL MOTA-ZA\’ZE\’ LE A\’ZAMATEHEE KULLA SHAYIN NAFSE WA AHLEE WA MAALEE WA WALADEE WA MAYN-YA\’NEENEE AMROHU
    </string>


    <string name="a5">
 Hazarat Imam Jaffer-e-Sadiq(a.s) has said that if one recites the following Tahlil 10 times, without shifting his ankle from his place after namaz, Allah(s.w.t) will forgive his 40000 sins and 4 crore good deeds will be written in his account. It is as if he has read the Holy Quraan 12 times. The Holy Prophet(p.b.u.h) has said that, “ I am reciting it 100 times but for you 10 times is enough.”\n
        \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
ASH-HADO AN LAA ELAAHA ILLALLAAHO WAHDAHU LAA SHAREEKA LAHU ELAAHAN WAAHEDAN AHADAN SAMADAN LAM-YATTAKHIZ SAAHEBATAN WALAA WALADAA
    </string>


    <string name="a6">
Hazarat Amir-al Momineen(a.s) has said that if one recites the following ayat before going to sleep, noor will spread from his bed to the Holy Ka\’aba and from there to the Baitul Muqaddas and angels will remain around the noor till morning and will pray to Allah(s.w.t) to forgive his sins.\n
Hazarat Imam Jaffer-e-Sadiq(a.s) has said that if one goes to sleep after reciting this ayat,he will get up at the desired time.\n
        \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
QUL INNAMA ANA BASHARUN MITHLUKUM YOOHA ILAYYA ANNAMA ILAHUKUM ILAHUN WAHIDUN FAMAN KANA YARJOO LIQAA RABBIHI FALYAAAMAL AAAMALAN SALIHAN WALA YUSHRIK BIAAIBADATI RABBIHI AHADA
    </string>

    <string name="a7">
 It is written in \’Lealiye Makhzuna\’ that for all manifest and hidden diseases of children, put sadqa below the pillow of the sick and recite the following dua continuously. The Sadqa kept should be given to a poor momin in the morning. In\’sha\’allah the person will get relief by morning.\n
        \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
ALLAHUMMA INNI AS\’ALOKA BE HAQQE WALIYYEKA MOOSABNA JA\’FAR, ILLAA AA\’FAYTANEE FEE JAMEE-E\’ JAWAAREEHEE MAA ZAHARA MINHAA WA MAA BATAN, WA DAF-A\’T A\’NNEE JAMEEU\’L AALAAME WAL ASQAAME YAA JAWAADO YAA KAREEM YAA ARHAMAR RAAHEMEEN
    </string>
    <string name="a8">
Hazrat Ali ibn Abu Talib(a.s) has prescribed this dua which is to be recited three times always.\n
        \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
ALLAAHO QADEEMUN AZALIYYUN YOZEELUL ELAL,WA HOWA QAA-EMUN AZALIYYUN BIL AZALIYYATE LAM YAZAL WALAA YOZAALO BE RAHMATEKA YAA ARHAMAR RAAHEMEENA WA SALLALLAAHO A\’LAA MOHAMMADIWN WA AALEHIT TAYYEBEENAT TAAHEREENA

    </string>
    <string name="a9">
A man saw the Holy Prophet(s.a.w) in his dreams many times. Everytime he asked, \’\’O Hazrat! What should I do so that when I die, my imaan(faith) is intact.\’\’ The Holy Prophet(s.a.w) replied, recite this dua always.\n
        \n
 BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
YAA ALLAAHO YAA ALLAAHO YAA ALLAAHO AL-AMAANO AL-AMAANO AL-AMAANO MIN ZAWAALIL EEMAAN, YAA DAA-EMAL MA\’ROOFE YAA QADEEMAL EHSAANE, WA YAA HAADEYAL MOZILLEEN IYYAAKA NA\’BODO WA IYYAKA NASTA-EE\’N WA SALLALLAAHO A\’LAA KHAYRE KHALQEHEE MOHAMMADIN WA AALEHI AJMAEEN
    </string>



    <string name="a10">
If you recite this \’vird\’, you will get 7 benefits:\n
1.Honour\n
        2.Status\n
        3.Sustenance\n
        4.Love\n
        5.Power\n
        6.Peace\n
        7.Hashmat\n
        \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
HASBEYALLAAHO LAA ELAAHA ILLAA HOWA A\’LAYHE TAWAKKALTO WA HOWA RABBUL A\’RSHIL A\’ZEEM\n \n
This vird is to be recited in three ways:\n
(1)    Recite 3699 times\n
(2)    Recite 64 times\n
(3)    Recite 18 times\n

    </string>






    <string name="a11">
It is narrated by Mukatil bin Suleman that,\’\’ I was beseeching Allah (s.w.t) for Ism-e-Azam for 20 years. Then once when I was in Baitul Muqadas, someone taught me the following dua in my dream.The influence of this dua is such that Allah(s.w.t) will surely accept your dua, if your dua is not accepted, then curse be upon me. \n \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
YAA QADEEMO, YA HAQQO, YAA DAA-EMA, YAA QAA-EMO, YA FARDO, YA SAMADO, YA ALLAHO, YA RAHMANO, YA RAHEEMO, YA HAYYO, YA QAYYOOMO, YA ZALJALAALE WAL IQRAAME, YA NOORAS-SAMAAWATE WAL ARZE WA MAA BAYNAHOMAA, WA RABBUL A\’RSHIL A\’ZEEM, WA YAA MAN LAM YALID, WA LAM YOOLAD WA LAM YAKUL LAHOO KUFUWAN AHAD, YAA KAAFEE YAA HAADEE YAA BAARE-O, YAA AA\’LEMO, YAA SAADEQO, YAA KAAF-HAA-YAA-A\’YN-SWAAD. YAA RABBAL ARBAAB, YAA SAYYADAS-SAADAAT YAA MALEKAL MOLOOK, YAA WALIYYAD DUNYAA WAL AAKHERAAH, ALLAHUMMA ANTA MALEKO MAN FIS SAMAA-E, WA MALEKO MAN FIL ARZE WALAA HUKMA FE HEMAA LE GHAYREKA WA QUDRATEKA FIL ARZEKA QUDRATEKA FISSAMAA-E, WA SULTAANEKA FIL ARZEKA, SULTAANEKA FIS-SAMAA-E, AS-ALOKA BISMEKAL KAREEM, WA WAJ-HAKAL MONEER, INNAKA A\’LAA KULLE SHAYIN QADEER, AN TOSALLEYA A\’LAA MOHAMMADIN WA AALE MOHAMMED, WA AN TOFARREJA A\’NNEE FARAJAN AAJELAN WAJ-A\’LLEE MIN KULLE GHAMMIN FARAJAN WA MAKHRAJAN WA YASSIRLEE KUL A\’SEER YA ARHAMAR RAAHEMEEN.
    </string>




    <string name="a12">
Allama Qummi on the \’Hashiya\’ of Mafatihul-Jinnan, has narrated from Ibn-e-Fahad that Abu Dawood was informed that his house is on fire. He replied saying that his house wasn\’t on fire. Then a second news came that his house was not burning. Third news came that houses around his house were burning but his house wasn\’t. So people asked Abu Dawood how he came to know that his house wasn\’t burning. He replied, \’\’ I have heard from the Holy Prophet(s.a.w) that if one recites the following dua in the morning, no loss will occur to him on that day. If it is recited at night, no loss will occur during the night.\’\’ It is narrated that for protection the 4 Quls should also be recited. \n \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
ALLAHUMMA ANTA RABEE, LAA ELAAHA ILLA ANTA. ALAYKA TAWAKKALTO WA ANTA RABBUL A\’RSHIL A\’ZEEM WA LAA HAWLA WA LAA QUWWATA ILLAA BILLAAHIL A\’LIYYIL A\’ZEEM. MAA-SHAA-ALLAAHO KAANA WA MAA LAM YASHAAA-O LAM YAKUN A-A\’LMO INNALLAAHA A\’LAA KULLE SHAYIN QADEET. WA ANNALLAAHA QAD AHAATA BE KULLE SHAYIN I\’LMAA. ALLAHUMMA INNEE A-OO\’ZO BEKA MIN SHARRE NAFSE WA MIN SHARRE QAZAA-IS-SOOO-E WA MIN SHARRE KULLE ZEE SHARRIWN WA MIN SHARRIL JINNE WAL INSE WA MIN SHARRE DAAB-BATIN ANTA AAKHEZUN BE NAASEYATEHAA INNA  RABBEE A\’LAA SERAATIM MUSTAQEEM




    </string>




    <string name="a13">
It is written in \’Zainul Muttakin\’ that by reciting this dua \n
(1)    Calamities and difficulties are suppressed.\n
(2)    Sustenance(Rozi) increases.\n
(3)    You over power your enemy.\n
(4)    You become respectful in the eyes of the people.\n
(5)    Your prayers are answered.\n
First recite Bismillah and Sura-e-Alhamd 3 times then recite the following dua.\n \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
MOHAMMADAR RASOOLULLAH SALLALLAAHO A\’LAYHE WA AALEHI AMAAMEE WA FAATEMATO BINTE RASOOLILLAAHEE FAWKA RAASE WA AMEERAL MOMEENEENA A\’LIYUBNO ABEE TAALIBIN WASIYYO RASOOLILLAAHE AN YAMEENEE WAL HASANO WAL HUSAYNO WA A\’LIYUN WA MOHAMMADUN WA JA\’FARUN WA MOOSAA WA A\’LIYYUN WA MOHAMMADIN WA A\’LIYYUN WAL HASANO WAL HUJJATAL MUNTAZERO MOHAMMADUN SAAHEBUZ-ZAMAAN A-IMMATEE SALAWAATULLAAHE A\’LAYHIM A\’N SHEMAALEE WA ABU ZARRIN WA SALMAANO WA MIQDAADO WA HAZAYFATO WA A\’MMAARATO WA ASHAABO RASOOLILLAHE RAZEYALLAAHO A\’NHUM MIWN-WARAA-EE WAL MALAA-EKATO A\’LAYHEMUS-SALAAMO HAWLEE, WALLAHO TA-A\’LAA SHAANOHU WA TAQADDASAT ASMAA-OHU MOHEETUN BEE WA HAAFEZEE WA HAFEEZEE, WALLAAHO MIWN WARAA-EHIM-MOHEET, BAL HOWA QURANUM MAJEED, FEE LAWHIM MAHFOOZ, FALLAAHO KHAYRUN HAAFEZAA WA HOWA ARHAMUR RAHEMEEN YAA A\’LIYYO YAA A\’LIYYO YAA A\’LIYYO SUBHAANALLAAHE WAL HAMDO LILLAAHE WA LAA ELAAHA ILLAL-LAAHO WALLAHO AKBAR WA LAA HAWLA WA LAA QUWWATAILLAA BILLAAHIL A\’LIYYIL A\’ZEEM, BE RABBIL KARIM, WA HOWAL A\’LIYYUN WALIYYUN NADEEMO YAA WAAHED.
ALLAHUMAA S\’ALLI A\’LAA MUH\’AMMADIN W\’WA AALI MUH\’MMAD

    </string>




    <string name="a14">
 It is narrated from the \’Ahlulbayt-e-Tahereen\’ that whomever recites the following dua 70 times every Friday, will become rich before 3 Fridays have passed. \n \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
YAA MOFEEDO YAA GHAFOORO YA WADOODO AGHNENEE BE HALAALEKA, WA BE TAA-ATEKA A\’N MA\’SEYATEKA WA FE FAZLEKA A\’MMAN SEWAAKA BE RAHMATEKA YAA ARHAMAR RAHEMEEN.





    </string>



    <string name="a15">
It is narrated by Hazrat Amir-al-Momineen(a.s) that one day the Holy Prophet(s.a.w) asked me: “O Ali, do you wish that I teach you such a thing that even if all the inhabitants of the 7 skies and 7 earths collectively wish to harm you, they cannot do it and whosoever desired to gain victory over you will not succeed.” I requested, O Holy Prophet, do teach me such a thing. Then the  Holy Prophet said that there are seven ayats in the Holy Quraan that one should recite and blow on oneself serially. \n
He(s.a.w) said, “O Ali, whosoever recited these  Hayqals or keeps them with him, Allah(s.w.t) will erase his 70000 sins, 70000 good deeds will be written in his name, 70000 palaces will be built for him in Paradise, he will have 70000 \’hullas\’—except Allah s.w.t, no one knows the significance of these \’hullas\’. Whosoever recites these 7 hayqals or keeps them with him, on the day of judgment, Allah(s.w.t) by His mercy and grace of the 7 Hayqals, will forgive him even if he deserves punishment(azaab). O Ali, if a sick person wears it around his neck, he will be cured. After reciting this and blowing it on oneself if one goes to meet a person in authority, he will get respect and the person will not be displeased with him.’\n
These ayats can be recited at anytime—but preferably after namaz with wudu.\n  \n

(1)    TO BLOW IN THE FRONT\n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
QUL LAN\’Y YUS\’EEBANAA ILLAA MA KATABALLAAHU LANA HUWA MAWLAANAA WA A\’LALLAAHI FAL—YATAWAKKALIL MUW—MINEEN
ALLAHUMAA S\’ALLI A\’LAA MUH\’AMMADIN W\’WA AALI MUH\’MMAD\n \n
(2)    TO BLOW ON THE BACK\n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
WA IN\’Y YAMSASKALLAAHU BI—Z”URRIN FALAA KAASHIFA LAHOOO ILLAA HUW WA IN\’Y YURIDKA BI—KHAYRIN\’ FALAA RAAADDA LI—FAZ”LIH YUS\’EEBU BIHEE MAN\’Y YASHAAA—U MIN I\’BAADIH WA HUWAL GHAFOORUR RAH\’EEM
ALLAHUMAA S\’ALLI A\’LAA MUH\’AMMADIN W\’WA AALI MUH\’MMAD \n \n
(3)    TO BLOW OVER THE HEAD\n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM \n
WA MAA MIN\’ DAAABBATIN\’FIL ARZ”I ILLAA A\’LALLAAHI RIZQUHAA WA YAA\’—LAMU MUSTAQARRAHAA WA MUSTAWDA—A\’HAA KULLUN\’FEE KITAABIM MUBEEN
ALLAHUMAA S\’ALLI A\’LAA MUH\’AMMADIN W\’WA AALI MUH\’MMAD \n \n


(4)    TO BLOW DOWNWARDS\n

BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM \n
INNEE TAWAKKALTU A\’LALLAAHI RABBEE WA RABBIKUM MAA MIN\’ DAAABBATIN ILLAA HUWA AAKHID\’UM BI—NAAS\’IYATIHAA INNA RABBEE A\’LAA S\’IRAAT\’IM MUSTAQEEM
ALLAHUMAA S\’ALLI A\’LAA MUH\’AMMADIN W\’WA AALI MUH\’MMAD \n \n
(5)    TO BLOW ON THE RIGHT SIDE\n
                         BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
WA KA—AYYIM MIN\’ DAAABBATIL LAA TAH\’MILU RIZQAHAA ALLAAHU YARZUQUHAA WA IYYAAKUM WA HUWAS SAMEE—U\’L A\’LEEM
ALLAHUMAA S\’ALLI A\’LAA MUH\’AMMADIN W\’WA AALI MUH\’MMAD \n \n
(6)    TO BLOW ON THE LEFT SIDE \n
                        BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM \n
MAA YAFTAH\’ILLAAHU LINNAASI MIR RAH\’MATIN\’ FALAA MUMSIKA LAHAA WA MAA YUMSIK FALAA MURSILA LAHOO MIM BAA\’—DIH WA HUWAL A\’ZEEZUL HAKEEM
ALLAHUMAA S\’ALLI A\’LAA MUH\’AMMADIN W\’WA AALI MUH\’MMAD \n \n


(7)    TO BLOW ALL OVER THE BODY \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM\n
WA LA—IN SA—ALTAHUM MAN KHALAQAS SAMAA WAATI WAL ARZ”A LAYAQOOLUNNALLAAH QUL A—FARA—AYTUM MAATAD—O\’ONA MIN\’ DOONILLAAHI IN ARAADANIYAL—LAAHU BI—Z”URRIN HAL HUNNA KAASHIFAATU Z”URRIHEEE AW ARAADANEE BI—RAH\’MATIN HAL HUNNA MUMSIKAATU RAH\’MATIH QUL H\’ASBIYALLAAH A\’LAYHI YATAWALLALUL MUTAWAKKILOON
ALLAHUMAA S\’ALLI A\’LAA MUH\’AMMADIN W\’WA AALI MUH\’MMAD \n
    </string>



    <string name="a16">
        This ayat of Surah Nahl is very effective and beneficial to safeguard against calamities, oppressors and enemies, for ease from difficulties for repayment of debts as well as fulfillment of your needs. \n
This ayat is very effective if you are apprehended. It should be recited 1,20,000 times with wudu in one sitting. Either one person recites or all recite collectively. It is necessary to recite totally 1,20,000 times. Both for ladies and gents. \n \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM \n
AMMAYN YOJEEBUL MUZTARRA EZAA DA-AA\’HO WA YAKSHEFUS-SOOO\’ \n
(Who answers the distressed one when he calls upon Him and removes the evil-Surah Nahl; Ayat 62)





    </string>



    <string name="a17">
        In \’Zainul Muttakin\’, it is narrated from the Holy Prophet(s.a.w) that whoever recites the following dua after Namaz-e-Fajr will get a reward of performing 1000 Haj and 1000 Shab-e-Baraats and praying namaaz over 1000 Shaheed(martyrs). Jibraael then came and said, “ O Mohammed(s.a.w), I have  brought such glad tidings which I have not brought for any other prophet. It is that whoever from your followers(ummat) recites this dua after Namaz-e-Fajr once and keep the dua with him, Allah( s.w.t) will bless him with seven things:\n
(1)    He will not die a sudden death.\n
(2)    He will be saved from the questions of Munkar and Nakir.\n
(3)    There will be no darkness or lack of space in his grave.\n
(4)    The doors of hell will be closed for him.\n
(5)    He will be protected from sicknesses.\n
(6)    All the 8 doors of paradise will open for him.\n
(7)    He will be saved from the anger of the kings.\n \n
                         BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM \n
LA ELAAHA ILALLAAHUL JALEELUL JABBARO LA ELAAHA ILLAAHUL A\’ZEEZUL GHAFFARO LA ELAHA ILLAAHUL WAHEEDUL QAHHAARO LA ELAAHA ILALLAAHO  WAHDAHU LAA SHAREEKA LAHU ELAAHAN WAAHEDAN WA NAHNO LAHU MUSLEMOON LA ELAAHA ILALLAHO WAHDAHU LAA SHAREEKA LAHU ELAAHAN WAHEEDAN WA NAHNO LAHU MUKHLESOON LA ELAAHA ILALLAAHO WAHDAHU LAA SHAREEKA LAHU ELAAHAN WAAHEDAN WA NAHNO LAHU A\’ABEDOON LA ELAAHA ILALLAAHO MOHAMMADUN RASOOLULLAH A\’LIYYUN WALIYULLAAAH, WA SALLALLAAHO A\’LAA KHAYRE KHALQEHI WA MAZHARE LUTFEHI MOHAMMADIN WA AALEHI AJMA-E\’ENAT TAYYEBEENAT TAAHEREENA BE RAHMATEKA YAA ARHAMAR RAAHEEMEEN. HASBONALLAAAHO WA NE\’MAL WAKEEL NE\’MAL MAWLAA WA NE\’MAL NASEER









    </string>





    <string name="a18">
Dua by Amir-al-Momineen, Ali ibn Abi Talib(a.s) for increase in memory. \n \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM \n
SUBHAANA MAN LAA YA\’TADEE A\’LAA AHLE MAMLAKATEHEE, SUBHAANA MAN LA YA\’KHOZO AHLAL ARZE BE ALWAANIL A\’ZAABE, SUBHAANAR RA-OOFIR RAHEEM, ALLAAHUMMAJ-A\’L LEE FEE QALBEE NOORAN WA BASARAN WA FAHMAN WA I\’LMAN INNAKA A\’LAA KULLE SHAYIN QADEER



    </string>
    <string name="a19">
Hazarat Imam Reza(a.s) has said: Recite this ayat before going on a journey of any type of vehicle. You will not meet with an accident. Even if the accident takes place, you will not be injure.\n \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM \n
SUBHAANALLLAZEE SAKH-KHARA LANAA HAAZAA WA MAA KUNNAA LAHU MUKRENEEN. WA INNA ELAA RABBENAA LA MUNWALEBOON




    </string>
    <string name="a20">
 Jibraael came in the presence of the Holy Prophet(s.a.w) in a happy mood and said, \’\’ Allah(s.w.t) has sent the following dua as a gift from the treasures of heaven.\’\’ Then the Holy Prphet(s.a.w) asked, “ O Jibraeel, what is the reward of reciting this dua?” Jibraeel replied, “Even if all the angels of the heaven and the earth join to describe the sawaab of this Dua till the day of Judgement, they will not be able to describe one-thousandth part of the sawaab. Any momin who recites this dua and utters the following words of the dua- Yaa Man Azharal Jameel Wa Sataral Qabeeh, Allah(s.w.t) will cover all his sins and He will show mercy on him in this world and his defects will be covered under 1000 veils in this world and the next. \n \n
BISMILLAAHIR RAH\’MAANI RAH\’EEM \n
YAA MAN AZHARAL JAMEEL WA SATARAL QABEEH, YAA MAN LAM YO-AAKHIZ BIL JAREERATE WALAM YAHTEKIS-SITRE YAA A\’ZEEMAL A\’FWE YAA HASANAT TAJAAWOZE, YAAA WAASE-A\’L MAGHFERATE YAA BAASETAL YADAYNE BIR RAHMATE, YAA SAAHEBA KULLE NAJWAA WA MUNTAHAA KULLE SHAKWAA, YAA MUBTADEYAN BIN-NE\’ME QABLA ISTEHKAAQEHAA, YAA RABBANAA YAA SAYYADANAA WA MAWLAANA WA GHAAYATA RAGHBATENAA, AS-ALOKA YAA ALLAAHO YAA ALLAAHO YAA ALLAAHO, AN LAA TOSHAWWEH KHALQINNAAR BE REHMATEKA YAA ARHAMAR RAAHEMEEN




    </string>














    <string name="tduaehazin">

In the name of Allah, The Beneficent, the Merciful\n
        O Allah bless Muhammad and his family \n
I whisper unto You O One Who is present in every place
so that You may hear my call for surely my sin is excessive and my shame is less

My Master, O my Master which of the terrifying states shall I remember and which of them shall I forget for if there was nothing except death it would be enough
 then what about after death greater and much worse?
        My master O my Master up to when and till when will I say, I am to blame, again and again, but then You do not find any truth or loyalty in me? I call for help and I call for help,

O Allah from desires which have overpowered me and from the enemy which has pounced on me and from the world which attracts me and from the soul that leads towards evil except that on which my Lord has mercy (12:53)
        My master O my master if You have had mercy on the likes of me then have mercy on me and if You have accepted from the likes of me then accept from me

O One Who accepts the early morning prayer accept me, O One who, I still know only good from Him O One who nourishes me with blessings morning and evening have mercy on me when I come to You alone, my glance fixed on You my actions carried on my neck When all of creation will withdraw away from me
        yes, even my father and mother and those for whom I worked and struggled then if You will not have mercy on me who will have mercy on me

who will give me solace from the loneliness of the grave and who will make me speak when I am alone with my deeds and when You will ask me about what You know better than me?
Then if I say yes (to my sins) where will be the escape from Your Justice? And if I say I did not commit it You will say was I not a witness over you?
        So (I beseech) Your Forgiveness Your Pardon O my master before the wearing of the clothes of Hell

Your Forgiveness Your Pardon O my Master before the Hell and the Fire Your Forgiveness Your Forgiveness O my Master before the hands are tied to the necks

O the most Merciful and the best of Forgivers






    </string>

    <string name="tduaekumayl">
        In the name of Allah, the Beneficent, the
Merciful \n
O Allah! Bless Muhammad and his
progeny. \n
O Allah! I beseech Thee by Thy mercy
which encompasses all things And by Thy
power by which Thou overcometh all
things and submit to it all things and
humble before it all things And by Thy
might by which Thou hast conquered all
things And by Thy majesty against which
nothing can stand up And by Thy
grandeur which prevails upon all things
And by Thy authority which is exercised
over all things And by Thy own self that
shall endure forever after all things have
vanished And by Thy Names which
manifest Thy power over all things And
by Thy knowledge which pervades all
things And by the light of Thy
countenance which illuminates everything
O Thou who art the light! O Thou who art
the most holy! O Thou who existed before
the foremost! O Thou who shall exist
after the last! O Allah! Forgive me my
such sins as would affront my continency
O Allah! Forgive me my such sins as
would bring down calamity O Allah!
Forgive me my such sins as would change
divine favours (into disfavours (O Allah!
Forgive me my such sins as would hinder
my supplication O Allah! Forgive me such
sins as bring down misfortunes (or
afflictions) O Allah! Forgive my such sins
as would suppress hope O Allah! Forgive
every sin that I have committed and
every error that I have erred O Allah! I
endeavour to draw myself nigh to Thee
through Thy invocation And I pray to
2
Thee to intercede on my behalf And I
entreat Thee by Thy benevolence to draw
me nearer to Thee And grant me that I
should be grateful to Thee and inspire me
to remember and to invoke Thee O Allah!
I entreat Thee begging Thee
submissively, humbly and awestrickenly
To treat me with clemency and mercy,
and to make me pleased and contented
with what Thou hast allotted to me And
cause me to be modest and unassuming
in all circumstances O Allah! I beg Thee
as one who is passing through extreme
privation and who supplicates his needs
to Thee and his hope has been greatly
raised by that which is with Thee O Allah!
Great is Thy kingdom and exalted is Thy
greatness Thy plan is secret, Thy
authority is manifest, Thy might is
victorious and subduing and Thy power is
prevalent throughout and it is not
possible to escape from Thy dominion O
Allah! Except Thee I do not find any one
able to pardon my sins nor to conceal my
loathsome acts Nor have I any one
except Thee to change my evil deeds into
virtues There is no god but Thou glory
and praise be to Thee I have made my
own soul to suffer I had the audacity (to
sin) by my ignorance Relying upon my
past remembrance of Thee and Thy grace
towards me O Allah! My Lord! How many
of my loathsome acts hast Thou screened
(from public gaze) How many of my
grievous afflictions (distresses) hast Thou
reduced in severity And how many of my
stumblings hast Thou protected, how
many of my detestable acts has Thou
averted, and how many of my
undeserving praises hast Thou spread
abroad! O Allah! My trials and sufferings
3
have increased and my evilness has
worsened, my good deeds have
diminished and my yokes (of misdeeds)
have become firm And remote hopes
restrain me to profit (by good deeds) and
the world has deceived me with its
allurements and my own self has been
affected by treachery and procrastination
Therefore, my Lord! I implore Thee by
Thy greatness not to let my sins and my
misdeeds shut out access to my prayers
from reaching Thy realm and not to
disgrace me by exposing those (hidden
ones) of which Thou hast knowledge nor
to hasten my retribution for those vices
and misdeeds committed by me in secret
which were due to evil mindedness,
ignorance, excessive lustfulness and my
negligence O Allah! I beg Thee by Thy
greatness to be compassionate to me in
all circumstances and well disposed
towards me in all matters My God! My
Nourisher! Have I anyone except Thee
from whom I can seek the dislodging of
my evils and understanding of my
problems? My God! My Master! Thou
decreed a law for me but instead I
obeyed my own low desires And I did not
guard myself against the allurements of
my enemy He deceived me with vain
hopes whereby I was led astray and fate
helped him in that respect Thus I
transgressed some of its limits set for me
by Thee and I disobeyed some of Thy
commandments; Thou hast therefore a
(just) cause against me in all those
matters and I have no plea against Thy
judgement passed against me I have
therefore become (justifiably) liable to
Thy judgement and afflictions But now I
have turned Thee, my Lord, after being
4
guilty of omissions and transgressions
against my soul, apologetically,
repentantly, broken heartedly, entreating
earnestly for forgiveness, yieldingly
confessing (to my guilt) as I can find no
escape from that which was done by me
and having no refuge to which I could
turn except seeking Thy acceptance of
my excuse and admitting me into the
realm of Thy capacious mercy O Allah!
Accept my apology and have pity on my
intense sufferings and set me free from
my heavy fetters (of evil deeds) My
Nourisher! Have mercy on the infirmity of
my body, the delicacy of my skin and the
brittleness of my bones O\’ Thou! Who
originated my creation and (accorded
me) my individuality, and (ensured) my
upbringing and welfare (and provided)
my sustenance (I beg Thee) to restore
Thy favours and blessings upon me as
Thou didst in the beginning of my life O\’
my God! My master! My Lord! And my
Nourisher! What! Wilt Thou see me
punished with the fire kindled by Thee
despite my belief in Thy unity? And
despite the fact that my heart has been
filled with (pure) knowledge of Thee and
when my tongue has repeatedly praised
Thee and my conscience has
acknowledged Thy love and despite my
sincere confessions (of my sins) and my
humble entreaties submissively made to
Thy divinity? Nay, Thou art far too kind
and generous to destroy one whom
thyself nourished and supported, or to
drive away from Thyself one whom Thou
has kept under Thy protection, or to
scare away one whom Thy self hast given
shelter, or to abandon in affliction one
Thou hast maintained and to whom Thou
5
hast been merciful I wish I had known o\’
my Master, my God and my Lord! Wilt
Thou inflict fire upon faces which have
submissively bowed in prostration to Thy
greatness, or upon the tongues which
have sincerely confirmed Thy unity and
have always expressed gratitude to Thee,
or upon hearts which have acknowledged
Thy divinity with conviction, or upon the
minds which accumulated so much
knowledge of Thee until they became
submissive to Thee, or upon the limbs
which strove, at the places appointed for
Thy worship, to adore Thee willingly and
seek Thy forgiveness submissively? Such
sort (of harshness) is not expected from
Thee as it is remote from Thy grace, o\’
generous one! O\’ Lord! Thou art aware of
my weakness to bear even a minor
affliction of this world and its
consequence and adversity affecting the
denizen of this earth, although such
afflictions are momentary, short-lived and
transient How then can I bear the
retributions and the punishments of the
hereafter which are enormous and of
intensive sufferings, of prolonged period
and perpetual duration, and which shall
never be alleviated for those who deserve
the same as those retributions will be the
result of Thy wrath; and Thy punishment
which neither the heavens nor the earth
can withstand and bear! My Lord! How
can I, a weak, insignificant, humble, poor
and destitute creature of Thine be able to
bear them? O\’ my God! My Lord! My
King! And Master! Which of the matters
shall I complain to Thee and for which of
them shall I bewail and weep? shall I
bewail for the pains and pangs of the
punishment and their intensity or for the
6
length of sufferings and their duration?
Therefore (my Lord!) If Thou wilt subject
me to the penalties (of hell) in company
of Thy enemies and cast me with those
who merited Thy punishments and tear
me apart from Thy friends and those who
will be near to Thee, then my God, my
Lord and my Master, though I may
patiently bear Thy punishments, how can
I calmly accept being kept away from
Thee? I reckon that though I may
patiently endure the scorching fire of Thy
hell, yet how can I resign myself to the
denial of Thy pity and clemency? How can
I remain in the fire while I have hopes of
Thy forgiveness? O\’ my Lord! By Thy
honour truly do I swear that, if Thou wilt
allow my power of speech to be retained
by me in the hell, I shall amongst its
inmates cry out bewailingly unto Thee
like the cry of those who have faith in Thy
kindness and compassion And I shall
bemoan for Thee (for being deprived of
nearness to Thee) the lamentation of
those who are bereaved, and I shall keep
on calling unto Thee: "Where art Thou o\’
Friend of the believers! O\’ (Thou who art)
the last hope and resort of those who
acknowledge Thee and have faith in Thy
clemency and kindness; o\’ Thou who art
the helper of those seeking help! O\’ Thou
who art dear to the hearts of those who
truly believe in Thee! And o\’ Thou who art
the Lord of the universe."
My Lord! Glory and praise be to Thee,
wouldst Thou (wish) to be seen
(disregarding) the voice of a muslim
bondman, incarcerated therein (the hell)
for his disobedience and imprisoned
within its pits for his evildoings and
misdeeds, crying out to Thee the
7
utterance of one who has faith in Thy
mercy and calling out to Thee in the
language of those who believe in Thy
unity and seeking to approach Thee by
means of Thy epithet "the Creator, the
Nourisher, the Accomplisher and the
Protector of the entire existence"?
My Lord! Then how could he remain in
torments when he hopefully relies upon
Thy past forbearance, compassion and
mercy? And how can the fire cause him
suffering when he hopes for Thy grace
and mercy and how can its roaring flames
char him when Thou hearest his voice
and sees his plight? And how can he
withstand its roaring flames when Thou
knowest his fraility? And how can he be
tossed about between its layers when
Thou knowest his sincerity? And how can
the guards of hell threaten him when he
calls out to Thee? "My Lord", and how
would Thou abandon him therein (the
hell) when he has faith in Thy grace to
set him free? Alas! That is not the
concept (held by us) of Thee nor has Thy
grace such a reputation nor does it
resemble that which Thou hast awarded
by Thy kindness and generosity to those
who believe in Thy unity I definitely
conclude that hadst Thou not ordained
punishment for those who disbelieved in
Thee, and hadst Thou not decreed Thy
enemies to remain in hell, Thou wouldst
have made the hell cold and peaceful and
there would never have been an abode or
place for any one in it; but sanctified be
Thy Names, Thou hast sworn to fill the
hell with the disbelievers from amongst
the jinns and mankind together and to
place forever Thy enemies therein And
Thou, exalted be Thy praises, hadst made
8
manifest, out of Thy generosity and
kindness, that a believer is not like unto
him who is an evil-liver. My Lord! My
Master! I, therefore implore Thee by that
power which Thou determineth and by
the decree which Thou hast finalised and
ordained whereby Thou hath prevailed
upon whom Thou hast imposed it, to
bestow upon me this night and this very
hour the forgiveness for all the
transgressions that I have been guilty of,
for all the sins that I have committed, for
all the loathsome acts that I have kept
secret and for all the evils done by me,
secretly or openly, in concealment or
outwardly and for every evil action that
Thou hast ordered the two noble scribes
to confirm whom Thou hast appointed to
record all my actions and to be witnesses
over me along with the limbs of my body,
whilst Thou observeth over me besides
them and wast witness to those acts
concealed from them? Which Thou in Thy
mercy hast kept secret and through Thy
kindness unexposed and I pray to Thee to
make my share plentiful in all the good
that Thou dost bestow; in all the favours
that Thou dost grant; and in all the
virtues that Thou dost allow to be known
everywhere; and in all the sustenance
and livelihood that Thou dost expand and
in respect of all the sins that Thou dost
forgive and the wrongs that Thou dost
cover up O\’ Lord! O\’ Lord! O\’ Lord! O\’ my
God! My Lord! My King! O\’ Master of my
freedom! O\’ Thou who holdeth my destiny
and who art aware of my suffering and
poverty, O\’ Thou who knoweth my
destitution and starvation, o\’ my Lord! O\’
Lord, o\’ Lord! I beseech Thee by Thy
glory and Thy honour, by Thy supremely
9
high attributes and by Thy names to
cause me to utilise my time, day and
night, in Thy remembrance, by engaging
myself in serving Thee (Thy cause) and to
let my deeds be such as to be acceptable
to Thee, so much so that all my actions
and offerings (prayers) may be
transformed into one continuous and
sustained effort and my life may take the
form of constant and perpetual service to
Thee O\’ my Master! O\’ Thou upon Whom
I rely! O\’ Thou unto Whom I express my
distress! O\’ my Lord! My Lord! My Lord!
Strengthen my limbs for Thy service and
sustain the strength of my hands to
persevere in Thy service and bestow
upon me the eagerness to fear Thee and
constantly to serve Thee So that I may
lead myself towards Thee in the field with
the vanguards who are in the fore rank
and be swift towards Thee among those
who hasten towards Thee and urge
eagerly to be near Thee and draw myself
towards Thee like them who sincerely
draw themselves towards Thee and to
fear Thee like the fear of those who
believe firmly in Thee and thus I may join
the congregation of the faithful
congregated near Thee (for protection) O\’
Allah! Whosoever intendeth evil against
me, let ill befall on him and frustrate him
who plots against me and assign for me a
place in Thy presence with the best of
Thy bondsmen and nearer abode to Thee,
for verily that position cannot be attained
except through Thy grace and treat me
benevolently, and through Thy greatness
extend Thy munificence towards me and
through Thy mercy protect me and cause
my tongue to accentuate Thy
remembrance and my heart filled with
10
Thy love and be liberal to me by Thy
gracious response and cause my evils to
appear fewer and forgive me my errors.
For verily, Thou hast ordained for Thy
bondsmen Thy worship and bidden them
to supplicate unto Thee and hast assured
them (of Thy) response So, my Lord! I
look earnestly towards Thee and towards
Thee, my Lord! I have stretched forth my
hands therefore, by Thy honour, respond
to my supplication and let me attain my
wishes and, by Thy bounty, frustrate not
my hopes and protect me from the evils
of my enemies, from among the jinns and
mankind o\’ Thou! Who readily pleased,
forgive one who owns nothing but
supplication for Thou doest what Thou
willest o\’ Thou! Whose Name is the
remedy (for all ills) and Whose
remembrance is a sure cure for all
ailments and obedience to Whom makes
one self sufficient; have mercy on one
whose only asset is hope and whose only
armour is lamentation O\’ Thou! Who
perfecteth all bounties and Who wardeth
off all misfortunes! O\’ Light! Who
illuminateth those who are in
bewilderment! O\’ Omniscient! Who
knoweth without (acquisition of) learning!
Bless Mohammed and the Descendants of
Mohammed and do unto me in
accordance with that which befitteth
Thee, and deal with me not in accordance
to my worth May the blessings of Allah be
bestowed upon His Apostle and the
Rightful Imams from his Descendants and
His peace be upon them plentifully
    </string>

    <string name="tduaeganjularsh">
         In the name of Allah, the Beneficent, the
Merciful \n
O Allah! Bless Muhammad and his
progeny. \n
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Master ,The Most Sanctified.
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Noble ,The Most Powerful.
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Compassionate ,The Merciful.
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Forgiving ,The Merciful.
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Noble ,The Wise
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Powerful,The Truthful(to His Word)
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Gentle ,The All Knowing
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Self Sufficient, The One Who is Worshipped
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Forgiving, The Loving
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Ultimate Truster ,The Supporter
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Watcher, The Keeper
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Prepetual ,The Upright
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The One Who Gives Live, The One Who Causes to Die
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Living,The Self- Subsistent
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Creator ,The Maker
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Most High ,The Incomparably Great
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The One ,The Single
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Granter Of Security ,The Protector
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Reckoner ,The Witness
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Forbearing,The Generous
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The First,The Eternal
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The First ,The Last
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Apparent,The Hidden
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Greatest,The Most High
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The One Who Fulfills the Needs
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Compassionate ,The Merciful
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Lord of The Great Throne
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to My Lord,The Most High
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Ultimate proof,The King
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Hearing,The All Seeing
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The One,The Subduer
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The AllaKnowing,The Wise
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Coverer(of the sins) ,The Oft Forgiving
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Merciful,The Devout
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Greatest,The Great
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Aware ,All Knowing
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Pur,The Sufficient
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Great,The Remaining
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Eternally Besought,The One
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Lord of The Earth and The Heaven
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Creator of The Created
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The One Who has Created Night and The Day
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Creator,The Continuous Granter of Sustenance
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Opener ,The All Knowing
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Noble ,The All Sufficient
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Oft-Forgiver,The Oft-Appreciative
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Great ,The Forbearing
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Possessor of the Dominion and The Heavens
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The possessor of the  Respect and The Greatness
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The possessor of the Grandeur and Power
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Possessor of The Pride and The Dignity
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Cover-er(of sins) ,The Great
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Know-er of the Unseen
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Praised, The Exalted
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Al-Wise ,The Eternal
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Powerful,The Cover-er (of sins)
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Hearing All Knowing
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Sufficient,The Great
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Knowing ,The Peace
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The King,The Helper
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Sufficient,The Merciful
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Sufficient,The Merciful
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to
        The One Whose Goodness is close at Hand
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Guardian of All Goodness
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Oft-Patient,The Coverer (of sins)
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Creator ,The Divine Light
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Sufficient,The Miracle
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Erudite ,The Oft-Thanked
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Sufficient, The Eternal
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Possessor of Manifest Grandeur
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Uncontaminated,And The One Who(spiritually) Purifies Others
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Truthful One to His words
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Manifest Truth
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Possessor of Even-Powered Strength
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Powerful,The Noble
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The All Knowing of The Unseen
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Living Who Shall Never Die
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Coverer of sins
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The One Whose help is sought,The Forgiving
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Lord of the Entire Universe
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Merciful,The Coverer of the Sins
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Compasiionate,The Forgiver
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Noble,The Granter of Desires
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Able ,The Powerful
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The possessor of Forgiveness and Forbearance
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Ruler of The Kingdom
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Evolver ,The Fashioner
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be The powerful and overcome
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Compeller The Majestic
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The One free from everything uttered by Polytheistic,
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Noble,The Haughty
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be  to The Lord of the Angels and the Spirit
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to Owner for Giveness and Blessings
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Ruler of The Kingdom
    There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Glory be to The Merciful, The Giverer of Blessings
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Adam chosen of Allah
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Nuh the saved of Allah
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Ibrahim Friend of Allah
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Ismail sacrified of AllahThere is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Musa the one who spoke to Allah
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Dawud the successor of Allah(on His Earth)
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Isa the spirit of Allah
        There is no creature or entity worthy of worship except for Allah,Muhammad is The Messenger of Allah
        The mercy of Allah be upon the best of His creations,and the light of His Divine Throne,the best of Prophets,and those who were sent(to guide humanity),Our beloved,leader,support,intercessor and master,Muhammad and upon his family and his selected distinguished companions.May Your Mercy be Upon them all.O\’The Most Merciful of the Merciful ones.Accept our supplication with your mercy .you are my facilitator in this world and in hereafter.make me among your obedient and pious servants.
</string>







    <string name="tduaemeraj">
         In the name of Allah, the Beneficent, the
Merciful \n
O Allah! Bless Muhammad and his
progeny. \n
        O Allah I beseech You.
O He with whom remain firmly
attached all the worshippers,
O He before whom all the
praiseworthy bow down and pay tribute,
O He unto whom all the tired and the
oppressed cry for help,
O He who is besought for fulfillment
of needs by all those who are deprived,
O He who does not send away any
supplicant disappionted,
O He whose door is never shut up for the beseechers,
O He who is indescribeable and indefinable,
O He in whose bestowals there is no let-up,
and they are not little nor scanty,
O He who is not out of the reach of prayers;
and is the best destination,
O He whose servants tie their hopes with (His) rope,
O He like unto whom,
there is no one, and no one is comparable to Him,
O He who was not begotten, nor begets,
O He whose bounties and favours are innumerable,
O He whose overflowing reservoir of
good is kept open for mankind,
O He to whom standing up
(wakefulness) and sitting down
(rest) cannot be attributed,
O He who urges his gifts and presents
to reach the created beings,
O He who is not circumstanced by
movement or stillness (inaction),
O Allah, O beneficent, O merciful, O loving friend,
O He who took pity on the aging Yaqub,
O He who overlooked the mistake of Dawud,
O He who does not break His word and
forgives those whom forgiveness has been assured,
O He who gives livelihood and covers
the misdeeds of the creatures to
their full satisfaction,
O He who gives asylum to all the
persecuted victims of revenge,
O He to come nearer to whom all
creatures lay with the face
downward on the ground in abject submission,
O He from whose beneficence not a
single (living) soul is kept away,
O He who does not rule unjustly, nor
shows mercy to the headstrong tryants,
have mercy on the petty transgressors
who did not carry out their obligations.
Verily You do whatever You will,
O Truthful. O Loving,
send blessings on Muhammad, the
best Mesenger, who called attention
(of all) to the best worshippable,
and on his descendants, pious, pure,
generous and liberal, and do well for
me as it is worthy of You,
O the most merciful, O the most generous
    </string>



    <string name="tduaenoor">
         In the name of Allah, the Beneficent, the
Merciful \n
O Allah! Bless Muhammad and his
progeny. \n
O Allah! O the One Who makes the light Radiant! (Verily) You radiated Yourself through Your Light (entering the souls of the Faithful). O absolute Light! All lights are the result of the abundance of Your light. O Allah! O the One Who controls all! Verily You are honoured because of Your (Divine) Honour. O the One Who grants honour to the creation! All honours are due to Your Honour. O Allah! O the owner of limitless greatness! You are Great through Your own greatness (There is no doubt in it). O greater than all greats! All greatnesses are owing to Your greatness. O Allah! O the One Who alone is worthy of worship! O the Bestower! Only You have (truly) bestowed favours on the creation, and O Favourer Lord! All these favours are because of Your favour. O Allah! O the owner of real greatness and grandeur! Only You are the possessor of true greatness and all the greatnesses of the people of the world are, O the Great!, due to Your greatness. O Allah! O the possessor of limitless knowledge! The sciences of all the scholars are but tiny reflections of Your attribute of omniscience as only Your knowledge is absolute knowledge. O the One Who is aware (of the wholes and parts). O Allah! O Holy Lord! (Doubtlessly) You are Holy through Your own holiness and all the holinesses are the result of Your holiness. O Allah! O the One Who is beautiful through Your own beauty! You alone is beautiful by Your own virtue of beauty. All the things beautiful are beautiful only as a consequence of the reflection of Your beauty. O Allah! O the provider of protection and salvation! You are the possessor of self-protection and all these safeties are as a result of Your virtue of safety. O Allah! O the One Who is patient and Who makes delay in punishing the sinners! You alone are truly patient and all these instances of patience are the reflections of Your patience. O Allah! O the owner of the kingdom of the entire creation! Only in Your hands is the real reins of kingdom and all the kingdoms have been granted only by You. O Allah! O the sustainer of the entire universe! Only You are the Sustainer because of Your own virtue of Lordship. All nourishments are due to Your nourishment. O Allah! O the One Who favours limitlessly! You alone deserve the showering of favours. All the favours shown by the creation are only the consequence of Your favours. O Allah! O the Wise! All of your commandments are full of wisdom. Every one of Your actions are sound through wisdom. All wisdoms are owing to Your wisdom. O Absolute Intelligence! O Allah! O the One Who is worthy of all praise! You are praiseworthy due to Your personal virtues and all the laudations are due to Your praiseworthiness. O the Entire Praise! O Allah! O the One Who has no partner! You alone, due to Your virtue of being one, the only ruler of the entire creation. No doubt, every uniqueness is nothing compared to Your attribute of being Only One God. O Allah! O the Unique. One Who has no likeliness. Verily, You remained the only One due to Your unity and the uniquenesses of all the creation are the samples of Your uniqueness. O the One and the Unique! O the Forbearer! Only You are the forebearer because of your virtue of forbearance and all the good behaviors are because of Your virtue of forbearance. O the One Who is more patient than all patients! O Allah! O the possessor of unlimited power! You are Absolute Power only because of Your attribute of Omnipotence. All powers and freedoms are the fruits of Your strength. O Absolute Power! O Allah! O the One Who is Everlasting! You are ancient and eternal because of your attribute of being eternal. All lastings are because of your eternity. O Allah! O the Testifier (of the prophet hood of Muhammed)! Verily You are unique in Your attribute of testifying and the witness, being Your witness, is above all witnesses. O the Testifier! O Allah! O the One Who is near! O the One Who is nearer than the jugular vein! You are near due to the virtue of being near and every nearness is because of your nearness. O Allah! O the One Who is ever helping in every circumstance! You help by the virtue of being the Helper. All helps are due to Your help. O the Best Helper! O Allah! O the One Who is hidden behind the veil of Oneness! And O the One Who hides the errors of sinners in the veil of Your Mercy! You are the Hider by virtue of being the hider and all hidings (like the hiding of the Qaem-e-Aal-e-Muhammad Imam Mehdi a.t.f.s.) are the examples of your veiling. O the Veiler! O Allah! O the One Who frowns upon the unbelievers and the hypocrites! You are the suppressor by virtue of Your being the crusher. All pressures and suppressions are becoming only to You. O Allah! O the One Who gives sustenance to the entire creation! You are the Sustainer by virtue of Your being the nourisher and all the nourishings are the samples of Your nourishment. O the giver of provision! O the Creator! You, by virtue of being the creator came into being to be the real creator of all, and all the created things are (in the matter of procreation) subservient to Your command. O Creator! O Allah! O the One Who resolves all problems to grant success by easing all hardships! You alone are the real Opener of the doors to success. There is no doubt that all the successes achieved by the creation are the result of the intelligence granted by You. O the Opener! O Allah! O the One Who is High by virtue of Your Height. 0 Allah! O the One Who is higher than all highs! O Allah! O the Unique Protector! You alone are protected through Your own Protection and all protections are under Your protection. O Protector! O Allah! O the owner of self-perfection! Verily You are perfect by Yourself and the perfections and excellences of the creations are through Your excellence and perfection. O the Perfect and the excellent! O Allah! O the keeper and maintainer of the relation of love and affection! You Yourself have taught love and all these intimacies are the result of Your teaching. They are also for meeting You. O the Best gatherer! O the One Who does at will! Whatever You have done has been done by Your absolute will, and real authority and will is only Your authority and will and all authorities are the gifts of Your authority. O the One Who does whatever You want! O Allah! O the One Who has created this universe with measure and the real measure is only Your measure. All measures and plannings are grace of Your planning. O the Measurer! O Allah! O the Forgiver of all big and small sins! It is only You Who forgives due to Your attribute of pardoning. As for the pardonings and forgiveness\’s of the creation, they are mere reflections of Your forgiveness. O Pardoner! O Allah! O the One Who joins the broken hearts and the dilapidated bones! In fact, such power is possessed only by You, and the joining and gatgering by the creations is but due to Your attribute of imposing Your Will. O Omnipotent! O Allah! O the One Who hears the voice of the weak and the ill (steps of an ant)! You hear by virtue of Your All-Hearingness. The hearing and answering of the creation is merely due to Your hearing and responding. O Allah! O the biggest Merciful and Beneficent! Only You are the owner of true greatness and all these greatnesses are existing and continuing only because of Your greatness. O the Greatest of all greats! O Allah! O the One Who causes the rivers of kindness flow! (really generosity is only Your generosity) and all these generosities of the people are only the leftovers of only Your table of generosity. O Allah! O the One Who pities every one of Your sinful slaves! Verily You are kind and merciful only on the basis of Your attribute of pity and sympathy. All kindnesses are because of Your kindness and pitifulness. O Centre of Mercy! O Allah! O the Owner of great Highness! (Reality is that) it is only Your height where even the bird of imagination cannot reach and the heights of these low ranking slaves are merely Your gifts. O the Hearer of the cry of the inflicted! O Lord! O Merciful! O Beneficent! O Ever living! O the One Who is lenient in punishing! O Dominant over all O the One Who makes hearts radiant! O the One besides Whom there is no deity! I have also relied only on You, that is, on the Lord of the Great Throne. All praise is for the limitlessly forgiving God. We hallow only HIS Name Who is extremely Great. We hallow only Him Who shows patience and mercy in giving punishment. We hallow Him Who sees each and every deed done by us. We hallow Him Who has no partner and Who will save us from hell. We hallow Him Who protects the whole world. We hallow Him Who is Kind. We hallow Him Who will forgive us. We hallow Him Who is older than oldness (ancientness). We hallow Him Who is the owner of honour and power. We hallow Him Whose existence is manifest to all We hallow Him Who cures the ill (gives health). We hallow Him Who is sufficient for us all. We hallow Him Who provides safety to us. We hallow Him Who makes us Faithful. We hallow Him Who shelters us. We hallow Him Who the best designer of faces. We hallow Him Who helps us. We hallow Him Who is absolutely unique. We hallow Him Who is like only Him (no one is like Him). We hallow Him Who showers mercy. We hallow Him Who holds us back from evils. We hallow Him Who leads us toward good. We hallow Him Who causes harm. We hallow Him Who grants light. We hallow Him Who is absolute Guidance. We hallow Him Who is the Master of destiny. We hallow Him Who is the Greatest. We hallow Him Who is High. We hallow Him Who watches the whole world. We hallow Him Who is Holy. His is the holy existence. All praise is for Allah. None besides Him is worthy of worship. So only Allah is the greatest of all. What is reality is that no one except the only One Allah has any power. Only He is High and Great. We hallow Him Who carries out His acts with His perfect power and Who imposes His command, with His particular strength. We hallow him and praise Him Who is the master and owner of the high Throne. Awe, Power, Greatness and Pomp becomes only Him. We hallow only Him Who is really the absolute Ruler Sovereign. We hallow only Him Who is the Lord of every thing existing. We hallow only Him Who is Ever-living and the Wise. We hallow the only one Lord and rely on Him Who has no death at all. Only He deserves all praise and hallowing and He is Holy. He is the nourisher of all angels and the Trustworthy Gabriel (Jibraeel). There will never be any deity except Him. He is totally unique and only one. HE has no partner. Entire kingdom is for Him alone. All praise is proven for Him. He dominates everything. O Allah! O Beneficent! O Merciful! O Everliving! O Everlasting! O the possessor of grace and mercy! O Light of the heavens and the earth Who makes them bright! O the Being Who alone is the Merciful Lord! We have trusted only You. You alone are the nourisher of the Great Throne. O Allah! We seek intercession of Your Honour and Greatness. Forgive us just in the name of these holy names of Yours. Keep all troubles and all calamities and anxieties and sorrows and all hardships away from us. O My Nourisher! Protect my family members (for the sake of Muhammad and his progeny) from all evils because, in all of my affairs I have relied only on You. O Allah! Shower safety and bounty on Your best creation, that is, Muhammed and his progeny, and on their pious offsprings, for the sake of Your perfect Mercy, O Allah! O Merciful! O Beneficent!
    </string>




    <string name="tduaeyasthasheer">
         In the name of Allah, the Beneficent, the
Merciful \n
O Allah! Bless Muhammad and his
progeny. \n
All praise is due to Allah. There is no god but He, the Living, the Just, the Manifest.
He is the Administrator without any minister and without consultation with any of his slaves. He is the First, who cannot be described.
He is Eternal and will live forever, (even) after the annihilation of all creatures.
He is the greatest Cherisher and Sustainer and the Light of the earths and heavens and their Creator and Maker out of nothing.
He created both of them and separated them - a proper separation. The heavens became stable in obedience to His commandment and the earths became fixed on the surface of the water with their pegs.
Then our Lord the All-Merciful subdued the high heavens and ruled from the Throne.
Everything that is in heaven and in the earth and in between them and what is below the earth belongs to Him. So, I bear witness that verily You are Allah.


There is none to elevate what You hath lowered and no one to exalt him whom You leaves in disgrace and no one to bring into disgrace him whom You exalts and no one to prevent him upon whom You bestoweth Thy favour and no one to bestow anything, which You hath withheld. You are Allah, there is no god but Thee. Who existed when there was neither the stable sky nor the broad earth nor the brilliant sun nor the dark night, nor the bright day, nor the vast and stormy sea, nor any sublime and stable mountain, nor any revolving planet, nor the luminous moon, nor any blowing wind, nor any raining cloud, nor flashing lightning, nor any praising thunder, nor any breathing soul, nor any flying bird, nor any blazing fire, nor any flowing water.
You existed before the existence of everything and You created everything and controlled everything and originated everything.
You enriched some and reduced others to poverty, caused some to die and brought others to life, and made some people glad and other weep. Verily You rules from the Throne.
You are of vast blessing, O Allah You are Great and Supreme. You are Allah and there is no god other than Thee.
You are the Creator and Supporter.

Thy Decree is everpowering and Thy Knowledge is operative. Thy strategy is wonderful; Thy promise is true; Thy word is right; Thy command is just; Thy utterance is right guidance; Thy Revelation is light; Thy mercy is vast and abundant; Thy forgiveness is superb; Thy grace is excessive; Thy gift is most respectable Thy cord is strong; Thy might is ever ready Thy protégé is powerful; Thy wrath is severe; and Thy stratagem is entrapping O Lord! With Thee are lodged all complaints.
You are present in all gatherings, and are the witness of all secrets, and the ultimate goal of all supplications, the expeller of all sorrows, the affluence of every needy person, the stronghold for every refugee, security for everyone who is terror-stricken, a shield for the weak a treasure for the indigent, the destroyer of griefs, the helper of the virtuous.

Such is Allah, our Lord.
There is no god but He.
You satisfieth such of Thy slaves as trust unto Thee. You are the protector of him who is firmly attached to Thee and humiliates himself before Thee, a shield for him who seeks refuge with Thee, the help of him who looks up to Thee for help, the forgiver of sins for him who begs Thy pardon,
the complier of the tyrant, the most grand of the grand, the most great of the great, the master of masters, the Lord of lords, the Succour of the grieved, the Helper of those crying for help, the Responder to the call of the distressed, the best of all listeners, the best of all observers, the best of all judges, the quickest of all reckoners, the most merciful of all the merciful the best of all forgivers, the satisfier of the needs of the faithful, and the hearer of the appeals of the virtuous. You are Allah, there is no god but Thee.

You are the Cherisher and Sustainer of all the worlds You are the Creator and I am a creature.
You are the Master and I am a servant, You are the Lord and I am a slave. You are the Provider while I am provided with sustenance, You are the Giver while I am a beggar, You are the Generous while I am a miser. You are the Mighty while I am weak, You are the Noble while I am humble. You are the independent while I am needy. You are the Master while I am slave.

You are the Forgive of sins while I am sinful. You are the Omniscient while I am ignorant. You are the forbearing while I am hasty. You are the All-Merciful and I have been treated with mercy. You are the Provider of safety but I am involved in suffering.
You are the Responder and I am the distressed.
And I bear witness that verily You are Allah, there is no god but thee thou bestoweth favours upon Thy slaves even without their asking. And I bear witness that verily You are Allah, the One, the Peerless, the Unique, the independent, the Single, and verily to Thee we must return.

May the blessings of Allah be upon Muhammad and his family the holy and pure.
O Lord, forgive my sins and keep my faults concealed and extend to me Thy special mercy and bounteous sustenance O the All-merciful! All praise is due to Allah the Cherisher and sustainer of all the worlds And for us Allah is the Sufficiency and the excellent Protector.
There is neither might nor power but with Allah the Great, the Exalted.




    </string>





    <string name="tduaetawassul">
         In the name of Allah, the Beneficent, the
Merciful \n
O Allah! Bless Muhammad and his
progeny. \n
O Allah, I beseech Thee, and We turn towards Allah with your help, through Thy Prophet, the Prophet of Mercy, Muhammad, may Allah Bless him and his Progeny, and grant them peace.
 O Abul-Qasim, O Messenger of Allah O guide of mercy, O intercessor of the community, O our chief, O our master,  We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah]; O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.
O Abul Hasan, O Commander of the Faithful, O \’Ali, son of Abu Talib, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind,

O our chief, O our master,  We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.
O Fatima Zahra, O daughter of Muhammad, O Joy to the eye of the Prophet, O our chief, O our master,  We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in Judgment over us.
O Abu Muhammad, O Hasan, son of \’Ali, O elected one

 O descendant of the Messenger of Allah, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind, O our chief, O our master, We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.
O Abu Abdallah, O Husain, son of \’Ali, O Martyr

O descendant of the Messenger of Allah, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind, O our chief, O our master,  We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.
O Abu Muhammad, O \’Ali, son of al-Husain, O Zayn al-Abidin, O Prostrator before Allah

O descendant of the Messenger of Allah, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind, O our chief, O our master, We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgement over us.
O Abu Ja\’far, O Muhammad, son of \’Ali, O knowledgeable one,

O descendant of the Messenger of Allah, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind, O our chief, O our master,We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.
O Abu \’Abdallah, O Ja\’far, son of Muhammad, O truthful one

O descendant of the Messenger of Allah, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind, O our chief, O our master, We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.
O Abu Ibrahim, O Musa, son of Ja\’far, O tranquil one,

 O descendant of the Messenger of Allah, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind, O our chief, O our master, We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.
 O Abul Hasan, O \’Ali, son of Musa, O devoted one,

 O descendant of the Messenger of Allah, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind, O our chief, O our master,We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.

O Abu Ja\’far, O Muhammad, son of \’Ali, O generous, Taqi\’ and pious one,

 O descendant of the Messenger of Allah, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind, O our chief, O our master, We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.
O Abul Hasan, O Ali, son of Muhammad, O guide (Hadi) and pure one (Naqi),

 O descendant of the Messenger of Allah, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind, O our chief, O our master, We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.
O Abu Muhammad, O Hasan, son of \’Ali, O Wise one and warrior,

 O descendant of the Messenger of Allah, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind, O our chief, O our master,We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.

O inheritor of al-Hasan, O successor, O upright one, O Proof, O awaited upriser, O Mahdi,

 O descendant of the Messenger of Allah, O decisive argument of Allah over mankind,We turn towards Allah with your help, seek thy intercession and advocacy before Allah, We call upon you before [mentioning] our requests [to Allah], O intimate of Allah, Stand by us when Allah sits in judgment over us.

 O our chief , O our master, O my chiefs,

O my Masters, I turn to Allah through you, O my Imams, my supporters on the days of my destitution.

I seek your advocacy before Allah, I request you to speak in my favour before Allah, obtain pardon for me from Allah, and deliver me from my sins,

through my love of you and nearness to you, obtain deliverance (for me) from Allah

O my chiefs, O close friends of Allah, may Allah bless all of them, and curse the enemies of Allah who have oppressed them and will oppress them so be it, O Lord of the worlds.
    </string>






    <string name="tduaeahad">
         In the name of Allah, the Beneficent, the
Merciful \n
O Allah! Bless Muhammad and his
progeny. \n
        O Allah! Lord of the Great Light, Lord of the Elevated Throne, Lord of the tumultuous seas, and the revealer of the Tawrah, Injeel, and Zaboor, Lord of the shadows and the warmth\’s, And the revealer of the Great Quran. Lord of the proximate angels and prophets and messengers. O Allah I beseech thee, for the sake of Your Nobel Visage. And for the sake of Your Enlightening Visage, and Your ever existing kingdom. O Ever Living! O Controller! I beseech Thee in Your Name which lit the heavens and the earths; and in Your Name, by which the ancient and the latter ones become upright. O Ever living who has before every living being. O Ever Living Who shall (exist) after every living being. O Ever Living Who existed when there was no life. O Giver of life to dead. O One Who causes death to the living one. O Ever Living. There is no god except Thou.

O Allah send our master the leader, the guide, the guided, the upriser with Your command. Blessings of Allah be on him and his pure forefathers from all the believing men and believing women. In the east\’s of the earth and it\’s west\’s, in its plains and its mountains, its lands and its seas, from me and my parents. Blessings, which are the weight of Allah\’s throne and ink of His words, and whatever His knowledge enumerates and His book encompasses.

O Allah renew for him my covenant, pledge and allegiance on my neck in the morning of this day of mine and whatever days (of my life) I live. I shall never turn away from it nor let it ever vanish. O Allah appoint me among his helpers, aides, and his protectors. Those who hasten to fulfill his commands and obey his orders. Those who are his supporters and compete with each other to (fulfill) his intention and seek martyrdom in his presence.

O Allah! If death occurs between me and him (before the reappearance) (death) which you have made obligatory and decreed for your servants, then raise me from my grave, wrapped in my shroud, my sword unsheathed, my spear bared, answering the call of the caller in cities as well as deserts.

O Allah! Show me the rightly guided face of (Imam a.s.), the praiseworthy moon (referring to the face of Imam a.s.) and enlighten my vision by looking at him. And hasten his reappearance, make his arrival smooth, vasten his path, make me tread on his way and implement his authority and strengthen his back. O Allah inhabit Your cities through him and give life to Your servants due to him for surely You have said and Your word is truth, "Corruption will become rampant in land and on sea because of the evil which men\’s hand have earned" Then O Allah manifest for us Your slave and the son of Your Prophet\’s daughter, whose name is the same as that of Your messenger, so that nothing from falsehood is victorious except that he tears them (falsehood) to pieces, establishes the truth and the truth confirms him. And O Allah! Appoint him as a refuge for Your oppressed servants and a helper for the one who does not find any helper for himself except You and the renewer of all the laws of Your book which have been tampered with and the rebuilder of the science of Your religion and the traditions of Your Prophet (peace of Allah be on him and his progeny) and O Allah! make him among those whom you have protected from the evils of the adversaries.

O Allah! and provide joy to Your Prophet Mohammed (peace be on him and his progeny) by his vision and (the vision of) the one who follows him on his call and have mercy on our poverty after his arrival O Allah remove his sorrow (of occultation) from this nation with his presence and hasten for us his reappearance. They (the disbelievers) consider it to be distant while we consider it to be near. For the sake of Your mercy, O the most Merciful of all Mercifuls.

Then one should gently strike his right thigh with his palm and say.

Hasten! Hasten! O my Master, O Master of the era

    </string>




    <string name="tduaesamaat">

 In the name of Allah, the Beneficent, the
Merciful \n
O Allah! Bless Muhammad and his
progeny. \n
Allah! I beseech Thee through Thy Name, the most great, the most majestic, the most magnificent and the most noble.

If Thou art requested therewith to open the closed doors of the sky these will open with Thy mercy. If Thou art requested thereby to remove the narrowness of the doors of the heaven, they will be opened wide. If Thou art requested thereby to make easy the difficulty, it will be easy.

If Thou art requested thereby to restore the dead to life, they will wise from their graves. If Thou art requested thereby to remove misery and adversity, they will be removed. I beseech Thee through the Majesty of Thy person, the Most Generous and the Most Honoured One, before Whom everybody bows down in submission and all necks bend down in reverence and through fear of Whom all voices become humbled and all hearts tremble; and I beseech Thee through Thy Might, which prevents the sky from falling on the earth except with Thy permission, and which controls all the heavens and the earth so closely that they cannot move away from their positions; and I beseech Thee through they Will, which the whole world obeys, and through Thy Word.

By which Thou hath created the heaven and the earth, and through Thy Wisdom, with which Thou hath created wonderful, and with which Thou created Darkness and made it Night, and made night the time of quiet and rest; and with which Thou created Light and made it Day, and made day the time of movement and observation; and with which Thou hath created the Sun, and made the sun of light.

And with which Thou hath created the Moon, and made the moon of light; and with which Thou hath created heavenly bodies, and made them fixed stars and planets, and lamps for guidance at night, and as a means of decoration, and missiles for driving away the devils, and hath created for them east and west, and hath created for them the places of ascendancy and orbits, and created for them a firmament and sphere, and fixed for them stages in the heave - and how beautiful the stages - and shaped the stars - and how beautiful the shapes - and made them stable through Thy Name; and Thy Wisdom Thou designed a system for them - and what a good system, and controlled the heavenly bodies through the king of the night and the king of day, and through hours, making them a means for the reckoning of years and counting, making appearance of heavenly bodies regular and universal.

And I beseech Thee, O Allah, through Thy Glory, with which Thou addressed Thy slave and Thy Messenger, Moses son of \’Imran peace be on him, while he was in the company of angels - which address even the favourite cherubin could not ever hear, above the clouds of light, above the box of evidence, with in the pillar of fire on Mount Sinai, and on Mount Hurith in the Holy Vale in the sacred tract of land to the right of Taurus Mountain-through a tree; and again addressed him on the soil of Egypt, after showing nine clear signs and on the day Thou split the sea for the Children of Israel, and caused springs to flow from a stone, thereby displaying wonders of Thy might in a deep sea; and on the day when Thou solidified the water of the sea in the midst of the storm, and caused the Children of Israel to pass by it, and fulfilled Thy excellent promises made to them because of their calmly endurance, and made them the master of the East and the West in the earth, wherein there are blessings for all the worlds; and Thou drowned Pharaoh and his armies and boats in the water.

And (I beseech Thee) through Thy name, which is the most great, the most majestic, and the most holy; and through Thy glory, with which Thou revealed light to Moses, Thy addressee, peace be on him, on Mount Sinal; and earlier radiated the light for Abraham, Thy sincere friend peace be on him, in the mosque of al-Khayf; and for Isaac, Thy chosen Prophet, peace be on him, in Bi-ri shiay\’, and for Thy Prophet Jacob, peace be on him, in Bayt iil and through Thy Glory, with which Thou fulfilled Thy promise to Abraham, peace be on him; and through Thy Oath in favour of Isaac; and through Thy witnessing favouring Jacob; and through the fulfillments of Thy promise to the faithful: and through Thy Names with which Thou accepted the prayers of supplications; and through Thy Glory, which appeared to Moses, son of Imran, in Qubbat al-Rumman; and through Thy Signs, which appeared on the soil of Egypt with great might and victory, with powerful signs and with the display of full command and great power; and with the affair of the perfect word; and with Thy words with which Thou doth a favor for the people of the skies and the earth and the people of here and the hereafter; and through Thy Mercy with which Thou bestowth upon all Thy creatures: and through thy Power with which Thou dominateth the worlds; and (I beseech Thee) through Thy Light, through fear of which Mount Sinai collapsed, through Thy Knowledge, and Thy Greatness and Majesty, and Thy Unique Magnificence and Thy honour, and (through) Thy might, which the earth could not bear, and, for which the heavens and earth bent down, and the great depths restrained themselves, and the seas and rivers became stable, and to which the mountains made submission, and due to which the earth became firm on its shoulders, and to which all creatures submitted, and due to which the winds breathed, and the flaming fires were extinguished in their places.

And I beseech Thee through Thy might, through which Thou hath been known to be All-powerful for ever and ever, and for which Thou hath been praised in the heavens and the earth; and I beseech Thee through Thy word, the Word of Truth, which became a blessing for our father Adam and his generation; and I beseech Thee through Thy word, by which Thou overcame everything; and I beseech thee through the light of Thy Face, which when it flased on Mount Sinai crushed it to pieces, whereby Moses fainted and fell down, and through Thy Glory, which appeared on Mount Sinai, and through which Thou addressed Thy slave and Thy Mesenger; Moses, son of \’Imran, and through Thy appearance in Sa\’ir and on Mount Faran near Rabawat, which are clean and holy places, when troops of heavenly angels were in rows, and with the sumissiveness of the angels praising Thee, and with Thy blessings with which Thou honoured Abraham, Thy sincere friend, peace be upon him, among the followers of Muhammad, Thy blessings be upon him and his Progeny and Thou honoured Isaac, Thy chosen prophet,

among the followers of Jesus, peace be on them both, and honoured Jacob, Thy favoured slave, by including him among the followers of Moses, peace be on them both, and honoured Thy intimate friend Muhammad, may the blessings of Allah be upon him and his Progeny, and peace be upon his offspring and seed, and his people. O Allah! Just as we believe in the turth and justice of these manifestations of Thy glory, without having been present at the time, and without having been eyewitnesses. So we beseech Thee to send Thy blessings upon Muhammad and the Progeny of Muhammad, and honour Muhammad and the Progeny of Muhamamd, and honour Muhammad and the Progeny of Muhammad and have mercy on Muhammad and the Progeny of Muhammad, with the blessings, honour, and mercy Thou sent and bestowed on and meted out to Abraham and the posterity of Abraham. Surely Thou art Praiseworthy, Glorious, the Doer of what Thou willeth. Thou art Powerful over all things.

Now express your desire and beseech Allah to fulfill it. Then recite the following.
O Allah! For the sake of this prayer, and for the sake of these Names which no one can interpret, the inner meaning of which no one other than Thyself knows. Send Thy blessing upon Muhammad and the Progeny of Muhammad; and give me the good of here and the hereafter; and do to me what suits Thee and do not do to me what I deserve and exact vengeance from…(enemy of progeny of Holy Prophet (s.a.w.a.), and forgive my sins past and future, and forgive my parents and all faithful men and women, and increase Thy lawful sustenance for me, and save me from the help of wicked men, wicked neighbours, wicked rulers, wicked companions, and evil days and hours, and exact vengeance for me on everyone who hatches secret plots against me, and on everyone who oppresses me and seeks to do injustice to me or my wife or my children or my brothers or my neighbours or my relations among faithful men and women. Verily Thou art able to do whatever Thou wileth, and Thou knowest everything. Amen, O Lord of the worlds.

O Allah! For the sake of this prayer, grant wealth and affluence to indigent faithful men and women, and recovery and sound health to the sick faithful men and women, and bliss and clemency to the living faithful men and women, and remit the sins of, and have mercy on, the deceased faithful men and women, and arrange the return home of all faithful travellers with safety and gain. Through Thy mercy, O Most Merciful of all the merciful. May Allah\’s blessings and peace in abundant measure be upon our master Muhammad, the last of the prophets, and his Progeny, the purified






    </string>

    <string name="tduaemashlool">

 In the name of Allah, the Beneficent, the
Merciful \n
O Allah! Bless Muhammad and his
progeny. \n
O Allah, I beseech Thee with Thy Name; the Name of Allah, the Most Merciful, the Benign.
O Lord of Majesty and Generosity; O Living; O Self-Subsisting, O Ever-living, there is no God but Thou. O Thou that art "He" of whom no one knoweth what "He" is, nor how "He" is, nor where "He" is, except "He."
O Lord of the Great Kingdom and Supremacy. O Lord of Honour and Omnipotence:
O Sovereign Lord, O Holy One! O Peace; O Keeper of Faith; O Guardian O Revered One; O Compeller; O Superb. O Creator
O Maker of all things from nothing; O Artist; O Beneficent; O Administrator; O Severe (in wrath); O Inventor; O Restorer; O Originator; O Most Loving: O Praised; O Adored. O Thou that art distant yet near; O Answerer of pray
er; O Observer; O Reckoner. O Innovator; O Exalted; O Unassailable; O Hearer. O Knower; O Wise; O Bountiful; O Forbearing; O Eternal; O Lofty; O Great.
O most Compassionate; O Giver of all good; O most perfect Requiter of good and evil; O Thou whose help is sought for. O Majestic; O Glorious; O Trusted; O Guardian; O Alleviator of suffering; O Fulfiller of hopes;
O Guide; O Magnanimous. O Giver of guidance; O Commencer; O First; O Last; O Evident; O Hidden. O Established; O Everlasting; O Knowing; O Ruler; O Dispenser of justice; O Equitable; O Thou that disjoineth and uniteth; O Pure; O Purifier; O Powerful;
O Almighty; O Great; O Magnificent. O One; O Matchless; O Eternal; O Absolute; O Thou that bareth none and is born of none; nor is there equal to Thee anyone nor hath Thee any spouse; nor any bearer of Thy burden; nor any consultant to give Thee advice; not does Thou need any supporter; nor is there with Thou any other deity; There is no God but Thou, and Thou art far exalted with great excellence above all that which the unjust folk do say concerning Thee
O High and Lofty; O most Glorious; O Opener; O Diffuser of fragrance; O Tolerant; O Helper; O Victorious; O Overtaker; O Destroyer; O Avenger; O Resurrector; O Inheritor; O Seeker; O Conquerer; O Thou from Whom no fugitive can escape. O Acceptor of repentance; O Ever-forgiving; O Great Bestower; O Causer of all causes; O Opener of doors (of relief and salvation); O Thou that answerest howsoever Thou art invoked. O Purifier; O Giver of manifold rewards; O Excuser; O Pardoner; O Light of all lights; O Director of all affairs. O Ever Blissful; O All-Aware; O Protector; O Luminous; O Seer; O Supporter; O Great. O Lone; O Unique; O Everlasting; O Upholder; O Eternal and Absolute. O Sufficer; O Healer; O Fulfiller of promises; O Deliver. O Benefactor; O Beautifier; O Bestower of grace; O Grantor of favors; O Gracious;
 O Peerless. O Thou that being Exalted overwhelmest; O Thou that being Master of all hast absolute power; O Thou, who being hidden art well informed; O Thou that being disobeyed forgiveth; O Thou Whom no thought can fully comprehend; nor sight perceive nor from whom any impression is hidden, O Nourisher of Mankind; O Ordainer of every destiny. O Thou of Exalted position; O Thou Formidable in Thy foundations; O Changer of times; O Acceptor of sacrifice; O Thou full of favors and benefactions; O Lord of Honor and Supremacy; O All Merciful; O most Compassionate; O Thou that has each day a distinctive Glory while no aspect of Thy Glory is erased by the prominence of another aspect. O Thou that art present in every place.
O Hearer of all voices; O Answerer of prayers; O Giver of success in all requirements; O Fulfiller of all needs; O Bestower of blessings; O Thou that taketh pity on our tears. O Thou that raiseth from the pitfalls; O Thou that relieveth agonies; O thou that art the Cherisher of good deeds. O Thou that raiseth men in rank and degree; O Thou that accedeth to requests; O Thou that bringeth the dead to life; O Thou that gathereth together that which is scattered.
O Thou that art informed of all intentions; Thou that restoreth that which has been lost; O Thou that art not confused by a multiplicity of voices; O Thou that art not harassed by a multitude of petitions; and Whom no darkness can hide or cover; O Light of heaven and earth. O Perfector of blessings; O Averter of calamaties;
O Producer of zephyrs; O Gatherer of nations; O Healer of disease; O Creator of light and darkness; O Lord of generosity and munificence; O Thou (on) whose throne no one can set foot! O Thou more generous than the most generous; O Thou more munificent than the most munificent; O Thou most keen of hearing than the most keen of hearing; O Thou more keen of vision than the most perceiving; O Protecting neighbor of those that seek Thy neighborhood. O Refuge of the fearful; O Patron of the faithful;
O Helper of those that seek Thy help; O ultimate Goal of those that aspire. O Companion of all strangers; O Friend of all the lonely ones; O Refuge of all outcasts; O Retreat of all persecuted ones; O Guardian of all those who stray. O Thou that takest pity on the aged and decrepit; O Thou that nourisheth the little baby; O Thou that joineth together broken ones;
O Liberator of all prisoners; O Enricher of the miserable poor; O Protector of the frightened refugees; O Thou for Whom alone are both destiny and disposal; O Thou for Whom all difficult things are simple and easy; O Thou that doth not need any explanation. O Thou Mighty over all things; O Thou Knower of all things. O Thou Seer of all things. O Thou that maketh breezes blow; O Thou that cleaveth the day-break; O Reviver of the spirits;
O Lord of Generosity and Clemency; O Thou in Whose hands are all keys. O Hearer of all voices; O Thou earlier in time than all that have passed away; O Giver of life to every soul after death. O my Means of defense in confronting hardships; O my Guardian in strange lands; O my Friend in my loneliness; O my Master in my bliss; O my Refuge at the time when the journey doth tire me out and my kinsfolk hand me over to my foes and all my comrades forsake me. O Supporter of those who have no support;
O Guarantor of those who have no guarantee; O Wealth of those who have no wealth; O Means of those who have no strength; O Refuge of those who have no refuge; O Treasure of those who have no treasure; O Helper of those who have no helper; O Neighbor of those who have no neighbor. O my Neighbor that art adjacent;
O my Support that art firm; O my God that art worshipped by virtue of positive knowledge; O lord of the Ancient House (the Ka\’ba); O Thou full of loving and kindness; O nearest Friend. Liberate me from the choking fetters, Remove from me all sorrow, suffering and grief, Protect me from the evil that I am unable to bear, and help me in that which I am unable to do.
O Thou that didst restore Yusuf unto Yaqub; O Thou that didst cure Ayyub of his malady; O Thou that didst forgive the fault of Dawood; O Thou that didst lift up Isa and saved him from the clutches of the Jews; O Thou that didst answer the prayer of Yunus from the darkness; O Thou that didst choose Musa by means of Thine inspired words; O Thou that didst forgive the omission of Adam and lifted up Idris to an exalted station by Thy mercy;
O Thou that didst save Nooh from drowning; O Thou that didst destroy the former tribe of Ad and then Thamud, so that no trade of them remained, and destroyed the people of Noah aforetime, for verily they were the most unjust and most rebellious; and overturned the ruined and deserted towns;; O Thou that destroyed the people of Lot; and annihilated the people of Sho\’aib; O Thou that chose Ibrahim as a friend; O Thou that chose Musa as one spoken unto; and chose Muhammed (Thy blessings be upon him and his Progeny) as Thy Beloved;
O Thou that gavest unto Luqman wisdom; and bestowed upon Sulaiman a kingdom the like of which shall not be merited by anyone after him; O Thou that didst afford succour unto the two-horned one against the mighty tyrants; O Thou that didst grant unto Khizr immortality; and brought back for Yusha, the son of Nun, the sun after it had set; O Thou that gave solace unto the heart of Musa\’s mother; and protected the chastity of Mariam, the daughter of Imran;
O Thou that didst fortify Yahya, the Son of Zakaria against sin; and abated the wrath for Musa; O Thou that gave glad tidings of (the Birth of) Yahya unto Zakaria; O Thou that saved Ismaeel from slaughter by substituting for him the Great Sacrifice;
O Thou that didst accept the offering of Habeel and placed the curse upon Qabeel. O Subduer of the alien hordes for Muhammad - the blessings of Allah be upon him and his Progeny - bestow Thy blessings upon Muhammad and his Progeny and upon all Thy Messengers and upon the Angels that are near Thee and upon all Thine obedient servants.
And I beg of Thee all the requests which anyone has begged of Thee with whom Thou has been pleased and unto whom Thou has assured the granting thereof, O Allah, O Allah, O Allah, O Most Merciful, O Most Merciful, O Most Merciful, O Most Beneficient, O Most Beneficient, O Most Beneficient, O Lord of Majesty and Grace, O Lord of Majesty and Grace, O Lord of Majesty and Grace. Through Thee, Through Thee, Through Thee, Through Thee, Through Thee, Through Thee,
Through Thee I beseech thee with the help of all the Names whereby Thou hast named Thyself, or which Thou hast sent down in any of Thy inspired Scriptures, or Which Thou hast inscribed in Thy knowledge of the unknown;
and (I beseech Thee) in the name of the honored and exalted positions of Thy Throne, and in the name of the utmost extent of Thy Mercy as expressed in Thy Book (the Quran) and in the name of that which "If all the trees on earth were to become pens and all the seven seas ink, the Words of Allah could not be fully written down."
"Verily Allah is the Honored, the Wise"; And I beseech Thee with the help of Thy Beautiful Names which Thou has praised in Thy Book, saying,:Unto Allah belong the beautiful names -- so call ye Him by Them; And Thou hast said "Call unto Me and I shall answer you; and Thou has said,
"And when My servants ask something of Me, lo, I am near, and I grant the prayer of the supplicant when he asks anything of Me, so pray ye unto Me and believe in Me, that ye may be made perfect; And Thou has said, "O My servants who have wronged yourselves, despair not of the Mercy of Allah; verilly Allah forgiveth all the sins; verily He is the Forgiving, the Merciful."
Therefore I pray unto Thee, My God, and I ask Thee, My Cherisher and Sustainer, and I hope from Thee, my Chief, and I crave Thy acceptance of my prayer, O my Protector, even as Thou hast promised me, and I call upon Thee even as Thou hast commanded me --
So, do unto me what pleases Thee to do, O Generous One! (Here the Devotee should pray for the fulfillment of his valid desires.) And all Praise be to Allah, the Cherisher and Sustainer of the worlds,
and the blessings of Allah be upon Muhammad and all His Holy Descendants
    </string>



   <string name="duaehazin">
     BISMILLA HIR RAHMA NIR RAHIM \n
       UNAJIKA YA
    MAW\’JOODAN FI KULLI MAKAA\’N LA\’Al\’lAKAA DASMAOO
    NEDAAEE FA\’QAD\’ADAMA JURMI WA GALA HAYYA\’I MAWLA YA YA MAWLAI
    AYEEL AHWALI ATAZ\’DEKAR WA AYUHA ANSAA WA LAAO LAM YAKOON IL\’AL
    MAAWT\’U LAKA FAA\’A KAYFAA WA MAA BADIL MAWT\’I A\’ZMOO WA ADHA\’AA

     MAWLAYA YA\’
     YA MAWLA\’I HATTA MATTA WA ILAA MATTA A\’QUL\’LU\’LAKA
            UTBAA MA\’RAATAN BAADAL UKHRAA THUMA\’LA TA\’JIDU ENDEE SIDQAAN WA
            LAA WA\’FAA\’AN FA YAA MAW\’THAA\’HU THUMA WA MAW\’THAA BIKA YA
            Allah\’HU MEEN HAW\’AA QAD\’QALABA\’NEE WA MEEN ADUU\’EN
            QADI\’STAK\’LABA ALLIY WA MEEN DUNYAA QAD\’DAZAYEE\’NAAT\’LI WA MIN
            NAFSEN AMARATEEN BI SUU\’ I\’IL LA MA
     RAHIMA RABEE


            MAWLAYA YA YA MAWLA\’I IN KUNTAA RAHIMTA MEDHLEE FA\’IHRAM\’NEE WA
            IN\’KUNTAA QABELTA MEDHLEE FA\’QBBAL\’NEE YA QABILA SAHRA\’TI
            IQ\’BAL\’NEE YA MAN LAM AZZAL ATA\’ARAFU MIN HUL HUZNA YA MAN
            JU\’RADEE\’NI BI\’NI\’AMEE SABAA\’HAN WA MASA\’AL IHRAM\’NEE YOWMAA
            ATIKKA FARDAA SHA\’KHRI\’SAN ILAY\’KA BASARI MUQALIDDAN AMMALI
            QAD\’TA BARA\’A JAMEE\’UL KHALQE MENNI

            NA\’AM WA ABI WA UMI WA MAN KANA LAHO KAD\’EE WASAA\’IY FA ILAM
                TARHEMNI FA MAY JARR\’HAMUNI WA MAY JU\’NIZU FIL QABRI WASH\’ATI WA
            MAY JUNDE\’QOO LISANI ITHA KHA\’LAWTU FI AMALI WA SAA\’AL\’TANEE AM
            MAA ALAMU ANTA BIHI MENNI FA IN QULTU NAA\’AM FA AY\’NAAL MAHRABOO
            MIN ADLEEK WA IN QULTA LAM AFAAL QULTA ALAM AKUN\’ I SHA\’HIDA
            ILAAYK

            FA AWFUKA AWFUKA YA MAWLA\’I QABLA SARA\’BI LI QAD\’RAAN AWFUKA
            AWFUKA YA MAWLA\’I QABLA JAHANAM WA\’N NIRRA AWFUKA AWFUKA YA
            MAWLA\’I QABLA ANTU\’RALAL AYDI ILAL A\’INA YA ARHAMEEL RAHMEEN, WA
            SALALUH ALA MOHAMMAD WA ALI MOHAMMAD


    </string>


   <string name="duaekumayl">
 Kumayl Ibn Ziyad Nakha\’i was a confidant amongst the companions of  Imam Ali Ibn Abi Talib (as.) and this sublime Du\’a was first heard from the beautiful, though anguished, voice of Imam Ali. \n
According to Allama Majlisi (on whom be Allah\’s Mercy) Kumayl had attended an assembly in the Mosque at Basra which was addressed by Imam Ali in the course of which the night of the 15th of Shaban was mentioned. Imam Ali said-"Whosoever keeps awake in devoutness on this night and recites the Du\’a of Prophet Khizr, undoubtedly that person\’s supplication will be responded to and granted. When the assembly at the Mosque had dispersed, Kumayl called at the house where Imam Ali was staying, and requested him to acquaint him with Prophet Khizr\’s "Du\’a". Imam Ali asked Kumayl to sit down, record and memorise the "Du\’a" which Imam Ali dictated to Kumayl.\n
Imam Ali then advised Kumayl to recite this "Du\’a" on the eve of (i.e. evening preceding) every Friday, or once a month or at least once in every year so that, added Imam Ali, "Allah may protect thee from the evils of the enemies and the plots contrived by impostors. O\’ Kumayl! in consideration of thy companionship and understanding, I grant thee this honour of entrusting this "Du\’a" to thee."\n \n




       BISMILLA HIR RAHMA NIR RAHIM \n
       ALLA-HOOMA INNI AS\’ALOKA BE-RAHMATEKALLATI VASE\’AT KOOLLA SHAI\’IN WABE-QOO-VATEKALLATI QAHARAT
       BEHA KOALLA SHAI\’IN WA KHAZA\’A LAHA KOALLA SHAI\’IN WAZALLA LAHA KAALLA SHAI\’IN WA BE-JABAROATEKAL-LATI GHALABTA BEHA KOOLLA
       SHAI\’IN WABE-\’LZZATEKAL-LATI LA YAQAOMO LAHA SHAI\’OON WA BE-\’AZMATEKAL-LATI MALA.TA KOOLLASHAI\’ IN WA BE-SOOLTANEKAL-LAZI
       \’ALA KAOLLA SHAI\’IN WA BE-VAJ-HEKAL-BAQI BA\’DAFANAA\’E KOALA SHAI\’IN WA BE-ASMAA\’EKAL-IATI MALA-AT ARKANA KAALLA SHAI\’IN
       BE-ILMEKAL-LAZI AHATA BE-KAOLLE SHAI\’INWO BE-NOORE VAJ-HEKAL-IAZI AZAA\’ALAHOO KAALLASHAI\’IN YA NOORO YA QOODDOASOYA AV-VALAL-
       AV-VALEENA YA AKHIRAL-AKHEREENA, ALLA-HOOMMAGHFIRLE-YAZ-ZON-OOBAL-LATI TAH-TEKAL-\’ASAM, ALLA-HOOMMAGHFIR-LEYAZ-ZONOOBAL-IATI
       TAGHYYEROOL-NE\’AMA. ALLA-HOOMMAGH-FIRLE-YAZ-ZONOOBAL-LATI TAHAB-BESAD-DOAA\’A;ALLA-HOOMAGHFIRLE-YAZ-ZANAOBAL-LATI TAQTA\’ OOR-
       RAJAA\’ A. ALLA-HAOMAGHFIRLE-YAZ-ZONOOBAL-LATI TONAZ-ZE-IOOI-BALAA\’A, ALLA-HOOMAGHFIRLI KOOLLA ZAMBIN AZ-NABTO-HOOWA KOOLLA
       KHATI\’ATIN AKH-TA-TOHA ALLA-HOONMA INNI ATA-QARRABO ILAHIKA BE-ZIKREKAVAS-TASHFE\’OBEKA ILA NAFSEKA WA AS\’ALOKA BE-JOODEKA WA
       KARAMEKA AN TOOD-NEYANI MINQOORBEKA WA AN TOOZE\’ANI SHOOKRAKA WA AN TOOLHEMANI ZIKRAKA, ALLO-HOOMMA INNIAS\’ALOKA SO\’ALA KHAZE\’IM MOOTAZOL-IIL KHASHE\’IM-MATAZAR-RE\’IN AN TOOSA MEHANI WATARHAMANI WA TAJ\’ALNI BE-QISMEKA RAZIYAN QANE\’AN WA FEE JAMI\’IL-AHVALEMOOTAVAZE\’AN,
       ALLA-HOOMA WA AS\’ALOKA SO\’ALA MANISH-TADDAT FAQATAHOO WA AL1ZALABEKA \’INDASH-SHADAA\’EDE HAJATAHOO WA \’AZOMA FEEMA \’INDAKA RAGHBA-TOHO,ALLA-HOOMMA\’AZOMA SOOLTANOKA WA \’ALA-MAKANOKA WA KHAFE-YA MAKROKA WA ZAHARA AMROKA WA GHALABAQAHROKA WA JARAT QOODRATOKA WA LA YOOMKENOOL
       FIRARO MIN HOOKOOMATEKA, ALLA-HOOMALA AJIDO LE-ZANOOBI GHAFERAON WA LA LE-QABAA\’EHI SATERAN WA LA LE-SHAIM MIN\’AMALIL QABEEHIN BIL-HOOSNE MOOBADDELAN GHAIRAKA LAA ILAHA ILLA ANTA SOOBHANAKA WABE-HAMDEKA ZALAMTO NAFSEE WA TAJARRATO BEJAHLI WA SAKANTO ILA QADEEME ZIKREKA LEEWA
       MINNEKA \’ALYYA, ALLA-HOOMMA MAVLAYA KAM MIN QABEEHE SATARATAHO WA KAM MINFADEHIM MINAL-BALAA\’E AQALTAHOO WA KAM MIN
       \’ISARIN WA KAM MIM MAKROOHIN DAF\’ATAHOOWA KAM MIN SANAA\’IN JAMEELIL-JASTO AHLAL-LAHOO NASHRATAHOO, AJLA-HOOMA \’AZMABALAA\’EE WA
       AFRATA BI SOO\’O HALI WA QASORATBI A\’MALI WA QA\’ADAT BI AGHLALI WA HABASANI \’AN NAFEE BO\’DO AMALI WAKHADA \’ATANID-DOONYABE-GHOROOREHA WA NAFSI
       BE-KHEYANATEHA WA MATALI YA SYYEDI FA-AS\’ALOKA BE-IZZATEKA AL-IA YAHJOBA \’ANKA DOAA\’EE SOO\’O \’AMALI WA FE\’ALI WA LA
       TAF-ZAHNI BE-KHAFI-YO MAT-TALA\’TA \’ALAIHE MIN SIRRI WA LA TOAJILNI BIL-\’OQOOBATE \’ALAMA \’AMILTOHOO FEE KHALAVATI MIN SOO\’AY
       FAILI WA ISAA\’A WA DAVAME TAFREETI WAJAHALATI WA KASRATE SHAHVATI WA GHAFALATI WA KIN; AJJA-HOOMMA BE-\’LZZATEKA LEEFIL-AHVAIE
       KOOLLEHA RA\’OOFAN WA \’ALYYA
       FEE JAMEE\’IL-OMOORE \’ATOOFAN ILAHI WAMAVLAYA WA RABBI MAL-II G HAIROKA AS\’ALOKA KASHAFA ZORRI VAN-NAZARA FEE AMREEILAHI WA MAV-LAYA AJVAITA \’ALYYA HOOKMA NIT-TABA.TO FEEHE HAVA NAFSI WA LAM AHTARISFAEHE MIN TAZ\’EENE \’ADOO-VEE FAGHARRANI BE-MAA AHVA WA AS\’ADAHO \’ALA ZALEKAL-QAZAA\’O FATAJAVAZTA BE-MA JARA \’ALYYA MIN ZALEKA BA\’ZA HODOODEKA WA KHALOFTO BA\’ZAAVAMIREKA FALAKAL-HAMDO \’ALYYA FEE JAMGE\’AY ZALEKA WA LA HOOJJATA LEE FEEMA JARA\’ALYYA FEEHE QAZAA\’OKA WA ALZAMANI HOOKMOKA WA BALAA\’OKA WA QAD ATAITOKA YA ILLAHIBA\’DA TAQSEERI WA ISRAFI \’ALA NAFSEE MO\’TAZERAN NADEMAM MAONKASERAM MOOSTAQEEJAMMOOSTAGHFERAM MONEEBAM MOQIRRAM MOOZ\’ENAM MO\’TAREFAL-LA AJEDO MAFARRAM MIMMA KANAMINNI WA LA MAFZA\’AN ATAVAJ-JAHOO ILLAHE FEE AMRI GHAIRAQABOOLEKA \’OZRI WA IDKHALEKA IYYAYA FEE SA\’ATIM MIR-RAHMATEKA. ALLA-HOOMA FAQBAL \’OZRI VAR-HAM SHIDDATA ZORRI WA FOKKANI MIN SHADDE VA-SAQI YA RABBIR-HAM ZA\’FA BADANI WA RIQQATA JILDI WA DIQQATA \’AZMI YA MAM BADA KHALQI WA ZIKRI WATARBEYATI WA BARRI WA TAGHZEYATI HABNJ LIB-TEDAA\’AY KARAMEKA WA SALEFE BARREKA BI

YA ILAHI WA SVYEDI WA RABBI ATORAKA MO\’AZZABI BE-NAREKA BA\’DA TAVHEEDEKA WA BA\’DAMANTAVA \’ALAJHE QALBI MIM MA\’REFATEKA WA LAHEJA BEHI LESANI MIN ZIKREKAVA\’TAQGDAHOO ZAMEERI MIN HOOBEKA WA BA\’DA SIDQE NAV-TERAFI WA DO\’AAEEKHAZE\’AN LE-ROBOO-BI-VATEKA HAIHATA ANTA AKRAMO MIN AN TOZVVE\’A MAR-RAB-BAITAHOOAV-TO-BA-\’LDDA MAN ADNAITAHOO AV TOSHARREDA MAN AVAB-BAITAHOO AV TOOSAL-LEMA ILAL-BALA\’AV MAN KAFAI-TAHOO WA RAHIMTAHOO WA LAITA SHAIRRI YA SYVADI WA ILAHI WAMAVLAYA ATOSAL-LITOONNARA \’ALA VAJOOHIN KHARRAF LE\’AZAMATEKA SAJEDATAN WA \’ALAAI-SONIN NATAQAT BE- TAV-HEEDEKA SADEQATAN WA BE-SHOOKREKA MA-DEHATANWA \’ALA QOLOOBE NETARAFAT BE-ILAHI-YATEKA MOHAQ-QEQATAN WA .ALA ZAMAA\’ERA HAVALMINAL \’LIME BEKA HATTA SARAT KHASHE\’ATAN WA \’ALA JAVAREHA SA\’AT ILA AV-TANETA\’ABBODEKA TAA\’E-ATANWA ASHARAT BE-LSTIGH-FAREKA MOOZ\’ANETAN MA HAKAZALZANNO BEKA WA LAOKHBIRNA BE-FAZLEKA \’ANKA YA KARIMO YA RABBE WA ANTA TA\’LAMO ZA\’FI \’AN QALEELIMMIM BALAA\’ID-DOONYA WA \’OQOOBATEHA WA MA YAJRI FEEHA MINAL-MAKAREHE \’ALA AHLEHA\’ALA ANNA ZALEKA BALAA\’OOM MAQROOHON QALEELOOM-MAKSOHOO YASEEROON BAQAA\’OHOOQASEEROON MOOD-DATOHOO FA-KAIFA EHTEMALI LE-BALAA\’IL-AKHIRATE WA JALEELE WAQOO\’IL- MAKARAHE FEEHA WA HOVA BALAA \’OON TA\’TOOLO MOODDATOHOO WA YADOOMOMAQAMAHOO WA LA YOKHAF-FAFO \’AN AHLEHE LE-ANNAHOO LA YAKOONA ILIA \’AN GHAZABEKAVAN-TEQAMEKA WA SAKHATEKA WA HAZA MA LA TAQOOMO LAHOOS-SAMAVATO VAL-ARZO YA SYYEDIFA-KAIFA BI WA ANA \’ABDOKAZ-ZA.EEFOOZ-ZALEELOOL-HAQEEROOL-MISKEE-NOOL-MOOSTAKEENO,YA ILLAHI WA RABBI WA SYYEDI WA MAVLAYA LE-IYYIL-OMOORE I1AIKA ASHKOO WA LAMAMINHAAZIJ-JO WA ABKJ LE-ALEEMIL \’AZABE WA SHIDDATEH AV LE-TOOLIL-BALAA.AYWA MOOD-DATEHI FALA\’IN SYYAR-TANI FIL-\’OQOOBATE MA.A A.DAA.EKA WA JAMA\’TA BAJNI WABAINA AHLE BALAA\’EKA WA FARRAQTA BAINI WA BAINA AHIB-BAA\’EKA FAHBANI, YA ILAHI WASYYEDI WA MAVLAYA WA RABBI SABARTO \’ALA \’AZABAKA FA-KAIFA ASBIRO \’ALA FIRAQEKA WAHABNISABARTO \’ALA HARRENAREKA FA-KAIFA ASBIRO \’ANIN-NAZARE ILA KARAMATEKAAM KAIFA SKONO FIN-NARE WA RAJAA\’EE \’AFOOKA FA-BE\’LZZATEKA YA SYYEDI WA MAVLAYAOOQSIMO SADEQAL-IA\’IN TARAKTANI NATEQAL-IA-AZZE-JANNA ILAIKA BAINA AHLEHAZAJEEJAL-AMELEENA WA LA-ASRO KHANNA ILAIKA SOORAKHAL-MOOSTASRE-KHEENA WA LA-ABKE-YANNA \’ALAIKA BOOKAA\’AL-FAQEDEENA WA LA \’NADE-YANNAKA AINA KOONTA YA VALI-YALMO\’MENEENA YA GHAYATE AMALIL\’ AREFEENA YA GHEYASAL-MOOSTAGHEE-SEENA YA HABEEBAQOLOOBIS-SADEQEENA WA YA ILAHAL \’ALAMEENA AFATORAKA SOOBHANAKA YA ILAHI WA BE-HAMDEKA TASMA\’O FEEHA SAVTA \’ABDIM MOOSLEMIN \’SOOJENA FEEHA BE-MOKHALAFATEHI WAZAKA TA\’MA \’AZABEHA BE-MA\’SI-YATEHI WA HOOBESA BAINA ATMAQEHA BE-JOPRMEHI WAJAREERATEHA, WA HOVA YOOZIJ-JO ILAIKA ZAJEEJA MO\’AM-MELIN LE-REHMATEKA WAYOONADEEKA BE-IESANE AHLE TAVHEEDEKA WA YATAVAS-SALO ILAIKA BE-ROBOOBI-YATEKA YAMAVLAYA FA KAIFA YABQA FIL\’ AZABE WA HOVA YARJOO MA SALAFA HILMEKA WA RAF\’ATEKA WARAHMATEKA AM KAIFA TOO-IEMOHOON-NARO WA HOVA YAMOLO FAZLAKA WA RAHMATEKA AM KATFAYOH-REQOHOOLAHABOOHA WA ANTA TASMA\’O SAVTAHOO WA TARA MAKA-NAHOP AM KAIFAYASHTAMELO \’ALAIHE ZAFEEROHA WA ANTA TA\’LAMO ZA\’FAHOO AM KAIFA YATA-GHA1-GHELOBAINAATBAQEHA WA ANTA TA\’LAMO SJDQAHOO AM KAIFA TAZJO-ROHOO ZABANI-YATOHAWA HOVA YOONADEEKA YA RABBAHOO AM KAIFA YARJOO FAZLEKA FEE \’ONOQEHI MINHA FA-TAT-ROKOHOO FEEHA HAIHATA MA ZALEKAZZ-ANNO BEKA WA LAL-MA\’ROOFO MIN FAZLEKA WA LAMOOSHBEHOOL-LEMA \’AMALTO BEHIL-MOVAHHEDEENA MIM BIRREKA WA EHSANEKA FA-BIL-YAQEENEAQTA\’O LAV LA MA HAKAMTA BEHI MIN TA\’ZEEBE JAHEDEEKA WA QAZAITA BEHI MINEKHLADE MO\’ANEDEEKA LAJA\’ALTAN NAHARA KOOLLAHA BAR-DAVN WA SALAMAVN WA

MA KANAT LE-AHADIN FEEHA MAQAR-RAVN WA LA MEQAMAL-LA-KINNAKA TAQADDASAT ASMAA\’OKAAQSAMTA AN TAMLA-AHA MINAL-KAFEREENA MINAL-JINNATE VANNASE AJMA\’EENA WA ANTOOKHAL-LIDO FEEHAL-MO\’ANEDEENA WA ANTA JALLA SANAA\’OKA QOOLTA MOO-BTADE\’AN WA TA-TAVVALTA BIL-IN.AME MOOTAKARREMAN AFAMAN KANA MO\’MENAN KAMAN KANA FASEQAL-LAYAS-TA-OONA ILAHI WA SYYEDI FA-AS\’ALOKA BIL-QOODRATILLATI QADDAR- TAHABIL-QAZI-YATIL-IATI QADDAR-TAHA WA BIL-QAZI-YATIL-IATI HATAM-TAHA WA HAKAMTAHA WAGHALABTA MAN \’ALAIHE AJRAITAHA AN TAHABA LEE FEE HAZEHIL-IAI-IATE WA FEEHAZEHIS-SA\’ATE KOOLLA JOORMIN AJRAMTOHOO WA KOOLLA ZAMBIN AZ-NAB-TOHOO WA KOOLLAQABEEHIN ASRAR-TOHOO WA KOOLLA JAHLIN \’AMIL-TOHOO KATAM-TOHOO AV A\’LAN-TOHOO AKH-FAL-TOHOO AV AZHAR-TOHOO WA KOOLLA SYYE\’ATIN AMARTA BE-LSBAQEHAL-KIRAMAL-KATEBEENAL-LAZEENA VAK-KAL-TA-HDOM BE-HIFZE MA YAKOONA MINNI WA JA\’ALTA-HOOMSHOHOODAN \’ALYYA MA\’A JAVAREHI WA KOONTA ANTAR-RAQEEBA \’ALYYA MIN VARAA\’EHIM VASH-SHAHEDA LEMA KHAFE-YA \’AN- HOOM WA BE-RAHMATEKA AKHFAI-TAHOO WA BE-FAZLEKA SATAR-TAHOO WA AN TAVAFFIRA HAZZI MIN KOOLLE KHAIRIN TOONZELOHOO AV EHSANIN TOOFZELOHOOAV BIRRIN TAN-SHOROHOO AV RIZQIN BASAT-TAHO AV ZAMBIN TAGHFEROHOO AV KHATA\’INTASTOROHOO, YA RABBE, YA RABBE YA RABBE YA ILAHI WA SYYEDI WA MAVLAYA WA MALEKARIQQI YAMAM BE-YADEHI NASI-YATI YA ALIMAN BE-ZORRI WA MASKALANI YA KHABIRANBE-FAQRI WA FAQATI, YA RABBE YA RABBE, YA RABBE AS\’ALOKA BE-HAQQEKA WA QOOD-SEKAWA A\’ZAME SIFATEKA WA ASMAA\’EKA AN TAJ\’AL AV-QATI FIL-IAILE VAU-NAHARE BE-ZIKREKAMA\’MOORATAVN WA BE-KHIZMATEKA MAVSOO-LATAVN, WA A\’MALI \’INDAKS MAQBOOLATAN- HATTATAKOONA A\’MALI WA AVRADI KOOLLAHA VIRDAVN VAHEDAN WA HALI FEE KHID-MATEKASARMADAN, YA SYYEDI, YA MAN \’ALAIHE MO\’AV-VALI, YA MAN ILAIHE SHAKAVTO AHVALI, YARABBTL, YA RABBE, YA RABBE QAV-VE \’ALA KHID-MATEKA JAVAREHI VASH-DOOD \’ALAL\’AZIMATE JAVANEHI VAHAB LI-YAL- JADDE FEE KHASH-YATEKA VAD-DAVAME FIL-ITTE-SALEBE-KHID-MATEKA HATTA ASRAHA ILAIKA FEE MAYA-DEENIS-SABEQEENA OOSRE\’A ILAIKA FILMOOBADEREENA VA3H-TAQA LLA AOORBEKA FIL-MOOSHTAQEENA WA ADNOOVA MINKA DONOV-VAL-MOOKHLESEENA WA AHFAKA MAKHAFATAL-MOOQENEENA VAJ-TAMA\’A FEE JAVAREKA MA\’AL-MO\’MENEENA, ALLA-HOOMMA WA MAN ARADANI BE-SOO\’JN FA-ARIDHO WA MAN KADANI FAKJDHAVAJ\’ALNI MIN AHSANE \’IBADEKA NASEEBAN \’INDAKA WA AQRA-BE-HIM MANZELATAM MINKA WAAKHZE-HIM ZAAL-FATAL-IADAJKA FA-INNAHOO LA-YANALO ZALEKA TLLA BE-FAZLEKA WA JODANIBE-JOODEKA VA\’TIF \’ALYYA BE-MAJ-DEKA VAH-TIZNI BE-RAHMATEKA VAJ\’AL LASANI BE-ZIKREKA LAHEJAN WA QALBI BE-HOOBBEKA MOOTAMYYEMAN WA MANNA BE-HOOSNE IJABATEKA WAAQILNI \’ASRATJ VAGHFIRLI ZALLATI FA INNAKA FAZAITA \’ALA \’LBADEKA BE-IBADATEKA WAAMARTA-HOOM BE-DOAA\’EKA WA ZAMINTA LAHOMAAL-IJABATA FA-ILAIKA YA RABBE NASABTAVAJ-HEYA WA ILAIKA YA RABBE MADAD-TO YADE-YA FA-BE-\’LZZATEKAS- TAJIB LEE DOAA\’EEWA BALLIGHNI MOONAYA WA LA TAQ-TA\’MIN FAZLEKA RAJAA\’EE YA SAREE\’OOR-REZA IGH-FIRLEMAL-LA YAMLEKOOD-DOAA\’A FA-INNAKA FA.ALOOL-LEMA TASHAA\’O YA MANIS-MOHOODAVAA\’OON WA ZIKROHOA SHLFAA\’AAN WA TA\’ATOHOO \’GHENAN IRHAM-MAR RASA MALEHIR-RAJAA\’O WA SILAHO-HOOL-BOOKAA\’O YA SABEGHAN-NE\’AMAY YA DAFE\’ANNEQAMAY YA NOORAL-MASTAV-HESHGENA FIZ-ZOLAME YA \’ALEMAL-LA-YA\’LAMA SALLE \’ALAA MOHAMMADIN WA AALEMOHAMMADIN VAF\’AL BI MA ANTA AHLOHOO WA SAL-IAL-IAHO \’ALA RASOALEHI VAL-A\’IMMATILMAYAMGENA MIN ALEHI WA SALJAM TASLEEMAN KASEERAN ASEERA:ALLAHAOMMA SAL1E ALAA MOHAMMADIN WA AALE MAHAMMA


   </string>


    <string name="duaeganjularsh">
         BISMILLA HIR RAHMA NIR RAHIM \n
      LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL MALIK UL QUDOOS
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL AZIZ UL JABBAR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL RAUF UR RAHEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL GHAFOOR IR RAHEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL KAREEM IL HAKEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL QAWI IL WAFI
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL LATEEF IL KHABEER
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL SAMAD IL MA\’BOOD
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL GHAFOOR IL WADOOD
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL WAKEEL IL KAFEEL
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL RAQEEB IL HAFEEZ
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL DAEM IL QAEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL MUHI UL MUMEET
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL HAYYUL QAYYUM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL KHALIQ IL BAARI
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL ALI IL AZEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL WAHID IL AHAD
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL MOMIN IL MUHAIMIN
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL HASEEB IS SHAHEED
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL HALEEM IL KAREEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL AWAL IL QADEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL AWAL IL AKHIR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL ZAHIR IL BAATIN
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL KABEER IL MUTA\’AL
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL QAZI IL HAJAAT
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL REHMAN IR RAHEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA RABBIL ARSHIL AZEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA RABBI AL AALA
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL BURHAN IL SULTAN
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AS SAMI IL BASEER
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL WAHID IL QAHAAR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL ALEEM IL HAKEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AS SATTAR IL GHAFAAR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AR REHMAN ID DAYYAN
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL KABEER IL AKBAR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL ALEEM IL ALLAM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AS SAFI IL KAAFI
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AZEEM IL BAQI
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AS SAMAD IL AHAD
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA RABIL ARDE WAS SAMAAEY
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL KHALIQ IL MAKHLOOK
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA MAN KHALAQ AL LAILE WAN NAHAAR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL KHALIQ IR RAZZAQ
LA ILAHHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL FATTAH IL ALEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL AZEEZ IL GHANI
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL GHAFOOR IS SHAKOOR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL AZEEM IL ALEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA ZIL MULKE WAL MALAKOOT
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA ZIL IZZATE WAL AZMATE
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA ZIL HAIBATE WAL QUDRATE
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA ZIL KIBRIYA E WAL JABAROOT
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AS SATTAR IL AZEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL ALIM IL GHAIB
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL HAMEED E WAL MAJEED
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL HAKEEM IL QADEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL QADIR IL SATTAR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AS SAMI IL ALEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL GHANI IL AZEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL ALAM IS SALAM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL MALIK IN NASEER
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL GHANI IR RAHMAN
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL QAREEB IL HASANAAT
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AS SABOOR IS SATTAR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL KHALIQ IN NOOR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL GHANI IL MOJIZ
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL FADIL IS SHAKOOR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL GHANI IL QADEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA ZIL JALAL IL MUBEEN
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL KHALIS IL MUKHLIS
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AS SADIQ IL WAED
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL HAQ IL MUBEEN
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA ZIL QUWATIL MATEEN
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL QAWI IL AZIZ
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL ALLAM IL GHOYOOB
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL HAYYIL LA YAMOOT
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AS SATTAR IL AYOOB
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL MUSTA\’AN IL GHAFOOR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA RABBIL ALAMEEN
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AR REHMAN IS SATTAR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AR RAHEEM IL GHAFAAR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL AZEEZ IL WAHAB
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL QADIR IL MUKTADIR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA ZIL GHUFRAN IL HALEEM
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL MALIK IL MULK
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL BARI IL MUSAWWIR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL AZIZ IL JABBAR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL JABBAR IL MUTAKABBIR
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN ALLAHI AMMA YASI FUN
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL QUDOOS IS SUBOOH
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA RABBIL MALAEKATI WAR ROOH
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHANA ZIL ALA E WAN NA\’AMA E
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL MALIK IL MAQSOOD
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO SUBHAN AL HANNAN IL MANNAN
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO ADAM SAFI ULLAH
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO NOOH E NAJI ULLAH
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO IBRAHIM KHALIL ULLAH
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO ISMAEL ZABI ULLAH
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO MUSA KALEEM ULLAH
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO DAWOOD KHALIFA TULLAH
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO EISA ROOH ALLAH
LA ILAHA ILLAL LAHO MUHAMMAD UR RASOOL ALLAH
WA SALLAL LAHO ALA KHAIRI KHALKIHI WA NOORI ARSHI HI
AFDALIL AMBIYA HI WAL MURSALEENA HABEEBINA WA SAYYIDINA
WA SANADINA WA SHAFI INA WA MAULANA MUHAMMADIN
WA ALA AALIHI WA ASHAABIHI AL MUNTAJABEENA BI REHMATIKA
YA AR HAMAR RAHEEMIN
    </string>


    <string name="duaemeraj">
 Allama Kafmi has written this dua\’a in his book Misbah, on the authority of Imam Ali ibna abi Talib who learned it from the Holy Prophet.
The Holy Prophet said:\n
"Allah will have mercy on him who keeps this dua\’a as a tawid, and recites it a great deal. He will forgive his sins and the sins of parents and his children, bestow on him countless blessings, keep him safe from misfortunes, multiply his earnings, and cure his ailments."
Top improve and develop memory write the (Arabic) text of this dua\’a on a clean piece of paper with saffron, wash it with pure water and drink it.\n
Hang the written (Arabic) text of this dua\’a (like a tawid) around the neck of children to keep them safe from wild and poisonous animals, and the evil of witchcraft and jinn.\n
It is reported that at the time of mi-raj the Holy Prophet saw this dua\’a written at the last post, qaaba qawsayn aw adnaa. The almighty Allah informed him that whoso recites this heavenly dua\’a or keeps it written version on his person, will get countless blessings.

\n \n


         BISMILLA HIR RAHMA NIR RAHIM \n
        ALLAAHUMMA INNEE AS—ALUKA YAA MAN AQARRA LAHOO BIL U\’BOODIYYAIL KULLU MAA\’—BOOD YAA MAN YAH\’MADUHOO KULLU MAH\’MOOD YAA MAN YAFZA—U\’ILAYHI KULLU MAJHOOD YAA MAN YAT\’LABU I\’NDAHOO KULLU MAQS\’OOD YAA MAN SAAA—ILUHOO GHAYRU MARDOUD YAA MAN BAABUHOOA\’N SU—AALIHEE GHAYRU MASDOOD YAA MAN HUWA GHAYRU MAWS\’OOFIN WA LAA MAH\’DOOD YAA MAN A\’TAA—UHOO GHAYRU MAMNOO—I\’NWA LAA MANKOOD

YAA MAN HUWA LIMAN DA-\’AHU LAYSA BI—BA—E\’EDIN WA HUWA NIA MAL MAQS\’OOD YAA MAN RAJAAA—U I\’BAADIHEE BIH\’ABLIHEE MASHDOOD YAA MAN SHIBHUHOO WA MITHLUHOO GHAYRU MAWJOOD

YAA MAN LAYSA BI—WAALIDIN WA LAA MAWLOOD YAA MAN KARAMUHOO WA FAZ\’LUHOO LAYSA BI—MAA\’—DOOD YAA MAN H\’AWZ”U BIRRIHEE LIL ANAAMI MAWROOD YAA MAN LAA YOOS\’AFU BIQIYAAMIN WA LAA QU—O\’OD YAA MAN LAA TAJREE A\’LAYHI H\’ARAKATUN WA LAA JAMOOD YAA ALLAAHU YAA RAH\’MAANU YAA RAH\’EEMU YAA WADOOD YAA RAH\’IMASHSHAYKHIL KABEERI YAA –QOOB YAA GHAFERAZ D\’AMBE DA\’WOOD

YAA MAN LAA YUKHLIFUL WAA—DA WA YAA\’—FUWA A\’NIL MAW—O\’OD YAA MAN RIZQUHOO WA SITRUHOO LIL—A\’AS\’EENA MAMDOOD YA MAN HUWA MALJAA—U KULLI MUQS\’AN MAT\’ROOD YAA MAN DAANA LAHOO JAMEE—U\’KHALQIHEE BIS SUJOOD YAA MAN LAYSA A\’N NAYLIHEE WAJOODIHEE AH\’ADUN MAS\’DOOD YAA MAL LAA YAH\’EEFU FEE H\’UKMIHEE WA YAH\’LUMU A\’NIZ\’Z\’AALIMIL A\’NOOD IRH\’AM U\’BAYDAN KHAAT\’I—AN LAM YOOFI BIL—U\’HOOD INNAKA FA—A\’ALUL LIMAA TUREED YAA BAARRU YAA WADOODU S\’ALLI A\’LAA MUH\’AMMADIN KHAYRI MAB—O\’OTHIN DA-A\’A ILLA KHAYRI MAA\’—BOOD WA A\’LAA AALIHIT\’ T\’AYYIBEENAT\’ T\’AAHIREENA ALIL KARAMI WALJOOD WAF—A\’L BINAA MAA ANTA AHLUHOO YAA ARH\’AMAR\’ RAAH\’IMEEN YAA AKRAMAL KARAMEEN.
    </string>

    <string name="duaenoor">
 It is reported in Muhaj al Dawat by sayyid bin Tawus that bibi Fatimah Zahrah taught this dua\’a to Salman. The Holy Prophet had given this dua\’a to his daughter with instruction that whoso recites it daily, in the morning and evening, remains safe from fever.\n \n




         BISMILLA HIR RAHMA NIR RAHIM \n
        ALLA-HUMA YA NOORAN-NORAY TANAV-VARTA BIN NOORAY VAN-NOORO FEE-NOORAY NOORAY –KA YA NOOR.

ALLA-HUMMA YA AZEEZO TA\’AZZAZTA BIL-IZZATAY VAL-IZ-ZATO FEE IZZATEKA YA AZEEZ.

ALLA-HUMMA YA JALEELO TAJALLAT BIL JALALE VAL-JALAALO FEE-JALAALE JALAALEKA YA JALEEL.

ALLA-HUMA YA WAHHABO TAVAH-HABTA BIL-HEBATAY VAL-HEBATO FEE-HEBATAY HEBATEKA YA WAHHAB.

ALLAHUMMA YA AZEEMO TA\’AZ-ZAMTA BIL AZ-MATAY VAL-AZMATO FEE-AZMATAY AZ-MATEKA YA AZEEM.

ALLA-HUMMA YA ALIMO TA\’ALLAMTA BIL-ILMAY VAL-ILMO FEE-ILMAY ILMEKA YA ALIM.

ALLA-HUMMA YA QUD-DOSO TAQAD-DASTA BIL-QUDSAY VAL-QUDSO FEE-QUDSAY QUDSEKA YA QUDDOOS.

ALLA-HUMMA YA JAMEELO TAJAMMALTA BIL-JAMAALAY VAL-JAMAAALO FEE-JAMAALAY JAMAALEKA YA JAMEEL

ALLA-HUMMA YA SALAAMO TASALLAMTA BIS-SALAAMAY VAS-SALAAMO FEE-SALAAME SALAAMEKA YA SALAAM.

ALLA-HUMMA YA SABOORO TASAB-BARTA BIS-SABRAY VAS-SABRO FEE-SABRAY SABREKA YA SABOR.

ALLA-HUMMA YA MALIKO TAMALLAKTA BIL-MALOOKOOTAY VAL-MALAKOOTO FEE – MALAKOOTAY MALKOOTEKA YA MAALIK.

ALLA-HUMMA YA RABBO TARABBAITA BIR-RABOOBIYYATAY VAR- RABOOBIYYATO FEE-RABOOBIYYATA RABOOBIYYATEKA YA RABB.

ALLAHUMMA YA MANNANO TAMANNANTA BIL MINNATAY VAL MINNATO FEE MINNATAY MINNATEKA YA MAN-NAN.

ALLA HUMMA YA HAKIMO TAHAKKAMTA BIL HIKMATAY VAL HIKMATO FEE HIKMATAY HIKMATEKA YA HAKEEM.

ALLHUMA YA HAMEEDO TAHAMMAD-TA BIL HAMDAY VAL HAMDO FE HAMDAY HAMDEKA YA HAMEED.

ALL HUMMA YA WAHEDO TAVAH-HADTA BIL VAHDA-NIYYATAY VAL VAH-DANIYYATO FEE VAHDA-NIYYATAY YA VAAHED.

ALLA-HUMMA YA FARDO TAFAR-RADTA BIL FARDA-NIYYATAY VAL – FARDA- NIYYATO FEE FARDA-NIYYATIN FARDANIYYATEKA YA FARDO.

ALLA HUMA YA HALIMO TAHALLAMTA BIL HILMAY VAL HILMO FEE HILMAY HILMEKA YA HALIM.

ALLA-HUMMA YA QADIRO TAQADDARTA BIL-QUDRATAY VAL-QUDRATO FEE-QUDRATAY QUDRATEKA YA QADEER.

ALLA-HUMMA YA QADEEMO TAQAD-DAMTA BIL-QEDAMAY VAL-QEDAMO FEE-QEDAMAY QEDAMEKA YA QADEEM.

ALLA-HUMMA YA SHAHEDO TASHAH-HADTA BISH-SHAHAADATAY VASH-SHAHAADATO FEE- SHAHAADATAY SHAHAADATEKA  YA SHAAHED.

ALLA-HUMMA YA QARIBO TAQAR-RABTA BIL-QURBAY VAL-QURBO FEE –QURBAY QURBEKA YA QARIB.

ALLA-HUMMA YA NASEERO TANAS-SARTA BIN-NUSRATAY VAN-NUSRATO FEE-NUSRATAY NUSRATEKA YA NASIR.

ALLA-HUMMA YA SATTAARO TASAT-TARTA BIS-SATRAY VAS-SATRO FEE-SATRAY SATREKA YA SATTAAR.

ALLA-HUMMA YA QAH-HAARO TAQAH-HARTA BIL-QAHRAY VAL-QAHRO FEE-QAHRAY QAHREKA YA QAH-HAAR.

ALLA-HUMMA YA RAZZAAQO TARAZ-ZAQTA BIR-RIZQAY VAR-RIZQO FEE – RIZQAY RIZQEKA YA RAZZAAQ.

ALLA-HUMMA YA KHAALEQO TAKHALLAKTA BIL-KHALQAY VAL-KHALQO FEE KHALQAY KHALQEKA YA KHAL-LAQ.

ALLA-HUMMA YA FATTAAHO TAFATTAH-TA BIL-FAT-HAY VAL –FAT-HO FEE-FAT-HAY FAT-HEKA YA FATTAAH.

ALLA-HUMMA YA RAFI\’O TARAFFA\’ATA BIR-RAF\’ATAY VAR-RAF\’ATO FEE RAF\’ATAY RAF\’ATEKA YA RAFI\’A.

ALLA-HUMMA YA HAFEEZO TAHAFFAZTA BIL-HIFZAY VAL-HIFZO  FEE-HIFZAY HIFZEKA YA HAFEEZ.

ALLA-HUMA YA FAAZELO TAFAZ-ZALTA BIL-FAZLAY VAL-FAZLO FEE FAZLAY FAZLEKA YA FAAZEL.

ALLA-HUMMA YA VAASELO TAVAS-SALTA BIL-VASLAY VAL-VASLO FEE-VASLAY VASLEKA YA VAASEL.

ALLA-HUMMA YA FAA\’ELO TAFA\’A-ALTA BIL-FE\’A-LAY VAL-FE\’ALO FEE-FE\’A-LAY FE \’ ALEKA YA FAA\’EL.

ALLA-HUMMA YA FAAREZO TAFAR-RAZTA BIL-FARZAY VAL-FARZO FEE-FARZAY FARZEKA YA FAAREZ

ALLA-HUMMA YA GHAF-FAARO TAGHAFFARTA BIL-MAGHFERATAY VAL-MAGHFERATO FEE-MAGHFERATAY MAGHFERATEKA YA GHAFFAAR.

ALLA-HUMA YA JABBARO TAJABBARTA BIL JABAROOTAY VAL-JABROOTO FEE-JABROOTAY JABROOTEKA YA JABBAAR.

ALLA-HUMMA YA SAMEE\’O TASAM-MA\’ATA BIS-SAM\’AY VAS-SAM\’O FEE-SAM\’AY SAM\’EKA YA SAMEE\’A.

ALLA-HUMMA YA KABEERO TAKABBARTA BIL-KIBRIYAA\’AY VAL – KIBRIYAA\’O FEE-KIBRIYAA\’AY KIBRIYAA\’EKA YA KABEER.

ALLA-HUMMA YA KARIMO TAKAR-RAMTA BIL-KARAMAY VAL-KARAMO FE-KARAMAY KARAMEKA YA KARIM.

ALLA-HUMMA YA RAHIMO TARAH-HAMTA BIR-RAHMAY VAR-RAHMO FEE-RAHMAY RAHMEKA YA RAHIM.

ALLA-HUMMA YA MAJIDO TAMAJJADTA BIL-MAJDAY VAL-MAJDO FEE-MAJDAY MAJDEKA YA MAJEED. YA MUJIBO, YA ALLAHO, YA RAH-MANO, YA RAHIMO, YA HAYYO, YA HALIMO, YA AZIZO, YA NOORAN-NOORAY, YA LA-ILAHA ILLA HUWA ALAIHE TAWAKKALTO VA-HUNA RABBUL ARSHIL AZEEM.

ALHAMDO-LILLAHIL WAHHABE,

SUB-HANAL MAJEEDAY,

SUB-HAANAS-SABORAY,

SUB-HAANAL BASEERAY,

SUB-HAANAL-MAANE-AY,

SUB-HAANAL QAYYOOMAY,

SUB-HAANAL-BARRAY,

SUB-HAANAL MO\’AAFEE,

SUB-HAANAL AVVALAY,

SUB-HAANAL MOIZ-ZAY,

SUB-HANAZ ZAAHERAY,

SUB-HAANASH SHAAFI,

SUB-HAANAL KAAFI,

SUB-HAANAS SALAMAY,

SUB-HAANAL MO\’A-MENAY,

SUB-HAANAL MOHAIMENAY,

SUB-HAANAL MOSAV-VER.

SUB-HAANAN NAASERAY,

SUB-HAANAL VAAHIDAY,

SUB-HAANAL AHADAY,

SUB-HAANAL FARDAY,

SUB-HAANAR RAHIMAY,

SUB-HAANAL MOAKH-KHERAY,

SUB-HAANAL MOQADDAMAY,

SUB-HAANAZ ZAAR-RAR,

SUB-HAANAN NOORAY,

SUB-HAANAL HAADI,

SUB-HAANAL MOQADDARAY,

SUB-HAANAL JALEELAY,

SUB-HAANAL MAJEEDAY,

SUB-HAANAR RAQEEB.

SUB-HAANAL-LAHE VAL-HAMDO LIL-LAHE VA-LA ILAAHA ILLAL-LAHO VALLAHO-AKBER, VA-LA HAVLA VA-LA QUVVATA ILLA BILLA HIL ALIYYIL AZEEM.

SUB-HAANA MAYN-YASHAA\’O  BE-QUDRATEHI VA-YA\’A-LAMO MAA-YARIDO BE-IZZATEHI

SUB-HAANALLAHE VA-BE HAMDEHI

SUB-HAAN LIL-ARSHIL AZEEME VAL-HABIBATAY VAL-QUDRATAY VAL KIBRIYAA\’AY VAL – JABAROOT.

SUB-HAANAL MALEKIL MAQSOODAY,

SUB-HAANAL MALEKIL MOWJODAY,

SUB-HAANAL MALEKIL MA\’A-BOODAY,

SUB-HAANAL HAYYIL HAKEEM.

SUB-HAANALLAHE TAWAKKALTO ALA  HAYYIL LAZI LA-YAMOOT.

SUBBOOHUN QUDDOOSUN RABBUL MALAAEKATAY VAR-ROOHE LA-ILAHA ILLAL-LAHO VAHDAHOO LA-SHARIKA LAHOO VA-LAHUL MULKO VA-LAHUL HAMDO VA-HUVA ALA KOOLLE SHAI\’IN QADEER.

YA ALLAHO YA RAHMANO YA RAHIMO YA HAYYO YA QAYYOMMO YA ZAL- JALAALAY VAL-IKRAAMAY YA NOORAS-SAMAAVATAY VAL-ARZAY YA LA-ILAHA ILLA ANTA ALAIKA TAWAKKALTO VA-ANTA RABBUL ARSHIL-AZEEM.

ALLA-HUMMAGHFIRLI BE-HURMATAY HAAZEHIL ASMAA\’AY VASRIF ANNI ZAR-RAA\’AY VAL-BALAA\’AY VAL-HOMOOMAY VAL-GHOMOOMAY VA-JAMEELI\’L AAFAATAY, VA-MIN AVLAADI VA-AABAAI VA-UMMA-HAATI VA-AQREBAA\’I VA-ASHIRATI FA-INNA ALAIKA FE JAMEE\’IL OMOORAY I\’ATEMAADI.

VAS-SALAATO VAS-SALAAMO ALA KHAIRAY KHALQEHI MOHAMMADIN VA-AALEHI AJMA\’EENA BE-RAHMATEKA YA AR-HAMAR RAAHEMEEN. …
    </string>




<string name="duaeyasthasheer">
 Ibna tawus in his book Muhaj al Dawat and Kafami in his book Misbah narrate this dua\’a on the authority of Imam Ali ibna abi Talib who learned it from the Holy Prophet.\n
The Holy Prophet advised him to recite this dua\’a regularly, whether in prosperity or poverty, till death, because it unveils the secretes of creation and divine strategy.\n
Words can not describe its merits. Intelligent can not describe its meanings. No sooner someone begins to recite it, Almighty Allah send blessings, and his mercy surrounds him, peace and tranquillity descend upon him.\n
The sound of this dua\’a moves to and from around the arsh, its direct destination. All his desired are fulfilled. His needs are taken care \nof. He gets freedom from wants and is kept safe from hardships and misfortunes. His mind opens up new dimensions of contemplation.\n
On the day of judgement he will be received by Allah with respect and honour.\n
It cures insanity if recited before a mad man.\n
It relives pain of childbirth if recited before the expectant mother.\n
It recited on forty Fridays consecutively all sins are forgiven.\n
It cures sickness and disperses sorrows. For him who recites it before going to sleep Allah appoints one thousand angels to pray for him till morning.\n
He who recites it and dies within 24 hours it treated like a martyr.\n
\n \n
     BISMILLA HIR RAHMA NIR RAHIM \n
    ALHAMDO LIL-IAHIL-IAZI LA ILAHA ILIA HOVAL-MALEKOOL-HAQQOOL-MOBEENOOL-MODABBERO, BELA VAZIRIN WA LA KHALQIN MIN IBADEHI YASTASHEEROOL\’AVVALO
GHAIRO MAVSOOFIM VAL-BAQI BA\’DA FANAA\’IL KHALQIL\’ AZIMOOR-ROBOO-BI-YATE, NOOROOS-SAMAVATE VAL\’ ARZEENA WA FATIRO HOMA WA MOBTADE.OHOMA BE-GHAIRE.
AMADIN KHALAQAHOMA WA FATAQAHOMA FATQAN FAQAMATIS-SAMA-VATO TA\’EA-TIN BE-\’ AMREHI VASTAQARRATIL.ARAZOONA BE-AV-TADEHA FAVQAL-MAAE. SOOMMA \’
ALA RABBONA FIS-SAMAVATIL\’OLA AR-RAHMANO \’ ALAL\’ARSHIS-TAVA LAHOO MA FIS-SAMAVATE WA MA FIL.ARZE WA MA BAINAHOOMA WA MA TAHTAS-SARA FA\’ANA ASH-HADO
BE-ANNAKA ANTAL-LAHOOL-AARAFE\’A LEMA VAZA\’TA WA LA VAZE\’AL-MARAFA\’TA
WA LA MO\’INNA LEMAN AZLAL-TA WA LA MOZILLA LEMAN AA.ZAZTA WA LA MANE\’AY LEMA AA\’TAITA WA LA MO\’TEEYA WA LEMA MANA.TA WA ANTAL-IAHO
LA ILAHA ILIA ANTA KOONTA IZLAM TAKOON SAMAA.OON MABNI-YATOON WA LA SHAMSOON MOZEE\’ATOON WA LA LAILOON MOOZLEMOON WA LA NAHAROON MOZI.OON WA LA BAHROON LOJJI-YOON WA
LA HABALOON RASIN WA LA NAJMOON SARIN WA LA QAMROON MOONIROON WA LA REEHOON TAHOOBBO WA LA SAHABOON YASKOBO WA LA RA\’DOON
YOOSABBEHO WA LA ROOHOON TANAFFASO WA LA TAA\’EROON YATEERO WA LA NAROON TATAVAQ-QADO WA LA MAA\’OON YATREDO KOONTA
QABLA QOOLLE SHAI\’IN WA KAV-VANTA KOOLLA SHAI\’IN WA QADARTA \’
ALA KOOLLE SHAI\’IN VAB- TADA\’TA KOOLLA SHAI\’IN WA AGHNAITA WA AFQARTA WA AMATTA WA AHAITA WA AZHAKTA
WA ABKAITA WA \’ ALAL\’ARSHISH-TAVAITA FATABA-RAKTA YA ALLAHO WA TA\’ALAITA ANTAL-IAHOOL-LAZI LA ILAHA ILIA ANTAL-KHALLAQOOL-MO.EENO AMROKA GHALIBOON WA ILMOKA NAFEZOON WA KAIDOKA GHARIBOON WA VA\’DOKA
SADEQOON WA QAVLOKA HAQQOON WA HOOKMOKA \’ ADROON WA KALAMOKA HOODAN WA VAH-YOKA NOOROON WA RAH-MATOKA VASE\’ATOON WA \’ AFVOKA \’ AZIMOON WA FAZLOKA KASEEROON WA .ATAA\’OKA JAZEELOON WA HABLOKA MATEE-
NOON WA IMKANOKA \’ ATIDOON WA JAROKA \’ AZIZOON WA BASOKA SHADEEDOON WA MAKROKA MAKEEDOON
ANTA YA RABBE MAVZE\’O KOOLLE SHAKVA WA HAZERO KOOLLE MALA\’IN WA SHAHIDO KOOLLE NAJVA MOONTAHA KOOLLE HAJATIN
MOFARREJO KOOLLE HOOZNIN GHENA KOOLLE MIS-KEENIN HISNO KOOLLE HAREBIN AMANO KOOLLE KHAA\’EFIL
HIRZOOZ-ZO\’AFAA\’E KANZOOL-FOQARAA\’AY MOFARREJO LAGH-GHAMAA\’AY MO\’EENOOS SALEHEENA ZALEKAL-LAHO ROBBONA LA ILAHA ILIA HOVA TAKFEE MIN
\’IBADEKA MAN TAVAK-KALA, ALAIKA WA ANTA JARR, MAN LA ZABEKA WA TAZARRA\’A ILAIKA \’ISMATO MAN\’ETA~;AMA BEKA NASIRO MANIN- TASARA
BEKA TAGHFIROOZ-ZONOOBA LEMANIS-TAGH-FARAKA JAB-BAROOL-JABABERATE AZIMOOL\’ OZAMAA\’AY KABIROOL-KOBA-RAA\’AY SAYYEDOOS-SADATE MAVLAL-MAVALI SAREEKHOOL-MOOSTAS-REKHEENA MONAFFESOON ANIL-MAKROOBEENA MOJEEBO DA\’VATIL-MOZTARREENA ASMA\’OOS-SAME\’EENA ABSAROON-NAZEREENA AHKAMOOL-HAKEMEENA ASRA\’ 001-
H ASEBEENA AR- HAMAR- RAHEMEENA KHA IROOL \’ GHAFEREENA QAZI HAVAA\’EJIL-MO\’MENEENA MOGHEESOOS-SALEHEENA ANTAL-IAHO LA ILAHA ILIA ANTA RABBOOL\’ ALAMEENA ANTA\’-
KHALIQO WA ANAL-MAKHLOOQO WA ANTAL-MALIKO WA ANAL-MAMLOOKO WA ANTAR-RABBO WA ANA\’-\’ABDO WA ANTAR-RAZIQO WA ANAL-MAFZOOQO WA ANTAL-MO\’TEE WA
ANAS-SAA\’ELO WA ANTAL-JAWADO WA ANAL-BAKHEE\’O WA ANTAL-QAVI-YO WA ANAZ-ZA\’EEFO WA ANTAL-\’
AZIZO WA ANAZ-ZALEELO WA ANTAL-GHANIYO WA ANAL-FAQIRO WA ANTAS-SAYYEDO WA ANAL-ABDO WA ANTAL-GHAFIRO WA ANAL-MOSEEO WA ANTAL-ALIMO WA ANAL-JAHILO
WA ANTAL-HAKEEMO WA ANAL-\’AJOOLO WA ANTAR-RAHMANO WA-ANAL-MARHOOMO WA ANTAL-MO\’AAFEE WA ANAL-MOOBTALA WA ANTAL-MOJEEBO
WA ANAL-MOOZTARRO WA ANA-ASH-HAD BE\’ ANNAKA ANTAL-IAHO LA ILAHA ILIA ANTAL-MO\’TEE. IBADEKA BELA SAVALIN WA ASH-HADO BE-ANNEKA ANTAL-LAHOOL-VAHIDOOL. AHADOOL -MOOTAFARREDOOS -SAMADOOL-
FARDO WA ILAIKAL-MASEERO WA SAL-IAL-IAHO .ALA MOHAMMADIN WA AHLE BAITEHIT-TAYYEBEENAT- TAHEREENA VAGH-FIRLI ZONOOBI VASTOOR \’ ALYYA OYOOBI VAFTAH-IEE
MIN LADOONKA RAHMATAN WA RIZQAN VASE.AN YA AR-HAMAR-RAHEMEENA VAL-HAMDO LIL-IAHE RABBIL\’ ALAMEENAHASBONAL-IAHO WA NE\’MAL-VAKEELO WA LA HOVLA WA LA
QOOVATA ILIA BILLAHIL. ALI-YIL\’ AZIM.
ALLAHOOMMA SALLE ALAA MOHAMMADIN WA AALEMOHAMMAD.
</string>


<string name="duaetawassul">
Shaykh Tusi says, in his book Misbah, that imam Hassan bin Ali Al Askari wrote this dua\’a for Abu Muhammad who requested him to teach him the proper way of reciting salawat. Allama Majlisi has mentioned this dua\’a on the authority of Ibn babawayh who confidently says that there is no difficulty or problem that this dua\’a does not solve.\n
The merciful Allah is beseeched in the name of and for the sake of the Holy prophet and his Ahl ul Bayt.\n
It is known as "quick-fulfillment-of-all-legitimate-desires" dua\’a.\n \n


     BISMILLA HIR RAHMA NIR RAHIM \n
    ALLAHOOMMA INNI AS\’ALOKA WA ATAVAJ-JAHO LLAIKA BE NABI-YYEKA NABI-YYIR RAHMATE MOHAMMADIN SAL-LAL-LAHO \’ALAIHE WA AALEHI YA ABAL-OASIME YA RASOOLAL-LAHE YA IMAMAR-RAHMATE YA SAYYEDANA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA\’NA WA TAVAS-SALNA BEKA ILAL-IAHE WA QADDAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN INDAL-IAHESH-FA.LANA INDAL-IAH.
YA ABAL-HASANE YA AMEERUL MO\’MINEENA YA ALI-YYABNA ABI TALIB YA HOOJJATAL-IAHE ALA KHALQEHI YA SAIYYEDANA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VASTASH-FA.NA WA TAVAS-SALNA BEKA I,AL LAHE WA QADDAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN .LNDAL-IAHE ISHFA.LANA INDALLAH
YA FATEMATUZ ZEHRO. YA BINTE MOHAMMADIN YAQOORRATA .AINIR-RASOOLE YA SAIYYEDATANA WA MAVLA. TANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA.NA WA TAVAS-SALNA BEKA ILAL-IAHE WA QADDAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJI HETAN .LNDAL-IAHEISH-FA.EE LANA .INDALLAHE.
YA ABA MOHAMMADIN YA HASSANABNA .ALIYYIN AYYO-HAL MOOJTABA YABNA RASOOLIL-LAHE YA HOOJJATAL-IAHE .ALA KHALQEHI YA SAIYYEDANA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA.NA WA TAVAS-SALNA BEKA LLAL-LAHE  WA QADDAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN \’INDAL-IAHEISH-FA\’LANA \’INDAL-IAHE,
YA ABA \’ ABDIL-LAHE YA HUSAINABNA \’ ALI-YYIN AYYOHASH SHAHEEDO YABNA RASOOLIL-LAHE YA HOOJJATAL-LAHE \’ ALA KHALQEHI YA SAIYYEDANA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA\’NA WA TAVAS-SALNA BEKA LLAL-IAHE WA QADAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN IN-DAL-IAHEISH-FA\’LANA \’INDAL-IAH
YA ABAL-HASANE YA \’ALI YABNAL-HUSAINE YA ZAINAL\’ABEDEENA YABNA RASOOLIL-LAHE YA HOOJJATAL-LAHE \’ ALA KHALQEHI YA SAIYYEDANA WA MAVFANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA\’NA WA TAVAS-SAFNA BEKA L\’AL-IAHE WAQADAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN \’INDAL-LAHEISH-FA\’LANA \’INDAL-IAH.
YA ABA JA\’FARIN YA MOHAMMADABNA \’ ALIYYIN AYYOHAL-BAQERCL YABNA RASOOLIL-LAHE YA HOOJJATAL-LAHE \’ ALA KHALQEHI YA SAYYEDANA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA\’NA WA TAVAS-SAFNA BEKA ILAL-IAHE WA QADDAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN INDAF-IAHEISH-FA\’LANA \’INDAL-IAH.
YA ABA \’ ABDIL-LAHE YA JA\’FARABNA MOHAMMADIN AYYOHAS-SADIQO YABNA RASOOLIL-LAHE YA HOOJJATAL-LAHE \’ ALA KHALQEHI YA SAYYEDANA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA\’NA WA TAVAS-SALNA BEKA ILAL-IAHE WAQADAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN \’INDAL-LAHEISH-FA\’LANA \’INDAL-IAH
YA ABAL-HASANE YA MOOSABNA JA\’FARIN AYYOHAL-KAZIMO YABNA RASOOLIL-LAHE YA HOOJJATAF-LAHE \’ AFA KHALQEHI YA SAYYEDANA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA\’NA WATAVAS-SALNA BEKA ILAL-IAHE WA QADDAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN \’INDAF.LAHEISH-FA.LANA \’INDAL.FAH.
YA ABAL-HASANE YA \’ ALI-YYABNA MOOSA AYYOHAR-RIZA YABNA RASOOLIL-LAHE YA HOOJJATAL.FAHE , FT.LA KHALQEHI YA SAYYEDNA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA\’NA WA TAVAS-SALNA BEKA ILAL-LAHE WA QADDAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN \’JNDAL-IAHEISH-FA\’LANA \’INDAL-IAH.
YA ABA JA\’FARIN YA MOHAMMADABNA \’ ALI-YYIN AYYOHAT-TAQI-YOOL JAVADO YABNA RASOOLIL-LAHE YA HOOJJATAL-LAHE \’ ALA KHALQEHI YA SAYYEDNA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA\’NA WA TAVAS-SALNA BEKA ILA-IAHE WA OADAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN \’INDAL.LAHEISH-FA\’LANA \’INDAL-IAH.
YA ABAL-HASANE YA , ALI-YYABNA MOHAMMADIN AYYOHAL-HADIYIN NAQIYYO YABNA RASOOLIL-LAHE YA HOOJJATAL-LAHE \’ ALA KHALQEHIYA SAYYEDANA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA\’NA WA TAVAS-SALNA BEKA ILAL-IAHE WA OADAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN \’INDAL-IAHEISH-FA\’LANA \’INDAL-IAH.
 YA ABA MOHAMMADIN YA HASANABNA ALIYYIN AYYOHAZ-ZAKI-YOOL-ASKARIYYO YABNA RASOOLIL-LAHE YA HOJJATAL-IAHE \’ ALA KHALQEHI YA SAYYEDANA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VASTASH-FA\’NA WA TAVAS-SALNA BEKA LLAL-IAHE WA OADDAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN \’INDAL-LAHEISH-FA\’LANA \’INDAF-IAH.
 YA VASI-YYAL.HASANE VAL-KHALAFAL-HOOJJATA AYYOHAL-OAA \’ EMOOL- MOONTAZAROOL- MAHDIYYO YABNA RASOOLIL-LAHE YA HOOJATAL-IAHE \’ ALA KHALQEHI YA SAYYEDANA WA MAVLANA INNA TAVAJ-JAHNA VAS-TASH-FA\’ANA WA TAVAS-SALNA BEKA L\’AL-IAHE WA OADDAMNAKA BAINA YADAI HAJATENA YA VAJIHAN \’INDAL-IAHEISH-FA\’JANA \’INDAL-IAH :
YA SADATI WA MAVALIYYA INNI TAVAJ-JAHTO BEKOOM A\’IMATI WA \’OODDATI LE-YAVME FAQRI WA HAJATI LLAL-LAHE WA TAVAS-SALTO BEKOOM ILLA-LAHE, VAS-TAS-FA\’TO BEKOOM LLAL-LAHE, FASH-FA\’OOLEE INDAL-LAHE, VASTANQWZOONI MIN ZONOOBI \’IDAL-LAHE, FA-INNAKOOM VASILATI LLAL-LAHE WA BE-HOOBBEKOOM WA BE-QOORBE-KOOM ARJOO NAJATAN MINAL-LAHE FAKOOMOO \’INDAL-LAHE RAJAA\’EE YA SADATI YA AVLIYAA\’ALLAHE SAL-LA-LAHO \’ALAIHIM AJMA\’EEN WA LA\’ANAL-LAHO A\’DALL-\’ALLAHE ZALEMEEHIM MINAL-AV-VALEENA VAL-AKHER-\’EENA AMEEN RABBAL\’ALAMEEN.
 ALLAHOOMMA SALE ALAA MOHAMMADIN WA ALE MOHAMMED.


</string>

<string name="duaeahad">
     BISMILLA HIR RAHMA NIR RAHIM \n
    ALLAHUMMA RABBAN-NOORIL ADHWEEMI WA RABBAL QURSIYYIR-RAFEE\’I WA RABBIL BAHRIL MASJOORI WA MUNZILAT-TAWRAATI WAL INJEELI WAZ-ZABOORI, WA RABBADH-DHILLI WAL HAROORI, WA MUNZILAL QUR\’AANIL ADHWEEMI WA RABBAL MALAAIKATIL MUQARRABEEN WAL AMBIYAAI WAL MURSALEEN. ALLAAHUMMA INNEE AS\’ ALUKA BI WAJ\’HIKAL KAREEM WA BI NOORI WAJHIKAL MUNEERI
    WA MULKIKAL QADEEMI YAA HAYYU YAA QAYYOOMU AS\’ALUKA BISMIKAL-LADHEE ASHRAKAT BIHIS-SAMAAWAATU WAL ARDHOONA WA BISMIKAL-LADHEE YASLAHU BIHIL AWWALOON WAL AAKHIROON YAA HAYYAN QABLA KULLI HAYYIN WA YAA HAYYAN BA\’ADA KULLI HAYYIN WA YAA HAYYAN HEENA LAA HAYYA YAA MUHYIYAL MAWTA WA
    MUMEETATAL AHYAA\’I YAA HAYYU LAA ILAAHA ILLA ANTA . ALLAAHUMMA BALLIGH MAWLAANAL IMAAMAL HAADIYAL MAHDIYYAL QAAIMA BI AMRIKA SWALAWAATULLAAHI ALAYHI WA ALAA AABAAIHIT-TWAAHIREEN AN JAMEE\’IL MU\’MINEENA WAL MU\’MINAATI FI MASHAARIKIL ARDHI WA MAGHAARIBIHAA, SAHLIHAA WA JABALIHAA,
    BARRIHAA WA BAHRIHAA, WA ANNEE WA AN WAALIDAYYA, MINAS-SWALAWAATI ZINATA ARSHILLAAHI WA MIDAADA KALIMAATIHI, WAMAA AHSWAAHU ILMUHU WA AHAATWA BIHI KITAABUHU, ALLAAHUMMA INNEE UJADDIDU LAHOO FI SWABEEHATI YAWMI HAADHA, WAMAA ISHTU MIN AYYAAMI, AHDAN WA AQDAN WA BAY\’ATAN LAHU FI UNUQEE LAA AHOOLU ANHA WALAA AZOOLU ABADAN. ALLAAHUMMAJ\’ALNEE
    MINANSWAAARIHI WA A\’AWAANIHI WADH-DHAABBEENA ANHU, WAL MUSAARI\’EENA ILAYHI FI QADHAAI HAWAAIJIHI WAL MUM\’TATHILEENA LI AWAAMIRIHI WAL MUHAA-MEENA ANHU, WAS-SAABIQEENA ILAA IRAADATIHI WAL MUSTASH\’HADEENA BAYNA YADAYHI. ALLAAHUMMA IN HAALA BAYNI WA BAYNAHUL MAWTUL-LADHEE JA\’ALTAHU ALAA IBAADIK HATMAN MAQDHIYYAN,
    FA AKHRIJNI MIN QABREE MU\’TAZIRAN, KAFANEE SHAAHIRAN, SWAYFEE MUJARRIDAN, QANAATEE MULABBIYAN, DA\’AWATAD-DAAII FIL HAADHIRI WAL BAADEE. ALLAAHUMA ARINIT-TWAL\’ATAR-RASHEEDATA, WAL GHURRATAL HAMEEDATA, WAQHUL NAADHIRI BI NADHRATIN MINNEE
    ILAYHI, WA AJJIL FARAJAHU,WA SAHHIL MAKHRAJAHU, WA AWSI\’A MAN\’HAJAHU, WA ANFIDH AMRAHU, WASHDUD AZRAHU WA\’MURILLAA-HUMMA BIHI BILAADAK, WA AHYI BIHI IBAADAK, FA INNAKA QULTA WA QAWLUKAL HAQQU
    DHWAHRAL FASAADU FIL BARRI WAL BAHRI, BIMAA KASABAT AYDINNAASI, FA AZHIRI-LLAAHUMMA LANAA WALIYYIK BINTI NABIYYIKAL MUSAMMA, BISMI RASOOLIK, HATTAA LAA YADHFARA BI SHAY\’IN MINAL BAATWILI ILLAA MAZZAQAHU, WA YUHIQQAL HAQQA, WA YUHAQQIQAHU WAJ\’ALHU ALLAAHUMMA MAFZA\’AN LI MADHLOOMI IBAADIK WA
    NAASWIRAN LIMAN LAA YAJIDU LAHU NAASWIRAN GHAYRAK, WA MUJADDIDAN LIMA UTTWILA MIN AHKAAMI KITAABIK, WA MUSHAYYIDAN LIMAA WARADA MIN A\’ALAAMI DEENIK,WA SUNANI NABIYYIK SWALLALLAAHU ALAYHI WA AALIHI WAJ\’ALHU . ALLAAHUMMA MIMMAN HASSWANTAHU MIN BA\’ASIL MU\’TADEEN,
    ALLAAHUMMA WA SURRA NABIYYIK MUHAMMADIN SWALLALLAAHU ALAYHI WA AALIHI, BI RU\’AYATIHI WAMAN TABIAHU ALAA DA\’AWATIHI, WARHAMISTIKAANTINA BA\’ADAHU, ALLAAHUMAKSHIF
    HAADHIHIL GHUMMATA AN HAADHIHIL UMMATAI, BI HUDHOORIHI WA AJJIL LANAA DHUHOORAHU, INNAHUM YARAWNAHU BAEEDAN WA NARAAHU QAREEBAN BI RAHMATIK YAA ARHAMAR-RAAHIMEEN.\n
THEN SAY 3 TIMES:\n
AL-AJAL AL-AJAL YAA SWAAHIBUZZAMAAN, - EACH TIME STRIKING SLOWLY YOUR RIGHT HAND ON THE THIGH.

</string>

    <string name="duaesamaat">

Shaykh Tusi, Sayyid ibna Tawus and Kafami report that this dua\’a, according to Muhammad ibn Uthman Umri, a reliable represetative of Imam Sahibuz Zaman, was taught by Imam Muhammad bin Ali Al Baqir and Imam Jafar bin Muhammad Al Sadiq. Allama Majlisi says that all the pious religious scholars used to recite this dua\’a. Shaykh Kafami says that this dua\’a contains ismi azam (the great name of Allah). Imam Muhammad bin Ali Al Baqir advised the faithfuls to recite this dua\’a as it brings the downfall of the enemies of Ahl ul Bayt. Imam Jafar bin Muhammad Al Sadiq(as) said that Allah swt taught this dua\’a to prophet Musa to overcome his enemies. This dua\’a is particularly recited in the closing hours before sunset on Friday \n \n





        BISMILLA HIR RAHMA NIR RAHIM \n
ALLAHUMMA IN-NEEE AS ALUKA  BIS-MIKAL-AZ\’EEMIL-AA-Z\’AMIL-AA\’Z-ZIL AL LIL AK-RAMI
AL-LAD\’EE ID\’AA DUE\’ETA BIHI A\’LAA MAGHAALIQI AB-WAABIS-SAMAA-LILIL-FAT-H\’I BIR\’RAH\’ MATIN FATAH\’AT
WA ID\’AA DUE\’ETA BIHI A\’LAA MAZ”AAA-IQI AB- WAABIL-ARZ”I LIL-FARAJIN-FARAJAT
WA ID\’AA DUE\’ETA BIHI A\’LAAL-U\’S-RI LIL-YUS-RI TAYAS-SARAT
WA ID\’AA DUE\’ETA BIHI A\’LAAL-AM-WAATI  LIN NUSHOORIN-TASHARAT
WA ID\’AA DUE\’ETA BIHI A\’LAA KASH –FIL-BA-SAAA-I WAZ”-Z”AR-RAAA-IN-KASHAFAT
WA BIJALAALI WAJ-HIKAL-KAREEM
AK-RAM-WUJODHI WA AA\’Z-ZIL-WUJOOH
AL-LAD\’EE A\’NAT LAHUL-WUJOOH
WA KHAZ”AAT LAHUR-RIQAAB
WA KHASHAA\’T LAHUL-AS\’-WAAT
WA WAJILAT LAHUL-QULOOBU MIM-MAKHAAFATIK
WA BI-QOD-WATIKAL-LATEE BIHAA
TUM-SIKUS-SAMAAA-A AN TAQAA\’ A\’LAAL-ARZ”I  IL-LAA BID\’NIK
WA TUM-SIKUS-SAMAAATI WAL-AR-Z”A AN TAZOOLAA
WA BI-MASHEEE-ATIKAL-LATEE DAL-LAHAAL-A\’ALAMOON
WA BI-KALIMATIKAL-LATEE  KHALAQ-TA BIHAAS-SAMAAWAATI WAL-ARZ”
WA BI-KALIMATIKAL-LATEE  S\’ANA\’-TA BIHAAL-A\’JAAA-IB
WA KHALAQ-TA BIHAAZ\’ Z\’UL-MATA WA JAA\’L-TAHAA LAYLAN
WA JAA\’L-TAL-LAYLA SAKANAA
WA KHALAQ-TA BIHAAN-NOORA WA JAA\’L-TAHU NAHARAA
WA JAA\’L TAN-NAHAAARA NUSHOORAAM-MUB-S\’IRAA
WA KHALAQ-TA BIHAAL QAMARA  WA JAA\’L-TAL-QAMARA NOORAA
WA KHALAQ-TA BIHAAL QAMARA WA  JAA\’L-TASH-SHAM-SA Z”I-YAAA-A
WA KHALAQ-TA BIHAAL-QAMARA WA JAA\’L-TAL-QAMARA NOORAA
WA KHALAQ-TA BIHAAL-KAWAAKIBA WA JAA\’L TAHAA NUJOOMAAW-WA BUROOJAAW-WA MAS\’AABEEH\’A WA ZEENATAW-WA RUJOOMA
WA JAA\’L-TA LAHAA MASHAARIQA QA MAGHAARIB
WA JAA\’L TA LAHAA MAT\’AALIA WA MAJAAREE
WA JAA\’L TA LAHAA FALKAAW-WA MASAABIH\’
WA QAD-DAR-TAHAA FIS-SAMAAA-I MANAZILA FAAH\’SANTA TAQ-DEERAHAA
WA S\’AW-WAR-TAHAA FA\’AH\’-SANTA TAS\’-WEERAHA
WA AH\’ S\’AYTAHAA BI-AS-MAAA-IKA IH\’S\’AAA-AA
WA DAB-BAR-TAHAA BI H\’IK-MATIKA TAD-BEERAAW-WA AH\’-SAN-TA TAD-BEERAHAA
WA SAKH-HAR-TAHAA BI-SUL-T\’AANIL-LAYLI WA SUL-TAAN-NAHAARI WAS-SAAA\’ATI WA A\’DADIS SINEENA WAL-H\’SAAB
WA JAA\’L-TA RU-YATAHAALIJAMEEI\’N-NAASI MAR-AAW-WAAH\’IDAA
WA-AS-ALUKALLAHUMMA BIMAJ- DIKA
AL-LAD\’EE KAL-LAM-TA BIHI A\’AB-DAKA WA RASOOLAKA MOOSAB-NA I\’M-RAANA A\’LAYHIS SALAAMU FIL-MUWAD-DASEEN
FAW-QA IH\’-SAASIL KAROOBEE-YEEN
FAW-QA GHAMAAA-IMIN-NOOR
FAW-QA TAABOOTISH-SHAHAADAH
FEE A\’MOODIN-NAARI WA FEE T\’OORI SAYNAAA-A
WA FEE JABALI H\’OOREETHA FIL-WAADEEL-MUQAD-DASI FIL-BUQ-A\’TIL- MUBAARAKATI MIN JAANIBIT\’-TOORIL-AYMANI MINASH-SHAJARAH
WA FEE ARZ”I MIS\’RA BI-TIS-I\’AAA-YAATIM BAY-YINAAT
WA YAW-MA FARAQ-TA LIBANEEE IS-RAAA-EELAL-BAH\’R
WA FIL-MUM-BAJISAATIL-LATEE S\’ANA\’-TA BIHAAL- A\’JAAA-IBA FEE BAH\’-RI SOOF
WA A\’QAD-TA MAAA-AL-BAH\’RI FEE QAL-BIL-GHAM-RI KAL-H\’IJAARATI
WA JAAWAZTA BI-BANEEE IS-RAAA-EELAL-BAH\’RA WA TAMMAT KALIMATUKAL- HUS-NAA A\’LAYHIM BIMAA
S\’ABAROO WA AW-RATH-TAHUM-MASHAARIQAL-AR-Z”I WA  MAGHAA RIBAHAAL-LATEE BAARAK-TA FEEHAA LIL-A\’ALAMEEN
WA AGH-RAQ-TA FIR-A\’WNA WA JUNOODAHU WA MARAAKIBAHU FIL-YAM
WA BIS-MIKAL-A\’ZEEMIL-AA\’Z\’AMIL-AA\’ZIL-AJAL-LIL-AK-RAM
WA BIMAJ-DIKAL-LAD\’EE TAJAL-LAYTA BIHI
LI-MOOSAA KALEMIKA A\’LAYHIS-SALAAMU FEE T\’OORI SAY-NAAA-A
WA LI-IBRAAHEEMA A\’LAYHIS-SALAAMU KHALEEKA MIN QAB-LU FEE MAS-JIDIL-KHEEF
WA LI-IS-H\’AAQA S\’AFEE-YIKA A\’LAYHIS-SALAAMU FEE BI-RI SHEEI\’N
WA LI-YAA\’-QOOBA NABEE-YIKA A\’LAYHIS-SALAAMU FEE BAYTI EEL
WA AW-FAYTA LI-IB-RIAHEEMA A\’LAYHIS SALAAMU BI-MEETHAAQIK
WA LIS-H\’AAQA- BIH\’IL-FIK
WA LI-YAA\’QOOBA BISHAHADATIK
WA LIL-MU-MINEENA BIWA\’-DIKA
WA LID-DAAE\’ENA BI-AS-MAAA-IKA FAJAAB-T
WA BI-MAJ-DIKAL-LAD\’EE Z\’AHARA LI-MOOSAA IBNI I\’M-RAANA A\’LAYHIS-SALAAMU A\’LAA QUB-BATIR-RUMMAAN
WA BIAAA-YAATIKAL-LATEE WAQAAT A\’LAAA AR-Z”I MIS-RA
BI-MAJ-DI  L-I\’Z-ZATI WAL-GHALABATI
BIAAA-YAATIN A\’ZEEZAH
WA BI-SUL-T\’AANIL-QOO-WAH
WA BI-I\’Z-ZATIL-QUD-RAH
WA BI-SHA-NIL-KALIMATIT-TAAA-MMAH
WA BI-KALMAATIKAL-LATEE TAFAZ”-Z”AL-TA BIHAA A\’LAAA AHLIS- SAMAAWAATI WAL-AR-Z”I WA AHLID-DUN-YAA WA AH-LIL-AA-KHIRAH
WA BI-RAH\’-MATIKAL-LATEE MANAN-TA BIHAA A\’LAA JAMEEI\’ KHAL-QIK
WA BIS –TIT\’AAA\’TIKAL-LATEE AQAM-TA BIHAA A\’LAAL-A\’ALAMEEN
WA BI-NOORIKAL-LAD\’EE QAD KHAR-RA MIN FAZAI\’HI THOORU SAYNAAA-A
WA BI-I\’L-MIKA WA JALAALIKA WA KIB-RI- YAAA-IKA WA I\’Z-ZATIK
WA JABAROOTIKAL-LATEE LAM TAS-TAQIL-LAAHAAL-ARAZ”
WAN-KHAFAZ”AT LAHAS-SAMAAWAAT
WANZAJARA LAHAAL-U\’M-QUL-AK-BAR
WA RAKADAT LHAAAL-BIH\’AARU WAL-AN-HAAR
WA KHAZ”AAT LAHAAL-JIBAA;
WA SAKANAT LAHAAAL-AR-Z”U BI-MANAAKIBIHAA
WAS-TAS-LAMAT LAHAAL-KHALAAA-IQU KUL-LUHAA
WA KHAFAQAT LAHAAR-RIYAAH\’U FEE JARAYAANIHAA
WA KHAMADAT LAHAAN-NEERAANU FEE AW-TAANIHAA
WU BISUL-T\’AANIKAL-LAD\’EE U\’RIFAT LAKA BIHAL-GHALABATU DAH-RAD-DUHOORI WA H\’UMID-TA BIHI FIS SAMAAWAATI WAL-ARAZ”EEN
WA BIKALIMATIKA KALIMATIS\’S\’ID-QIL-LATEE SABAQAT LI-ABEENAAA AAA-DAMA A\’LAYHIS-SALAAMU WA D\’UR-REE YATIHU BIR-RAH\’-MAHWA AS-ALUKA BI-KALIMATIKAL-LATEE GHALABAT KUL-LAA SHAY
WA BI-NOORI WAJ-HIKAL-LAD\’EE TAJAL-LAYTA BIHI LIL-JABALI FAJAA\’L –TAHU DAK-KAAW-WA KHAR-RA MOOSAA S\’AI\’QAA
WA BIMAJ-DIKAL-LAD\’EE Z\’HARA A\’LAA TOORI SAY-NAAA-A FAKAL-LAM-TA BIHI A\’AB-DAKA WA RASOOLAKA MOOSAABINA I\’M-RAAN
WA BIT\’AL-ATIKA FEE SAAE\’ER
WA Z\’UHOORIKA FEE JABALI FAARAANA BI-RABAWAATIL-MUQAD-DASEENA WA JUNOODIL-MALAAA-IKATIS-S\’AAA-F-FEEN
WA KHUSOOI\’L-MALAAA-IKATIL-MUSAB-BIH\’EEN
WA BI-BARAKAATIKAL-LATEE BAARAK-TA  FEE UMMATI MUH\’AMMADIN S\’AL-LAALLAHU A\’ILAYHI WA AA-LIH
WA BAARAK-TA LI-YAA\’QOOBA IS-RAAA-EELIKA FEE UMMATI MOOSAA A\’LAY-HIMAAS-SALAAM
WA BAARAK-TA LIH\’ABEEBIKA MUH\’AMMADIN S\’AL-LAALLAHU A\’ALIHI WA AA-LIHI FEE I\’T-RATIHI WA D\’UR-REE-YATHI WA UMMATIH
ALLLAHUMMA WA KAMAA GHIB-NAA A\’N D\’AALIKA WA LAM NASH-HAD-HU WA AAA-MAN-NAA BIHI WA LAM NARAHU S\’ID-QAAAW-WA A\’D-LAA
AN TUS\’AL-LIYA A\’LAA MUH\’AMMAIW-WA AN TUBAARIKA A\’LAA MUH\’AMMADIN-WA AA-LI MUH\’AMMADIN KAAF-Z”ALI MAA S\’AL-LAYTA WA BAARAK-TA WA TARAH\’-H\’AM-TA A\’LAAA IB-RAAHEEMA WA AA-LI IB RAHEEM
IN-NAKA H\’AMEEDUM-MAJEED
FAA\’AALUL-LIMAA TUREED
WA ANTA A\’LAA KUL-LI SHAY-IN QADEERUN\n
Now express your desire and beseech Allah to fulfill it. Then recite the following\n

ALLAHUMA BIH\’AQ-QI HAD\’AAD-DUA\’AAA-I
WA BIH\’AQ-QI HAD\’IHEEL-AS-MAAA-IL-LATEE  LAA YAA\’-LAMU TAF-SEERAHAA WA-LAA TA-WEELAHAA WA-LAA YAA\’-LAMU BAAT\’INAHAA WA-LAA Z\’AAHIRAHAA GHAYRUK
S\’AL-LI A\’LAA MUH\’AMMAD WA AA-LI MUH\’AMMAD
WA AN TARZUQANEE  KHAYRAD-DUN-YAA WAL-AA-KHIRAH
WAF-A\’L BEE MAA ANTA AH-LUH
WA-LAA TAF-A\’L BEE ANA AH-LUHU
WAN-TAQIM LEE MIN
WAGH-FIR LEE MIN D\’UNOOBEE MAA TAQAD-DAMA MINHAA WA MAA TAAKH-HARA WA LI-WWAALIDAY-YA WA LI-JAMEEI\’L-MU-MINEENA WAL-MU-MINAAT
WA WAS-SIA\’ A\’LAY-YA MIN H\’ALAALI RIZQIK
WA WAS-SIA A\’LAY-YA MIN H\’ALAALI RIZQIK
WAK-FINEE MAOONATA IN-SAANI SAW-IW-WA SUL-TAANI SAW-IW-WA QAREENI SAW-IW-WA YAW-MI SAW-IW-WA SAAA\’TI SAW-IN
WAN-TAQIM LEE MIMMAY-YAKEEDUNEE WA MIMMAY-YAB-GHEE A\’LAY YA WA YUREED BEE WA BI-AH-LEE WA   AW-LAADEE WA IKH-WAANEE WA JEERAANEE WA QARAABAATEE MINAL-MU-MINEENA WAL-MU-MINAATI Z\’UL-MAA
IN-NAKA A\’LAA MAA TASHAAA-U QADEER
WA BIKUL-LI SHAY-IN A\’LEEM
AA-MEEN RAB- BAL-A\’ALAMEEN
ALLAHUMMA BIH\’AQ-QI HAD\’AAD-DUA\’AAA-I TAFAZ”-Z” AL
A\’LAA FUQARAAA-IL-MUMINEENA WAL-MUYMINAATI BIL-GHINAA WATH-THAR-WAH
WA A\’LAA MAR-Z”AAL –MU-MINAATI BISH-SHIFAAA-I WAS\’SIH\’H\’AH
WA A\’LAA AH\’YAAA-IL-MUMINEENA WAL-KARAAMAH
WA A\’LAA AM-WAATIL-MU-MINAATI  BIL-MAGH-FIRATI WAR-RAH\’-MAH
WA A\’LAA MUSAAFIREEL-MUMINEENA WAL-MU-MINAATI BIR-RAD-DI ILAAA AW-T\’AANIHIM SAALIMEENA GHAANIMEEN
BI-RAH\’-MATIKA YAAA AR-H\’AMAR-RAAH\’IMEEN
WA S\’AL-LAALLAHU A\’LAA SAY-YIDINAA MUH\’AMMADIN KHATAMIN-NABEE-YEENA WA I\’T-RATIHIT-TAAHIREENA WASAL-LAMA TAS-LEEMAN KATHEERAA
    </string>

    <string name="duaemashlool">
         BISMILLA HIR RAHMA NIR RAHIM \n
ALLAAHUMMA INNI AS-ALOKA BISMEKA BIS-MILLAHIR RAH\’MAANIR RAH\’EEM YAA D\’AL JAALALE WAL IKARAAME YAA H\’AYYO YAA QAYYOOMO YAA H\’AYYO LAA ILAAHA ILLA ANTA YAA HUWA YAAMANL LAA YA\’LAMO MAA HUWA WALAA KAIFA HUWA WALAA AINA HUWA WALAA H\’AITHO HUWA ILLA HUWA YAA D\’AL MULKE WAL MALAAKOOTE YAD\’AL I\’ZZATE WAL JABA ROOTE YAA MALEKU YAA QUDOO SO YAA SALAAMO YAA MO-MINO YAA MUHAI MENO YAA A\’ZEEZO YAA JABBAARO YAA MUTAKAB BERO YAA KHAALEQO YAA BAAREYO YAA MUSAW WERO YAA MO FEEDO YAA MUDAB BERO YAA SHADEEDO YAA MUB DEO\’ YAA MOE\’EDO YAA MOBEE DO YAA WADOODO YAA MAH\’ MOODO YAA MA\’ BOO DO YAA BAE\’EDO YAA QAREEBO YAA MOJEE BO YAA RAQEEBO YAA H\’ASEEBO YAA BA DEE\’O YAA RAFEE\’O YAA MANEE\’O YAA SA MEE\’O YAA A\’LEEMO YAA H\’ALEEMO YAA KA REEMO YAA H\’AKEEMO YAA QADEEMO YAA A\’LIYYO YAA A\’Z\’EEMO YAA H\’ANNAANO YAA MANNAANO YAA DAY YAANO YAA MUSTA\’ AANO YAA JALEELO YAA JAMEELO YAA WAKEELO YAA KAFEELO YAA MO QEELO YAA MONEELO YAA NABEELO YAA DA LEELO YAA HAADI YAA BAADI YAA AWWALO YAA AAKHERO YAA Z\’AAHERO YAA BAA T\’ENO YAA QAAEMO YAA DAEMO YAA A\’A LEMO YAA H\’AA KEMO YAA QAAZ"I YAA A\’ADELO YAA FAAS\’ELO YAA WAAS\’ELO YAA T\’AA HERO YAA MUT\’AH HERO YAA QAADERO YAA MUQTADERO YAA KABEERO YAA MUTA KABBERO YAA WAAHE DO YAA AH\’ADO YAA S\’AMADO YAA MANL LAM YALID WALAM YOO LAD WALAM YAKULLAHU KUFOWAN AH\’ADON WA LAM YAKUL LAHU S\’AAHEBATON WALAA KAANA MAA\’AHO WA ZEERUN WALAT TAKHA D\’A MAA\’AHO MUSHEE RAN WA LAH\’TAAJA ILA Z\’AHEERIN WALA KAA NA MAA\’AHO MIN ELA AHIN GHAIROHO LAA ELAAHA ILLA ANTA FATA A\’ALAITA A\’AMMA YAQOOLUZ\’ Z\’AALEMOO NA O\’LUWWAN KABEE RA YAA A\’LIYYO YAA SHAAMEKHO YAA BAA D\’EKHO YAA FATTAA H\’O YAA NAFFAAH\’O YAA MURTAAH\’O YAA MOFAR REJO YAA NAAS\’E RO YAA MUNTAS\’ERO YAA MUDREKO YAA MUHLE KO YAA MUNTAQE MO YAA BAA\’ETHO YAA WAARETHO YAA T\’AALE BO YAA GHAALEBO YAA MANLLA YAFOOTOHU HAAREBUN YAA TAW WAABO YAA AWWAABO YAA WAH HAABO YAA MOSAB BEBAL ASBAA BE YAA MOFATTEHAL ABWAABE YAA MAN H\’AITHO MAA DO\’EYA AJAABA YA T\’AHOORO YAA SHAKOORO YAA A\’FOO-O YAA GHAFOORO YAA NOORAN NOORE YAA MODABBERAL UMOORE YAA LAT\’EEFO YAA KHABEERO YAA MOJEERO YAA MONEE RO YAA BAS\’EERO YAA Z\’AHEERO YAA KABEE RO YAA WITRO YAA FARDO YAA ABADO YAA SANADO YAA S\’AMADO YAA KAAFI YAA
        SHAAFI YAA WAAFI YAA MOA\’AFI YAA MOHSINO YAA MUJMELO YAA MUN E\’MO YAA MUFZ\’ELO YAA MUTA KARREMO YAA MUTAFAR REDO YAA MAN A\’LAA FAQAHARA YAA MAN MALAKA FAQADARA YAA MAN BAT\’ANA FA KHABARA YAA MAN O\’BEDA FASHAKARA YAA MAN U\’S\’EYA FAGHAFARA YAA MAN LAA TAH\’WEEHIL FEKARO WALA YUDREKOHO BAS\’ARUN WALAA YAKHFA A\’LAIHE ATHA RUN YAA RAAZEQAL BASHARE YAA MUKAD DERA KULLE QADARIN YAA A\’ALEYAL MAKAANI YAA SHADEEDAL ARKAA NE YAA MOBADDELAZ\’ Z\’AMAANE YAA QAA BELAL QURBANE YAA D\’AL MANNE WAL EH\’SAANE YAD\’AL I\’Z ZATE WASSULT\’AANE YAA RAH\’EEMO YAA RAH\’MAANO YAA MAN HUWA KULLA YAUMIN FEE SHA-NIN YAA MAN LAA YASHGHALOHU SHAANUN A\’N SHA-NIN YAA A\’Z\’EE MASH SHA-NE YAA MAN HOWA BEKULLE MAKAA NIN YAA SAAMEA\’AL AS\’WAATE YAA MUJEE BAD DAA\’A-WAATE YAA MUNJEH\’AT\’ T\’ALEBAATE YAA QAAZ"EYAL H\’AA JAATE YAA MUNZELAL BARAKAATE YAA RAA H\’EMAL A\’BARAATE YAA MO QEELAL A\’THA RAATE YAA KAASHEFAL KORO-BAATE YAA WALIY YAL H\’ASANAATE YAA RAAFEA\’D DARAJAATE YAA MO-TEYAS SO-LAATE YAA MOH\’YEYAL AMWAATE YAA JAA MEA\’ASH SHATAATE YAA MUT\’T\’ALEA\’N A\’LAN NIYAATE YAA RAADDA MAAQAD FAATA YAA MAN LAA TASH TABEHO A\’LAIHIL AS\’WAATO YAA MAN LAA TUZ" JEROHUL MAS-ALAATO WALAA TAGH SHAAHUZ\’ Z\’OLO-MAATO YAA NOORAL ARZ"E WAS SAMAA WAATE YAA SAABE GHAN NEA\’AME YAA DAAFEA\’N NEQAME YAA BAAREAN NA SAME YAA JAAMEA\’L OMA ME YAA SHAAFIYAS SAQAME YAA KHAALEQAL NOORE WAZ\’Z\’OLAME YAD\’AL JOODE WAL KARAME YAA MAN LAA YAT\’A-O A\’RSHAHO QADAMUN YAA AJWADAL AJWADEENA YAA AKRAMAL AKRAMEENA YAA ASMA-A\’S SAAMEE\’ENA YAA ABS\’ARAN NAA Z\’EREENA YAA JAA RAL MUSTAJEEREENA YAA AMAANAL KHAA EFEENA YAA Z\’AHRAL LAA JEENA YAA WALIY-YAL MO-MENEENA YAA GHA YAATHAL MUSTAGHE THEENA YAA GHAA YATAT T\’AA-LEBEENA YAA S\’AAH\’EBA KULLE GHAREEBIN YAA MO-NESA KULLE WAH\’EEDIN YAA MALJA-A KULLE T\’AREEDIN YAA MA-WAA KULLE SHAREEDIN YAA H\’AAFEZ\’A KULLE Z"AAALLATIN YAA RAAH\’EMASH SHAYKHIL KABEERE YAA RAAZEQAT T\’IFLIS\’ S\’A-GHEERE YAA JAABERAL A\’Z\’MIL KASEERE YAA FAAKKA KULLE ASEERIN YAA MUGHNEYAL BAAAESIL FAQEERE YAA I\’S\’MATAL KHAAEFIL MUSTAJEERE YAA MAN LAHUT TADBEERO WATTAQ DEERO YAA MANIL A\’SEERO A\’LAIHE SAHLUN YASEERO YAA MAN LAA YAH\’TAAJO ELAA TAFSEERIN YAA MAN HOWA A\’LAA KULLE SHAYYIN QADEERUN YAA MAN HOWA BE-KULLE
        SHAYYIN KHABEE RUN YAA MAN HOWA BEKULLE SHAYYIN BA S\’EERUN YAA MURSELAR REYAH\’E YAA FAALEQAL IS\’BAH\’E YAA BAA\’ ETHAL ARWAH\’E YAD\’AL JOODE WAS SAMAAH\’E YAA MAN BE YADEHI KULLO MIFTAAH\’IN YAA SAAMEA\’A KULLE S\’AWTIN YAA SAABEQA KULLE FAUTIN YAA MUH\’YEYAA KULLE NAFSIN BA\’DAL MAUTE YAA U\’DDATI FEE SHIDDATI YAA HAA FEZ\’I FEE GHURBATI YAA MOONESI FEE WAH\’ DATI YAA WALIYYI FEE NE\’MATI YAA KAHFI H\’EENA TOE\’EENIL MAD\’AA HEBO WATO SAL-LEMONIL AQAAREBO WA YAKHD\’OLONI KULLO S\’AAHEBIN YAA I\’MAA DA MANLLA I\’MAADA LAHU YAA SANADA MAN LAA SANADA LAHU YAA D\’UKHRA MAN LAA D\’UKHRA LAHU YAA H\’IRZA MAN LAA H\’IRZA LAHU YAA KAHFA MAN LAA KAHFA LAHU YAA KANZA MAN LAA KANZA LAHU YAA RUKNA MAN LAA RUKNA LAHU YAA GHEYAATHA MAN LAA GHEYAATHA LAHU YAA JAARA MAN LAA JAARA LAHU YAA JAAREYAL LAS\’EEQA YAA RUKNEYAL WATHEEQA YAA ELAAHI BITTAH\’-QEEQE YAA RABBAL BAITIL ATEEQE YAA SHAFEEQO YAA RAFEEQO FUKKANI MIN H\’ALAQIL MAZ"EEQE WAS\’RIF A\’NNI KULLA HAMMIN WAGHAMMIN WAZ"EE QIN WAKFENI SHARRA MAALA OT\’EE QO WA A-I\’NNI A\’LAA MAA OT\’EEQO YARAAD DA YOOSOFA A\’LAA YA\’QOO BA YAA KAASHEFA Z"URRE AYYOOBA YAA GHAAFERAD\’ D\’AN-BE DAO\’OUDA YAA RAAFE A\’A I\’ESABNE MARYA MA WA MUNJEYAHU MIN AEDIL YAHOODE YAA MUJEEBA NIDAA-E YOONOSA FIZ\’ Z\’OLOMAA TE YAA MUST\’AFEA MOOSA BEL KALEMAATE YAA MAN GHAFARA LE AADAMA KHAT\’EE-ATAHU WARA FAA\’A IDREESA MAKAA NAN A\’LIYYAN BE RAH\’ MA-TEHI YAA MAN NAJAA NOOH\’AN MINAL GHARAQE YAA MAN AHLAKA A\’ADANIL OOLA WA THAMOODA FAMAA ABQA WAQAUMA NOO H\’IN MIN QABLO INNA HUM KAANOO HUM AZ\’LAMA WA AT\’GHAA WAL MO-TAFEKATE AHWA YAA MAN DAM MARA A\’LAA QAUME LOOT\’IN WADAMDAMA A\’LAA QAUME SHUAE\’BIN YAA MANIT TA KHAD\’A IBRAHEEMA KHALEELAN YAA MAINIT TAKHAD\’A MOOSA KALEEMAN WAT-TA KHAD\’A MUH\’AM MADAN S\’ALLAAHO A\’LAIHE WA AALEHI WA A\’LAIHIM AJMA\’EENA H\’ABEE BAN YAA MO-TEYA LUQMAANAL H\’IK MATA WAL WAAHEBA LESU LAIMAANA MUL KAN LAA YAMBAGHI LE AH\’A DIN MIN BA\’DEHE YAA MAN NAS\’ARA D\’AL QARNAINE A\’LAL MOLOO KIL JABAABERATE YAA MAN AA\’T\’AL KHIZ\’RAL H\’AYAATA WARADDA LE YOOSHAA\’ ABNE NOO NISH SHAMSA BA\’DA GHUROOBEHA YAA MAN RABAT\’A A\’LAA QALBE UMME MOOSA WA AH\’S\’ANA FARJA MARYAMAB NATE I\’M RAANA YAA MAN H\’AS\’S\’ANA YAH\’YABNA ZAKARIYYA MENAD\’ D\’ANBE WASAKKANA A\’N MOOSAL GHAZ"ABA YAA MAN BASHSHARA ZAKARIYYA
        BEYAH\’YA YAA MAN FADAA ISMAE\’ELA MINAD\’ D\’ABH\’E BEDI\’BH\’IN A\’Z\’EEMIN YAA MAN QABELA QURBAANA HAABEELA WA JA\’ALAL LA\’ANATA A\’LA QAA BEELA YAA HAZEMAL AH\’ZAABE LE MUH\’AM MADIN S\’ALLAL-LAAHO A\’LAIHE WA AALEHI S\’ALLE A\’LAA MUH\’AM MADIN WA AALE MUH\’AMMADIN WA A\’LA JAMEEI\’L MURSA LEENA WA MALAA EKATEKAL MUQAR RABEENA WA AHLE T\’AA\’ATEKA AJMAE\’ENA WA AS- ALOKA BEKULLE MAS-ALATIN SA-LAKA BEHA AH\’ADUN MIMMAN RAZ"EE TAA\’NHO FA H\’ATAMTA LAHU A\’LAL IJAABATE YAA ALLAAHO YAA ALLAAHO YAA ALLAAHO YAA RAH\’ MAANO YAA RAH\’MAA NO YAA RAH\’MAANO YAA RAH\’EEMO YAA RAH\’EE MO YAA RAHEE MO YAA D\’AL JALAALE WAL EKRAAME YAA D\’AL JALAALE WAL EKRAAME YAA D\’AL JALAALE WAL EKRAAME BEHI BEHI BEHI BEHI BEHI BEHI BEHI AS ALOKA BEKULLISMIN SAM MAI TA BEHI NAFSAKA AW ANZAL TAHO FEE SHAYYIN MIN KOTU BEKA AWIS TA-ATHARTA BEHI FEE I\’LMIL GHAIBE I\’NKDAKA WA-BE MA-A\’AQEDIL I\’ZZE MIN A\’RSHEKA WA BE MUNTAHAR RAH\’MATE MIN KETAABEKA WA-BEMA LAU ANNA MAA FIL ARZ"E MIN SHAJA-RATIN AQLAAMUN WAL BAH\’RO YAMUDDOHO MIN BA\’DEHI SAB-A\’TO ABH\’ORIN MAA NA FEDAT KALEMAA TULLAAHE IN NALLAAHA A\’ZEEZUN H\’AKEEMUN WA AS-ALOKA BE ASMAAEKAL H\’USNA ALLATI NAA\’ ATTAHA FEE KETAA BEKA FAQULTA WALIL LAAHIL ASMAAUL H\’US NA FADO\’OHO BEHA WA-QULTA UDO\’OONI ASTA JIB LAKUM WAQULTA WA ID\’AA SA-LAKA I\’BAADI A\’NNI FA INNI QAREEBUN OJEEBO DAA\’WATAD DAA\’I ID\’AA DA\’AANE WA QULTA YAA I\’BAADEYAL LA D\’EENA ASRAFU A\’LAA ANFOSEHIM LAA TAQNAT\’U MIN RAH\’ MATILLAAHE INNAL LAAHA YAGH FERUD\’ D\’UNOOBA JAMEE\’AN INNAHU HOWAL GHAFOORUR RAH\’EEMO WA ANA AS AOLAKA YAA ILAAHI WA ADO\’OAKA YAA RABBE WA ARJOOKA YAA SAYYEDI WA AT\’MAA\’O FEE IJAABATI YAA MAULAAYA KAMAA WA A\’D TANI WA QAD DAA\’AOTOKA KAMAA AMARTANI FAF A\’L BI MAA ANTA AHLOHU YAA KAREEMO WAL H\’AM DO LILLAHE RABBIL A\’A LAMEENA WA S\’ALAL LAAHO A\’LAA MUH\’AM MADIN WA AALEHI AJMAE\’ENA




    </string>




    <string name="title_activity_b1">B1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_activity2">MainActivity2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b2">B2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b3">B3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b4">B4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b5">B5</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b6">B6</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b7">B7</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b8">B8</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b9">B9</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b10">B10</string>
    <string name="title_activity_b11">B11</string>
    <string name="title_activity_duas">Duas</string>
    <string name="title_activity_namaz">Namaz</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c1">C1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c2">C2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c3">C3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c4">C4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c5">C5</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c6">C6</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a1">A1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a2">A2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a3">A3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a4">A4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a5">A5</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a6">A6</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a7">A7</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a8">A8</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a9">A9</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a10">A10</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a11">A11</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a12">A12</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a13">A13</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a14">A14</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a15">A15</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a16">A16</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a17">A17</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a18">A18</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a19">A19</string>
    <string name="title_activity_a20">A20</string>
</resources>
